{"prompt": "28100,28101,28102,28103,28104,28105,28106,28107,28108", "answer": "28109"}
{"prompt": "36667,36668,36669,36670,36671,36672,36673,36674", "answer": "36675"}
{"prompt": "19211,19212", "answer": "19213"}
{"prompt": "27820,27821,27822,27823,27824", "answer": "27825"}
{"prompt": "28935,28936,28937,28938,28939,28940,28941,28942,28943", "answer": "28944"}
{"prompt": "37054,37055,37056,37057,37058,37059", "answer": "37060"}
{"prompt": "25306,25307,25308,25309,25310,25311", "answer": "25312"}
{"prompt": "36730,36731,36732,36733,36734,36735,36736", "answer": "36737"}
{"prompt": "24312,24313,24314,24315,24316,24317,24318,24319", "answer": "24320"}
{"prompt": "14440,14441,14442,14443,14444,14445,14446,14447,14448", "answer": "14449"}
{"prompt": "20612,20613,20614", "answer": "20615"}
{"prompt": "22241,22242,22243,22244,22245", "answer": "22246"}
{"prompt": "40279,40280,40281,40282,40283,40284", "answer": "40285"}
{"prompt": "14549,14550,14551,14552,14553,14554,14555,14556", "answer": "14557"}
{"prompt": "34354", "answer": "34355"}
{"prompt": "15522,15523,15524,15525,15526,15527,15528,15529", "answer": "15530"}
{"prompt": "1147,1148,1149,1150,1151,1152,1153", "answer": "1154"}
{"prompt": "39254,39255,39256,39257,39258,39259,39260,39261,39262", "answer": "39263"}
{"prompt": "21334,21335,21336", "answer": "21337"}
{"prompt": "4894,4895,4896,4897,4898,4899,4900,4901,4902,4903", "answer": "4904"}
{"prompt": "4381,4382,4383,4384", "answer": "4385"}
{"prompt": "16751,16752,16753,16754,16755,16756", "answer": "16757"}
{"prompt": "35100,35101,35102,35103,35104", "answer": "35105"}
{"prompt": "1973,1974,1975,1976", "answer": "1977"}
{"prompt": "39622", "answer": "39623"}
{"prompt": "26879,26880,26881,26882,26883", "answer": "26884"}
{"prompt": "28259,28260", "answer": "28261"}
{"prompt": "14209,14210,14211", "answer": "14212"}
{"prompt": "4168,4169", "answer": "4170"}
{"prompt": "38373", "answer": "38374"}
{"prompt": "24439,24440,24441,24442", "answer": "24443"}
{"prompt": "18675,18676,18677,18678,18679,18680,18681,18682,18683,18684", "answer": "18685"}
{"prompt": "39952,39953", "answer": "39954"}
{"prompt": "41891", "answer": "41892"}
{"prompt": "29267,29268,29269,29270,29271,29272,29273,29274,29275,29276", "answer": "29277"}
{"prompt": "24649", "answer": "24650"}
{"prompt": "27628,27629,27630,27631,27632,27633,27634", "answer": "27635"}
{"prompt": "36284,36285,36286,36287,36288", "answer": "36289"}
{"prompt": "40414,40415", "answer": "40416"}
{"prompt": "29706,29707,29708,29709,29710,29711,29712", "answer": "29713"}
{"prompt": "27296,27297,27298,27299,27300,27301,27302,27303,27304,27305", "answer": "27306"}
{"prompt": "18158,18159,18160,18161,18162,18163,18164,18165", "answer": "18166"}
{"prompt": "40142,40143,40144,40145,40146,40147,40148,40149,40150", "answer": "40151"}
{"prompt": "35779,35780,35781,35782", "answer": "35783"}
{"prompt": "6400,6401,6402,6403,6404,6405,6406,6407,6408,6409", "answer": "6410"}
{"prompt": "24891,24892,24893,24894,24895,24896,24897,24898", "answer": "24899"}
{"prompt": "38291,38292,38293", "answer": "38294"}
{"prompt": "6013,6014,6015,6016,6017,6018,6019,6020", "answer": "6021"}
{"prompt": "43035,43036,43037", "answer": "43038"}
{"prompt": "27101,27102,27103,27104,27105,27106,27107", "answer": "27108"}
{"prompt": "25948,25949,25950,25951,25952,25953,25954", "answer": "25955"}
{"prompt": "35494,35495,35496,35497,35498,35499", "answer": "35500"}
{"prompt": "38790,38791,38792,38793,38794,38795,38796", "answer": "38797"}
{"prompt": "10890,10891,10892,10893,10894,10895,10896,10897,10898", "answer": "10899"}
{"prompt": "7720,7721,7722,7723,7724,7725,7726,7727", "answer": "7728"}
{"prompt": "40338,40339,40340,40341,40342,40343,40344", "answer": "40345"}
{"prompt": "43254,43255,43256,43257,43258,43259,43260,43261", "answer": "43262"}
{"prompt": "11415,11416,11417,11418,11419,11420,11421", "answer": "11422"}
{"prompt": "18614,18615,18616,18617,18618,18619,18620,18621,18622,18623", "answer": "18624"}
{"prompt": "44390,44391,44392,44393,44394,44395", "answer": "44396"}
{"prompt": "10272,10273,10274,10275,10276", "answer": "10277"}
{"prompt": "15921,15922,15923", "answer": "15924"}
{"prompt": "10958", "answer": "10959"}
{"prompt": "20399", "answer": "20400"}
{"prompt": "42979,42980,42981,42982", "answer": "42983"}
{"prompt": "14448,14449,14450,14451,14452,14453,14454", "answer": "14455"}
{"prompt": "28910,28911,28912,28913,28914,28915,28916,28917,28918", "answer": "28919"}
{"prompt": "5988,5989,5990,5991,5992,5993,5994", "answer": "5995"}
{"prompt": "32026,32027,32028,32029,32030", "answer": "32031"}
{"prompt": "39473", "answer": "39474"}
{"prompt": "12272,12273,12274,12275,12276,12277", "answer": "12278"}
{"prompt": "3365,3366,3367,3368,3369", "answer": "3370"}
{"prompt": "28365,28366,28367,28368,28369,28370,28371,28372,28373,28374", "answer": "28375"}
{"prompt": "13614,13615,13616,13617,13618,13619,13620,13621,13622,13623", "answer": "13624"}
{"prompt": "7634,7635,7636,7637", "answer": "7638"}
{"prompt": "6079,6080,6081", "answer": "6082"}
{"prompt": "21236,21237,21238,21239,21240,21241", "answer": "21242"}
{"prompt": "16787,16788,16789,16790,16791,16792", "answer": "16793"}
{"prompt": "1680,1681,1682,1683,1684,1685", "answer": "1686"}
{"prompt": "1957", "answer": "1958"}
{"prompt": "41779", "answer": "41780"}
{"prompt": "35018,35019", "answer": "35020"}
{"prompt": "31017,31018,31019", "answer": "31020"}
{"prompt": "26760,26761,26762,26763,26764,26765,26766,26767,26768", "answer": "26769"}
{"prompt": "33238", "answer": "33239"}
{"prompt": "28076,28077,28078,28079", "answer": "28080"}
{"prompt": "18914", "answer": "18915"}
{"prompt": "45300,45301,45302", "answer": "45303"}
{"prompt": "8573,8574,8575", "answer": "8576"}
{"prompt": "2942,2943", "answer": "2944"}
{"prompt": "26422,26423,26424", "answer": "26425"}
{"prompt": "24228,24229,24230,24231,24232,24233", "answer": "24234"}
{"prompt": "22569,22570,22571,22572", "answer": "22573"}
{"prompt": "4307,4308,4309,4310,4311", "answer": "4312"}
{"prompt": "34154,34155,34156,34157,34158,34159,34160,34161,34162", "answer": "34163"}
{"prompt": "39692,39693,39694,39695,39696,39697,39698", "answer": "39699"}
{"prompt": "35233,35234,35235", "answer": "35236"}
{"prompt": "26684,26685,26686,26687", "answer": "26688"}
{"prompt": "17243,17244,17245,17246,17247,17248,17249,17250", "answer": "17251"}
{"prompt": "39988,39989,39990,39991,39992,39993,39994,39995", "answer": "39996"}
{"prompt": "36133,36134,36135,36136,36137,36138,36139,36140,36141,36142", "answer": "36143"}
{"prompt": "39975,39976,39977,39978,39979", "answer": "39980"}
{"prompt": "34655,34656", "answer": "34657"}
{"prompt": "12322,12323,12324,12325,12326", "answer": "12327"}
{"prompt": "14149,14150,14151,14152,14153,14154", "answer": "14155"}
{"prompt": "456,457,458,459,460,461,462", "answer": "463"}
{"prompt": "40837,40838,40839,40840,40841,40842,40843,40844", "answer": "40845"}
{"prompt": "22407,22408,22409,22410,22411,22412,22413", "answer": "22414"}
{"prompt": "43165,43166,43167,43168,43169,43170,43171", "answer": "43172"}
{"prompt": "27019,27020,27021,27022", "answer": "27023"}
{"prompt": "9935,9936,9937,9938,9939,9940,9941,9942", "answer": "9943"}
{"prompt": "25798,25799,25800,25801", "answer": "25802"}
{"prompt": "309,310,311,312,313,314,315,316", "answer": "317"}
{"prompt": "18939,18940,18941,18942,18943,18944,18945", "answer": "18946"}
{"prompt": "34140,34141,34142,34143,34144", "answer": "34145"}
{"prompt": "11196,11197,11198,11199,11200,11201,11202", "answer": "11203"}
{"prompt": "17638,17639,17640,17641,17642", "answer": "17643"}
{"prompt": "28192,28193,28194,28195,28196,28197,28198,28199,28200", "answer": "28201"}
{"prompt": "13547,13548,13549", "answer": "13550"}
{"prompt": "2621,2622,2623,2624,2625,2626", "answer": "2627"}
{"prompt": "17371,17372", "answer": "17373"}
{"prompt": "25066,25067,25068,25069,25070,25071,25072,25073,25074", "answer": "25075"}
{"prompt": "25372,25373,25374,25375,25376,25377,25378,25379,25380", "answer": "25381"}
{"prompt": "19935,19936,19937,19938,19939,19940,19941,19942,19943,19944", "answer": "19945"}
{"prompt": "44568,44569,44570", "answer": "44571"}
{"prompt": "38099,38100,38101,38102,38103,38104,38105,38106,38107,38108", "answer": "38109"}
{"prompt": "34326,34327,34328,34329,34330,34331,34332,34333,34334,34335", "answer": "34336"}
{"prompt": "7382,7383,7384,7385,7386,7387", "answer": "7388"}
{"prompt": "38391,38392,38393,38394,38395,38396,38397,38398", "answer": "38399"}
{"prompt": "26267,26268", "answer": "26269"}
{"prompt": "1036,1037,1038,1039,1040,1041,1042", "answer": "1043"}
{"prompt": "9376", "answer": "9377"}
{"prompt": "42946,42947,42948,42949,42950,42951,42952,42953,42954", "answer": "42955"}
{"prompt": "30666,30667,30668,30669,30670,30671,30672,30673,30674,30675", "answer": "30676"}
{"prompt": "44647,44648,44649,44650,44651,44652,44653,44654", "answer": "44655"}
{"prompt": "31280,31281,31282,31283,31284,31285,31286,31287,31288", "answer": "31289"}
{"prompt": "8677,8678", "answer": "8679"}
{"prompt": "11972,11973,11974,11975,11976,11977,11978,11979", "answer": "11980"}
{"prompt": "15508,15509,15510,15511,15512,15513", "answer": "15514"}
{"prompt": "36877,36878,36879,36880,36881", "answer": "36882"}
{"prompt": "25889,25890,25891,25892,25893,25894", "answer": "25895"}
{"prompt": "43338,43339,43340", "answer": "43341"}
{"prompt": "28990", "answer": "28991"}
{"prompt": "17614,17615", "answer": "17616"}
{"prompt": "27691,27692,27693", "answer": "27694"}
{"prompt": "30901,30902,30903,30904,30905,30906", "answer": "30907"}
{"prompt": "42776,42777,42778,42779,42780", "answer": "42781"}
{"prompt": "37694,37695", "answer": "37696"}
{"prompt": "31577", "answer": "31578"}
{"prompt": "22461,22462,22463,22464,22465,22466,22467,22468", "answer": "22469"}
{"prompt": "4671,4672,4673,4674,4675,4676,4677,4678", "answer": "4679"}
{"prompt": "4395,4396,4397,4398,4399,4400,4401,4402", "answer": "4403"}
{"prompt": "35749,35750,35751,35752,35753,35754,35755,35756,35757,35758", "answer": "35759"}
{"prompt": "37907,37908,37909,37910,37911,37912,37913,37914", "answer": "37915"}
{"prompt": "1568,1569,1570,1571,1572,1573,1574,1575", "answer": "1576"}
{"prompt": "42759,42760,42761,42762,42763,42764,42765,42766,42767", "answer": "42768"}
{"prompt": "34447,34448,34449,34450", "answer": "34451"}
{"prompt": "37839,37840", "answer": "37841"}
{"prompt": "21259,21260", "answer": "21261"}
{"prompt": "43608,43609,43610", "answer": "43611"}
{"prompt": "42815,42816,42817,42818,42819", "answer": "42820"}
{"prompt": "44736,44737,44738", "answer": "44739"}
{"prompt": "32140,32141", "answer": "32142"}
{"prompt": "34234,34235,34236,34237", "answer": "34238"}
{"prompt": "25514,25515,25516,25517,25518,25519,25520,25521,25522", "answer": "25523"}
{"prompt": "28884", "answer": "28885"}
{"prompt": "24333,24334,24335,24336,24337,24338,24339,24340,24341", "answer": "24342"}
{"prompt": "29553,29554,29555,29556", "answer": "29557"}
{"prompt": "30914", "answer": "30915"}
{"prompt": "12812,12813,12814,12815,12816,12817,12818", "answer": "12819"}
{"prompt": "9876,9877,9878,9879,9880,9881,9882,9883,9884,9885", "answer": "9886"}
{"prompt": "41379,41380,41381,41382", "answer": "41383"}
{"prompt": "35619,35620,35621,35622,35623,35624,35625,35626,35627", "answer": "35628"}
{"prompt": "23972,23973,23974,23975,23976,23977,23978,23979", "answer": "23980"}
{"prompt": "8961,8962,8963,8964", "answer": "8965"}
{"prompt": "39506,39507,39508,39509,39510,39511,39512,39513,39514", "answer": "39515"}
{"prompt": "6850,6851,6852", "answer": "6853"}
{"prompt": "16679,16680,16681,16682,16683,16684", "answer": "16685"}
{"prompt": "30236,30237,30238,30239,30240,30241,30242,30243", "answer": "30244"}
{"prompt": "38182,38183,38184,38185,38186,38187,38188,38189,38190,38191", "answer": "38192"}
{"prompt": "44269,44270,44271,44272", "answer": "44273"}
{"prompt": "4855", "answer": "4856"}
{"prompt": "34808,34809,34810,34811,34812,34813,34814", "answer": "34815"}
{"prompt": "21207,21208,21209,21210", "answer": "21211"}
{"prompt": "32955,32956", "answer": "32957"}
{"prompt": "2903,2904,2905,2906", "answer": "2907"}
{"prompt": "14366,14367,14368,14369,14370,14371,14372,14373", "answer": "14374"}
{"prompt": "15384", "answer": "15385"}
{"prompt": "16182,16183,16184,16185,16186,16187,16188", "answer": "16189"}
{"prompt": "35851,35852,35853,35854,35855,35856,35857,35858,35859", "answer": "35860"}
{"prompt": "12266,12267,12268,12269,12270,12271,12272", "answer": "12273"}
{"prompt": "29918,29919,29920,29921,29922,29923", "answer": "29924"}
{"prompt": "41309", "answer": "41310"}
{"prompt": "29963,29964,29965,29966,29967,29968,29969", "answer": "29970"}
{"prompt": "35647,35648,35649,35650,35651,35652", "answer": "35653"}
{"prompt": "15306,15307,15308,15309,15310,15311,15312,15313", "answer": "15314"}
{"prompt": "44893,44894,44895,44896,44897,44898,44899", "answer": "44900"}
{"prompt": "30432,30433,30434,30435,30436,30437,30438,30439,30440,30441", "answer": "30442"}
{"prompt": "14239,14240,14241,14242,14243", "answer": "14244"}
{"prompt": "24908", "answer": "24909"}
{"prompt": "44970,44971,44972,44973", "answer": "44974"}
{"prompt": "22953,22954,22955,22956,22957,22958,22959,22960,22961,22962", "answer": "22963"}
{"prompt": "36580,36581,36582,36583,36584,36585", "answer": "36586"}
{"prompt": "40367,40368,40369", "answer": "40370"}
{"prompt": "34197,34198,34199,34200,34201,34202,34203,34204", "answer": "34205"}
{"prompt": "32753,32754,32755,32756,32757,32758", "answer": "32759"}
{"prompt": "33315,33316,33317", "answer": "33318"}
{"prompt": "43867,43868", "answer": "43869"}
{"prompt": "18939", "answer": "18940"}
{"prompt": "17479,17480", "answer": "17481"}
{"prompt": "28751,28752", "answer": "28753"}
{"prompt": "7872,7873,7874,7875", "answer": "7876"}
{"prompt": "23401,23402,23403,23404,23405,23406,23407", "answer": "23408"}
{"prompt": "41858,41859,41860,41861,41862,41863", "answer": "41864"}
{"prompt": "33841,33842,33843,33844,33845,33846,33847,33848", "answer": "33849"}
{"prompt": "10385,10386", "answer": "10387"}
{"prompt": "45134,45135", "answer": "45136"}
{"prompt": "14717,14718,14719,14720,14721,14722,14723,14724,14725", "answer": "14726"}
{"prompt": "35575,35576,35577,35578,35579,35580,35581", "answer": "35582"}
{"prompt": "2347,2348,2349", "answer": "2350"}
{"prompt": "17912", "answer": "17913"}
{"prompt": "37044,37045", "answer": "37046"}
{"prompt": "18488,18489,18490,18491,18492,18493", "answer": "18494"}
{"prompt": "576,577,578,579,580", "answer": "581"}
{"prompt": "14789,14790,14791", "answer": "14792"}
{"prompt": "19021,19022,19023,19024,19025", "answer": "19026"}
{"prompt": "39024,39025,39026", "answer": "39027"}
{"prompt": "25239,25240,25241,25242,25243,25244", "answer": "25245"}
{"prompt": "8723,8724,8725,8726", "answer": "8727"}
{"prompt": "7632,7633,7634", "answer": "7635"}
{"prompt": "33450,33451,33452,33453,33454,33455,33456", "answer": "33457"}
{"prompt": "16100,16101,16102,16103,16104,16105,16106", "answer": "16107"}
{"prompt": "36944,36945,36946,36947,36948", "answer": "36949"}
{"prompt": "9464,9465,9466", "answer": "9467"}
{"prompt": "26724,26725,26726,26727,26728,26729,26730,26731", "answer": "26732"}
{"prompt": "15969,15970,15971,15972,15973,15974,15975,15976,15977", "answer": "15978"}
{"prompt": "27081,27082,27083,27084,27085,27086,27087,27088,27089", "answer": "27090"}
{"prompt": "32350,32351,32352,32353,32354,32355,32356", "answer": "32357"}
{"prompt": "10822,10823", "answer": "10824"}
{"prompt": "12519,12520,12521,12522,12523,12524,12525,12526,12527", "answer": "12528"}
{"prompt": "28777,28778,28779", "answer": "28780"}
{"prompt": "9544,9545,9546,9547,9548,9549,9550,9551", "answer": "9552"}
{"prompt": "17144,17145,17146,17147", "answer": "17148"}
{"prompt": "9282", "answer": "9283"}
{"prompt": "28111", "answer": "28112"}
{"prompt": "14734", "answer": "14735"}
{"prompt": "11540,11541,11542,11543,11544,11545,11546,11547,11548", "answer": "11549"}
{"prompt": "27984,27985,27986,27987,27988,27989,27990,27991", "answer": "27992"}
{"prompt": "37671", "answer": "37672"}
{"prompt": "14166,14167,14168,14169", "answer": "14170"}
{"prompt": "43989,43990,43991", "answer": "43992"}
{"prompt": "1813,1814,1815,1816,1817,1818", "answer": "1819"}
{"prompt": "8923,8924,8925,8926,8927", "answer": "8928"}
{"prompt": "42183", "answer": "42184"}
{"prompt": "26695,26696", "answer": "26697"}
{"prompt": "40775,40776", "answer": "40777"}
{"prompt": "35766,35767,35768,35769,35770,35771,35772,35773", "answer": "35774"}
{"prompt": "19242,19243", "answer": "19244"}
{"prompt": "18909,18910,18911", "answer": "18912"}
{"prompt": "26053,26054,26055,26056,26057,26058,26059,26060,26061", "answer": "26062"}
{"prompt": "13010,13011,13012,13013", "answer": "13014"}
{"prompt": "33475,33476,33477,33478,33479,33480", "answer": "33481"}
{"prompt": "41495,41496,41497,41498,41499,41500,41501,41502,41503,41504", "answer": "41505"}
{"prompt": "25765,25766", "answer": "25767"}
{"prompt": "38758", "answer": "38759"}
{"prompt": "14412,14413,14414,14415,14416,14417", "answer": "14418"}
{"prompt": "40437,40438,40439,40440,40441,40442,40443", "answer": "40444"}
{"prompt": "31429,31430,31431", "answer": "31432"}
{"prompt": "21477,21478,21479,21480,21481,21482,21483,21484,21485,21486", "answer": "21487"}
{"prompt": "12241,12242,12243,12244,12245,12246,12247,12248,12249", "answer": "12250"}
{"prompt": "20357,20358,20359,20360,20361,20362,20363", "answer": "20364"}
{"prompt": "37965,37966,37967,37968,37969,37970,37971,37972,37973", "answer": "37974"}
{"prompt": "14071,14072,14073,14074,14075,14076,14077,14078,14079,14080", "answer": "14081"}
{"prompt": "23085,23086,23087,23088,23089,23090,23091,23092,23093", "answer": "23094"}
{"prompt": "43487,43488,43489,43490,43491,43492", "answer": "43493"}
{"prompt": "18025,18026,18027", "answer": "18028"}
{"prompt": "2447,2448,2449,2450,2451", "answer": "2452"}
{"prompt": "22968,22969", "answer": "22970"}
{"prompt": "13679,13680,13681,13682,13683,13684,13685,13686,13687,13688", "answer": "13689"}
{"prompt": "13304,13305,13306,13307,13308,13309,13310,13311,13312", "answer": "13313"}
{"prompt": "42919,42920,42921,42922,42923,42924,42925,42926", "answer": "42927"}
{"prompt": "22166,22167,22168,22169,22170,22171,22172,22173", "answer": "22174"}
{"prompt": "10398,10399,10400,10401,10402,10403,10404,10405,10406", "answer": "10407"}
{"prompt": "25810,25811,25812", "answer": "25813"}
{"prompt": "33404,33405,33406", "answer": "33407"}
{"prompt": "9219,9220,9221,9222,9223,9224,9225", "answer": "9226"}
{"prompt": "8198,8199,8200,8201,8202,8203,8204,8205", "answer": "8206"}
{"prompt": "44718,44719,44720,44721,44722,44723,44724,44725,44726", "answer": "44727"}
{"prompt": "40932,40933,40934,40935,40936,40937,40938,40939,40940", "answer": "40941"}
{"prompt": "10697,10698,10699,10700,10701", "answer": "10702"}
{"prompt": "27187,27188,27189", "answer": "27190"}
{"prompt": "12566,12567,12568,12569,12570", "answer": "12571"}
{"prompt": "41107,41108,41109,41110,41111,41112,41113,41114,41115", "answer": "41116"}
{"prompt": "34772,34773,34774,34775,34776", "answer": "34777"}
{"prompt": "13849,13850,13851,13852,13853,13854,13855,13856", "answer": "13857"}
{"prompt": "44090,44091,44092,44093,44094,44095,44096", "answer": "44097"}
{"prompt": "11558,11559,11560,11561,11562,11563,11564", "answer": "11565"}
{"prompt": "11989,11990,11991,11992,11993,11994,11995,11996,11997", "answer": "11998"}
{"prompt": "34431,34432", "answer": "34433"}
{"prompt": "40999,41000,41001,41002,41003,41004", "answer": "41005"}
{"prompt": "127,128,129", "answer": "130"}
{"prompt": "34965,34966,34967,34968,34969,34970,34971,34972", "answer": "34973"}
{"prompt": "875,876", "answer": "877"}
{"prompt": "7240,7241,7242,7243,7244,7245", "answer": "7246"}
{"prompt": "44562,44563,44564,44565,44566,44567,44568", "answer": "44569"}
{"prompt": "33518,33519,33520,33521,33522", "answer": "33523"}
{"prompt": "33784,33785,33786,33787,33788,33789,33790", "answer": "33791"}
{"prompt": "26842,26843,26844,26845,26846,26847,26848,26849,26850,26851", "answer": "26852"}
{"prompt": "3162,3163,3164,3165,3166", "answer": "3167"}
{"prompt": "36146,36147", "answer": "36148"}
{"prompt": "1548,1549,1550,1551,1552,1553", "answer": "1554"}
{"prompt": "70,71,72,73", "answer": "74"}
{"prompt": "9336,9337,9338,9339,9340,9341,9342,9343", "answer": "9344"}
{"prompt": "3299,3300", "answer": "3301"}
{"prompt": "24151,24152,24153,24154,24155,24156,24157,24158,24159", "answer": "24160"}
{"prompt": "42549,42550,42551,42552", "answer": "42553"}
{"prompt": "521,522,523,524,525,526,527,528,529,530", "answer": "531"}
{"prompt": "38202,38203,38204,38205,38206,38207,38208,38209,38210,38211", "answer": "38212"}
{"prompt": "44755,44756,44757,44758,44759", "answer": "44760"}
{"prompt": "29479,29480", "answer": "29481"}
{"prompt": "2533,2534,2535,2536", "answer": "2537"}
{"prompt": "19288,19289,19290,19291,19292,19293,19294,19295,19296,19297", "answer": "19298"}
{"prompt": "23527,23528,23529,23530", "answer": "23531"}
{"prompt": "20236,20237,20238,20239", "answer": "20240"}
{"prompt": "14616", "answer": "14617"}
{"prompt": "12944,12945,12946,12947,12948", "answer": "12949"}
{"prompt": "27729,27730,27731,27732,27733,27734,27735,27736", "answer": "27737"}
{"prompt": "20040", "answer": "20041"}
{"prompt": "3511,3512,3513,3514,3515,3516,3517,3518,3519,3520", "answer": "3521"}
{"prompt": "1889,1890,1891,1892,1893,1894,1895", "answer": "1896"}
{"prompt": "6214,6215,6216,6217", "answer": "6218"}
{"prompt": "5512,5513,5514,5515,5516,5517,5518", "answer": "5519"}
{"prompt": "11045,11046,11047,11048,11049,11050", "answer": "11051"}
{"prompt": "5854,5855,5856,5857,5858,5859,5860", "answer": "5861"}
{"prompt": "7931,7932,7933,7934,7935,7936,7937,7938,7939", "answer": "7940"}
{"prompt": "7766,7767", "answer": "7768"}
{"prompt": "32287,32288,32289,32290,32291,32292,32293", "answer": "32294"}
{"prompt": "31984,31985,31986,31987", "answer": "31988"}
{"prompt": "18914,18915,18916,18917,18918,18919,18920,18921,18922,18923", "answer": "18924"}
{"prompt": "7266,7267,7268,7269,7270", "answer": "7271"}
{"prompt": "6483,6484,6485,6486", "answer": "6487"}
{"prompt": "9457", "answer": "9458"}
{"prompt": "19297,19298,19299,19300,19301", "answer": "19302"}
{"prompt": "31434,31435,31436,31437,31438,31439,31440,31441,31442,31443", "answer": "31444"}
{"prompt": "24639,24640,24641,24642,24643", "answer": "24644"}
{"prompt": "34270,34271,34272,34273,34274,34275,34276,34277,34278", "answer": "34279"}
{"prompt": "41384,41385,41386,41387,41388,41389", "answer": "41390"}
{"prompt": "13719,13720,13721,13722,13723,13724", "answer": "13725"}
{"prompt": "32818,32819,32820,32821", "answer": "32822"}
{"prompt": "38538,38539", "answer": "38540"}
{"prompt": "33641,33642,33643,33644,33645,33646", "answer": "33647"}
{"prompt": "4645,4646,4647,4648,4649,4650", "answer": "4651"}
{"prompt": "14309,14310,14311", "answer": "14312"}
{"prompt": "39791,39792,39793,39794", "answer": "39795"}
{"prompt": "20686,20687,20688,20689,20690,20691,20692,20693,20694", "answer": "20695"}
{"prompt": "13512,13513,13514,13515,13516,13517", "answer": "13518"}
{"prompt": "17441,17442,17443", "answer": "17444"}
{"prompt": "7424,7425,7426,7427,7428,7429,7430,7431,7432", "answer": "7433"}
{"prompt": "36421,36422,36423,36424,36425", "answer": "36426"}
{"prompt": "44230,44231,44232,44233,44234,44235,44236,44237,44238,44239", "answer": "44240"}
{"prompt": "31987,31988", "answer": "31989"}
{"prompt": "38139,38140,38141,38142,38143,38144,38145", "answer": "38146"}
{"prompt": "39564,39565,39566,39567", "answer": "39568"}
{"prompt": "26248,26249,26250,26251,26252", "answer": "26253"}
{"prompt": "12849,12850,12851,12852,12853,12854,12855,12856,12857,12858", "answer": "12859"}
{"prompt": "22086,22087,22088", "answer": "22089"}
{"prompt": "28842,28843,28844,28845", "answer": "28846"}
{"prompt": "28708,28709,28710,28711,28712,28713", "answer": "28714"}
{"prompt": "41999,42000,42001,42002,42003", "answer": "42004"}
{"prompt": "6339,6340,6341,6342,6343,6344,6345", "answer": "6346"}
{"prompt": "22028,22029,22030,22031", "answer": "22032"}
{"prompt": "15426,15427,15428,15429,15430,15431", "answer": "15432"}
{"prompt": "10414,10415,10416", "answer": "10417"}
{"prompt": "14890,14891,14892,14893,14894,14895,14896,14897,14898,14899", "answer": "14900"}
{"prompt": "13864,13865,13866", "answer": "13867"}
{"prompt": "11098,11099,11100,11101,11102,11103,11104,11105", "answer": "11106"}
{"prompt": "808,809,810,811,812,813,814,815", "answer": "816"}
{"prompt": "16756,16757,16758,16759,16760,16761,16762,16763,16764,16765", "answer": "16766"}
{"prompt": "36106,36107,36108,36109,36110", "answer": "36111"}
{"prompt": "5115,5116,5117,5118,5119,5120,5121,5122,5123,5124", "answer": "5125"}
{"prompt": "9265,9266,9267,9268,9269", "answer": "9270"}
{"prompt": "18903", "answer": "18904"}
{"prompt": "35948", "answer": "35949"}
{"prompt": "40235,40236,40237,40238,40239", "answer": "40240"}
{"prompt": "25844,25845,25846,25847,25848,25849", "answer": "25850"}
{"prompt": "42301,42302,42303,42304,42305,42306,42307", "answer": "42308"}
{"prompt": "34365,34366,34367,34368,34369", "answer": "34370"}
{"prompt": "43819,43820,43821,43822,43823,43824,43825,43826", "answer": "43827"}
{"prompt": "4774,4775,4776,4777,4778,4779,4780,4781,4782", "answer": "4783"}
{"prompt": "24906", "answer": "24907"}
{"prompt": "18036", "answer": "18037"}
{"prompt": "27846,27847", "answer": "27848"}
{"prompt": "42636", "answer": "42637"}
{"prompt": "34661,34662", "answer": "34663"}
{"prompt": "18103,18104,18105,18106", "answer": "18107"}
{"prompt": "25696,25697,25698,25699,25700,25701,25702,25703", "answer": "25704"}
{"prompt": "38573,38574,38575", "answer": "38576"}
{"prompt": "39556,39557,39558,39559,39560,39561,39562,39563,39564", "answer": "39565"}
{"prompt": "23836,23837,23838,23839,23840,23841", "answer": "23842"}
{"prompt": "39621,39622", "answer": "39623"}
{"prompt": "6779,6780", "answer": "6781"}
{"prompt": "17357,17358,17359,17360", "answer": "17361"}
{"prompt": "26473,26474,26475,26476,26477,26478,26479,26480,26481", "answer": "26482"}
{"prompt": "45307,45308", "answer": "45309"}
{"prompt": "24233,24234,24235,24236,24237,24238,24239", "answer": "24240"}
{"prompt": "34656,34657,34658,34659,34660,34661", "answer": "34662"}
{"prompt": "24373,24374,24375,24376,24377,24378,24379", "answer": "24380"}
{"prompt": "5740", "answer": "5741"}
{"prompt": "4039,4040,4041,4042,4043,4044,4045,4046,4047,4048", "answer": "4049"}
{"prompt": "37848,37849,37850,37851,37852,37853", "answer": "37854"}
{"prompt": "40692", "answer": "40693"}
{"prompt": "10149,10150,10151,10152,10153,10154,10155,10156", "answer": "10157"}
{"prompt": "36821,36822", "answer": "36823"}
{"prompt": "41282,41283,41284,41285,41286,41287,41288,41289", "answer": "41290"}
{"prompt": "23118,23119,23120,23121,23122", "answer": "23123"}
{"prompt": "17072,17073,17074,17075", "answer": "17076"}
{"prompt": "40776,40777,40778,40779,40780,40781,40782", "answer": "40783"}
{"prompt": "24121,24122,24123,24124,24125,24126,24127,24128,24129,24130", "answer": "24131"}
{"prompt": "1987,1988", "answer": "1989"}
{"prompt": "36995,36996", "answer": "36997"}
{"prompt": "17664,17665,17666,17667,17668,17669,17670,17671,17672,17673", "answer": "17674"}
{"prompt": "12177,12178,12179,12180,12181,12182,12183", "answer": "12184"}
{"prompt": "20048,20049,20050,20051,20052,20053,20054", "answer": "20055"}
{"prompt": "34616,34617,34618", "answer": "34619"}
{"prompt": "14704,14705,14706", "answer": "14707"}
{"prompt": "31213", "answer": "31214"}
{"prompt": "43159,43160,43161,43162,43163,43164,43165", "answer": "43166"}
{"prompt": "16448,16449,16450,16451,16452,16453", "answer": "16454"}
{"prompt": "33083,33084,33085,33086,33087,33088", "answer": "33089"}
{"prompt": "43715,43716,43717,43718,43719,43720,43721,43722,43723", "answer": "43724"}
{"prompt": "19580", "answer": "19581"}
{"prompt": "39403,39404,39405,39406,39407", "answer": "39408"}
{"prompt": "2216,2217", "answer": "2218"}
{"prompt": "12933,12934,12935,12936,12937,12938,12939,12940,12941,12942", "answer": "12943"}
{"prompt": "36091", "answer": "36092"}
{"prompt": "43053,43054,43055,43056,43057,43058", "answer": "43059"}
{"prompt": "19314,19315", "answer": "19316"}
{"prompt": "39661,39662,39663,39664,39665,39666,39667", "answer": "39668"}
{"prompt": "36449,36450,36451,36452,36453,36454,36455", "answer": "36456"}
{"prompt": "4484,4485,4486", "answer": "4487"}
{"prompt": "19469,19470,19471,19472,19473,19474", "answer": "19475"}
{"prompt": "30707,30708,30709,30710,30711", "answer": "30712"}
{"prompt": "32732,32733,32734,32735,32736,32737,32738,32739", "answer": "32740"}
{"prompt": "10207,10208,10209,10210,10211,10212", "answer": "10213"}
{"prompt": "22852,22853,22854,22855,22856", "answer": "22857"}
{"prompt": "37712,37713,37714,37715,37716", "answer": "37717"}
{"prompt": "30184,30185,30186,30187", "answer": "30188"}
{"prompt": "20461", "answer": "20462"}
{"prompt": "4976,4977,4978,4979,4980", "answer": "4981"}
{"prompt": "29702,29703,29704,29705,29706", "answer": "29707"}
{"prompt": "13233,13234", "answer": "13235"}
{"prompt": "17814,17815,17816,17817", "answer": "17818"}
{"prompt": "18349,18350,18351,18352,18353,18354,18355", "answer": "18356"}
{"prompt": "32228,32229,32230,32231,32232,32233,32234,32235", "answer": "32236"}
{"prompt": "9591,9592,9593,9594,9595,9596", "answer": "9597"}
{"prompt": "35818,35819,35820,35821,35822,35823", "answer": "35824"}
{"prompt": "5009,5010,5011,5012,5013,5014", "answer": "5015"}
{"prompt": "1345,1346,1347,1348,1349", "answer": "1350"}
{"prompt": "19093,19094", "answer": "19095"}
{"prompt": "37092", "answer": "37093"}
{"prompt": "35439,35440,35441,35442,35443,35444,35445", "answer": "35446"}
{"prompt": "11997,11998", "answer": "11999"}
{"prompt": "31279,31280", "answer": "31281"}
{"prompt": "21908,21909,21910,21911,21912,21913", "answer": "21914"}
{"prompt": "25343,25344,25345,25346,25347,25348,25349,25350,25351", "answer": "25352"}
{"prompt": "24531,24532,24533", "answer": "24534"}
{"prompt": "16100", "answer": "16101"}
{"prompt": "21226,21227,21228,21229,21230", "answer": "21231"}
{"prompt": "15514,15515,15516,15517,15518,15519,15520,15521,15522", "answer": "15523"}
{"prompt": "42988,42989,42990,42991,42992,42993,42994", "answer": "42995"}
{"prompt": "23813,23814,23815,23816", "answer": "23817"}
{"prompt": "4321,4322,4323,4324,4325", "answer": "4326"}
{"prompt": "9873,9874,9875,9876", "answer": "9877"}
{"prompt": "28968,28969,28970,28971,28972,28973,28974,28975", "answer": "28976"}
{"prompt": "4325,4326,4327,4328,4329,4330,4331,4332", "answer": "4333"}
{"prompt": "34744,34745,34746,34747,34748", "answer": "34749"}
{"prompt": "32123,32124,32125,32126,32127,32128", "answer": "32129"}
{"prompt": "24198,24199,24200,24201,24202,24203,24204", "answer": "24205"}
{"prompt": "42074,42075,42076,42077,42078,42079,42080", "answer": "42081"}
{"prompt": "7963,7964,7965,7966,7967,7968,7969,7970,7971,7972", "answer": "7973"}
{"prompt": "10981,10982,10983,10984,10985,10986,10987,10988", "answer": "10989"}
{"prompt": "40319,40320,40321,40322,40323,40324,40325", "answer": "40326"}
{"prompt": "41629,41630,41631,41632,41633,41634,41635", "answer": "41636"}
{"prompt": "34120,34121,34122", "answer": "34123"}
{"prompt": "20365,20366,20367,20368", "answer": "20369"}
{"prompt": "22322,22323,22324,22325,22326,22327,22328", "answer": "22329"}
{"prompt": "39647,39648", "answer": "39649"}
{"prompt": "40349,40350", "answer": "40351"}
{"prompt": "42034,42035,42036,42037", "answer": "42038"}
{"prompt": "6872,6873", "answer": "6874"}
{"prompt": "11281,11282,11283,11284,11285,11286,11287", "answer": "11288"}
{"prompt": "44413", "answer": "44414"}
{"prompt": "22127,22128,22129,22130,22131,22132,22133,22134,22135,22136", "answer": "22137"}
{"prompt": "6704,6705", "answer": "6706"}
{"prompt": "34044,34045,34046,34047,34048,34049,34050,34051", "answer": "34052"}
{"prompt": "11682,11683,11684,11685,11686,11687,11688,11689", "answer": "11690"}
{"prompt": "26710,26711,26712,26713,26714", "answer": "26715"}
{"prompt": "41084", "answer": "41085"}
{"prompt": "25020,25021,25022", "answer": "25023"}
{"prompt": "16393,16394,16395,16396,16397,16398,16399,16400,16401,16402", "answer": "16403"}
{"prompt": "23,24,25,26,27,28,29,30,31,32", "answer": "33"}
{"prompt": "13358,13359,13360,13361,13362,13363,13364,13365,13366,13367", "answer": "13368"}
{"prompt": "4056,4057,4058,4059,4060,4061,4062,4063,4064,4065", "answer": "4066"}
{"prompt": "26487,26488,26489", "answer": "26490"}
{"prompt": "36158,36159", "answer": "36160"}
{"prompt": "16415,16416,16417", "answer": "16418"}
{"prompt": "44855,44856,44857,44858,44859,44860,44861", "answer": "44862"}
{"prompt": "29360,29361,29362", "answer": "29363"}
{"prompt": "39271,39272,39273,39274,39275,39276,39277,39278,39279,39280", "answer": "39281"}
{"prompt": "12842,12843,12844,12845,12846,12847,12848,12849", "answer": "12850"}
{"prompt": "26044,26045,26046,26047,26048,26049,26050,26051,26052,26053", "answer": "26054"}
{"prompt": "16921,16922,16923", "answer": "16924"}
{"prompt": "1034,1035,1036", "answer": "1037"}
{"prompt": "8726,8727,8728", "answer": "8729"}
{"prompt": "22245,22246,22247", "answer": "22248"}
{"prompt": "20868,20869,20870,20871,20872,20873", "answer": "20874"}
{"prompt": "595,596,597,598,599", "answer": "600"}
{"prompt": "9331,9332,9333,9334", "answer": "9335"}
{"prompt": "15637,15638,15639,15640,15641,15642,15643", "answer": "15644"}
{"prompt": "5535,5536,5537,5538,5539,5540,5541", "answer": "5542"}
{"prompt": "23449,23450,23451,23452", "answer": "23453"}
{"prompt": "10252,10253,10254,10255,10256,10257,10258,10259,10260", "answer": "10261"}
{"prompt": "44748,44749,44750,44751,44752,44753,44754,44755", "answer": "44756"}
{"prompt": "31504,31505,31506,31507,31508,31509,31510", "answer": "31511"}
{"prompt": "19129,19130,19131,19132", "answer": "19133"}
{"prompt": "31182", "answer": "31183"}
{"prompt": "14318,14319,14320,14321,14322,14323", "answer": "14324"}
{"prompt": "38085,38086,38087,38088,38089,38090,38091,38092", "answer": "38093"}
{"prompt": "19321,19322,19323,19324,19325,19326,19327", "answer": "19328"}
{"prompt": "8824,8825,8826,8827,8828,8829,8830", "answer": "8831"}
{"prompt": "20598,20599,20600,20601,20602,20603,20604,20605,20606", "answer": "20607"}
{"prompt": "37144", "answer": "37145"}
{"prompt": "6539,6540,6541,6542", "answer": "6543"}
{"prompt": "22152,22153,22154,22155,22156,22157,22158,22159", "answer": "22160"}
{"prompt": "5847,5848,5849,5850,5851,5852,5853,5854", "answer": "5855"}
{"prompt": "28754,28755,28756,28757,28758", "answer": "28759"}
{"prompt": "6316,6317,6318,6319,6320,6321", "answer": "6322"}
{"prompt": "25005,25006,25007,25008,25009,25010,25011,25012,25013", "answer": "25014"}
{"prompt": "8672,8673,8674,8675,8676,8677", "answer": "8678"}
{"prompt": "11188,11189,11190,11191,11192,11193,11194,11195,11196", "answer": "11197"}
{"prompt": "29135,29136,29137,29138,29139,29140", "answer": "29141"}
{"prompt": "27793,27794,27795,27796,27797,27798,27799,27800", "answer": "27801"}
{"prompt": "40026,40027,40028,40029,40030,40031,40032,40033,40034", "answer": "40035"}
{"prompt": "1118", "answer": "1119"}
{"prompt": "35029,35030,35031,35032,35033,35034,35035", "answer": "35036"}
{"prompt": "31725,31726,31727,31728,31729,31730,31731", "answer": "31732"}
{"prompt": "36170,36171", "answer": "36172"}
{"prompt": "41517,41518", "answer": "41519"}
{"prompt": "39608,39609,39610,39611,39612,39613,39614", "answer": "39615"}
{"prompt": "30921,30922", "answer": "30923"}
{"prompt": "28391,28392,28393,28394,28395,28396,28397,28398,28399,28400", "answer": "28401"}
{"prompt": "38351,38352,38353,38354", "answer": "38355"}
{"prompt": "13079,13080,13081,13082,13083,13084,13085,13086", "answer": "13087"}
{"prompt": "37974,37975,37976,37977,37978,37979,37980,37981,37982", "answer": "37983"}
{"prompt": "4052", "answer": "4053"}
{"prompt": "25022,25023,25024,25025", "answer": "25026"}
{"prompt": "13382", "answer": "13383"}
{"prompt": "38279,38280", "answer": "38281"}
{"prompt": "9679,9680,9681", "answer": "9682"}
{"prompt": "11736,11737,11738,11739,11740,11741,11742,11743", "answer": "11744"}
{"prompt": "24832,24833,24834,24835,24836", "answer": "24837"}
{"prompt": "20694,20695,20696,20697,20698,20699", "answer": "20700"}
{"prompt": "15021", "answer": "15022"}
{"prompt": "27075,27076,27077,27078,27079,27080,27081", "answer": "27082"}
{"prompt": "36165,36166,36167", "answer": "36168"}
{"prompt": "42671,42672,42673,42674,42675,42676,42677,42678", "answer": "42679"}
{"prompt": "43266,43267", "answer": "43268"}
{"prompt": "27282,27283,27284,27285,27286", "answer": "27287"}
{"prompt": "9942,9943,9944,9945,9946,9947", "answer": "9948"}
{"prompt": "185,186,187,188,189,190,191", "answer": "192"}
{"prompt": "18473,18474,18475,18476,18477", "answer": "18478"}
{"prompt": "4825,4826,4827,4828", "answer": "4829"}
{"prompt": "44138,44139,44140,44141,44142", "answer": "44143"}
{"prompt": "43280,43281,43282,43283", "answer": "43284"}
{"prompt": "29654,29655,29656,29657,29658,29659,29660,29661,29662,29663", "answer": "29664"}
{"prompt": "43991,43992,43993,43994,43995,43996,43997", "answer": "43998"}
{"prompt": "34037", "answer": "34038"}
{"prompt": "26071,26072,26073,26074", "answer": "26075"}
{"prompt": "34470,34471,34472", "answer": "34473"}
{"prompt": "36278,36279", "answer": "36280"}
{"prompt": "12867,12868,12869,12870", "answer": "12871"}
{"prompt": "43619,43620", "answer": "43621"}
{"prompt": "33957,33958,33959,33960,33961,33962,33963,33964,33965,33966", "answer": "33967"}
{"prompt": "35720,35721,35722,35723,35724,35725,35726,35727,35728,35729", "answer": "35730"}
{"prompt": "43986,43987", "answer": "43988"}
{"prompt": "15178,15179", "answer": "15180"}
{"prompt": "35445,35446,35447,35448,35449,35450", "answer": "35451"}
{"prompt": "39782,39783,39784,39785,39786,39787,39788,39789,39790", "answer": "39791"}
{"prompt": "26522,26523,26524,26525,26526,26527,26528,26529,26530,26531", "answer": "26532"}
{"prompt": "10902,10903,10904,10905,10906,10907", "answer": "10908"}
{"prompt": "12915,12916,12917,12918,12919,12920,12921,12922", "answer": "12923"}
{"prompt": "17603,17604", "answer": "17605"}
{"prompt": "43277,43278,43279,43280", "answer": "43281"}
{"prompt": "32615,32616,32617", "answer": "32618"}
{"prompt": "8465,8466", "answer": "8467"}
{"prompt": "43058,43059,43060,43061", "answer": "43062"}
{"prompt": "8797,8798,8799,8800,8801,8802,8803", "answer": "8804"}
{"prompt": "12670,12671,12672,12673,12674,12675,12676", "answer": "12677"}
{"prompt": "38034,38035,38036,38037,38038,38039,38040,38041,38042", "answer": "38043"}
{"prompt": "43386,43387,43388,43389,43390,43391,43392,43393", "answer": "43394"}
{"prompt": "6223,6224,6225,6226,6227,6228,6229,6230,6231", "answer": "6232"}
{"prompt": "15362,15363", "answer": "15364"}
{"prompt": "609,610,611,612,613,614,615,616,617", "answer": "618"}
{"prompt": "4610,4611,4612,4613,4614,4615", "answer": "4616"}
{"prompt": "3817,3818,3819,3820", "answer": "3821"}
{"prompt": "28122,28123,28124,28125,28126,28127,28128,28129,28130,28131", "answer": "28132"}
{"prompt": "22935", "answer": "22936"}
{"prompt": "33689,33690,33691,33692,33693", "answer": "33694"}
{"prompt": "32523,32524,32525,32526,32527,32528,32529,32530,32531", "answer": "32532"}
{"prompt": "18440,18441,18442", "answer": "18443"}
{"prompt": "38837,38838,38839,38840,38841,38842", "answer": "38843"}
{"prompt": "44582,44583,44584,44585,44586", "answer": "44587"}
{"prompt": "41891,41892,41893,41894", "answer": "41895"}
{"prompt": "3280,3281,3282,3283,3284,3285,3286,3287,3288", "answer": "3289"}
{"prompt": "33270,33271,33272", "answer": "33273"}
{"prompt": "17162,17163,17164,17165,17166", "answer": "17167"}
{"prompt": "7998,7999,8000,8001,8002,8003,8004,8005,8006", "answer": "8007"}
{"prompt": "39918,39919,39920,39921,39922", "answer": "39923"}
{"prompt": "15605,15606,15607,15608", "answer": "15609"}
{"prompt": "31071", "answer": "31072"}
{"prompt": "21100,21101,21102,21103,21104,21105,21106", "answer": "21107"}
{"prompt": "31616,31617", "answer": "31618"}
{"prompt": "29302,29303,29304,29305,29306,29307,29308,29309", "answer": "29310"}
{"prompt": "42780,42781,42782,42783", "answer": "42784"}
{"prompt": "13401,13402", "answer": "13403"}
{"prompt": "3225", "answer": "3226"}
{"prompt": "15722,15723,15724,15725,15726,15727,15728,15729,15730", "answer": "15731"}
{"prompt": "13375,13376,13377", "answer": "13378"}
{"prompt": "8877,8878,8879,8880,8881,8882,8883,8884,8885", "answer": "8886"}
{"prompt": "5,6,7,8", "answer": "9"}
{"prompt": "37153,37154,37155", "answer": "37156"}
{"prompt": "23809,23810,23811,23812,23813", "answer": "23814"}
{"prompt": "10518,10519,10520,10521", "answer": "10522"}
{"prompt": "23565,23566", "answer": "23567"}
{"prompt": "42524", "answer": "42525"}
{"prompt": "17998,17999,18000,18001,18002,18003,18004,18005,18006,18007", "answer": "18008"}
{"prompt": "38693,38694", "answer": "38695"}
{"prompt": "16863,16864,16865,16866,16867,16868,16869", "answer": "16870"}
{"prompt": "35521,35522,35523,35524,35525,35526,35527,35528,35529", "answer": "35530"}
{"prompt": "35634,35635,35636,35637,35638,35639,35640,35641,35642,35643", "answer": "35644"}
{"prompt": "45251,45252,45253,45254,45255,45256,45257,45258,45259,45260", "answer": "45261"}
{"prompt": "39939,39940,39941,39942,39943,39944,39945,39946,39947", "answer": "39948"}
{"prompt": "34385,34386,34387,34388,34389,34390,34391,34392", "answer": "34393"}
{"prompt": "20461,20462,20463,20464,20465,20466,20467", "answer": "20468"}
{"prompt": "19776,19777,19778,19779,19780,19781,19782,19783,19784", "answer": "19785"}
{"prompt": "488", "answer": "489"}
{"prompt": "43730,43731", "answer": "43732"}
{"prompt": "5180,5181,5182", "answer": "5183"}
{"prompt": "467,468,469,470", "answer": "471"}
{"prompt": "44632,44633,44634,44635,44636,44637,44638", "answer": "44639"}
{"prompt": "27464,27465", "answer": "27466"}
{"prompt": "14879,14880,14881,14882", "answer": "14883"}
{"prompt": "24799,24800,24801,24802,24803,24804,24805,24806,24807", "answer": "24808"}
{"prompt": "26179,26180", "answer": "26181"}
{"prompt": "19095,19096,19097,19098,19099,19100,19101,19102", "answer": "19103"}
{"prompt": "22771,22772,22773,22774,22775,22776,22777,22778,22779,22780", "answer": "22781"}
{"prompt": "23638,23639,23640,23641,23642,23643,23644,23645", "answer": "23646"}
{"prompt": "4844,4845,4846", "answer": "4847"}
{"prompt": "38138,38139", "answer": "38140"}
{"prompt": "20573,20574,20575,20576,20577,20578,20579,20580,20581", "answer": "20582"}
{"prompt": "27038,27039,27040,27041,27042,27043,27044", "answer": "27045"}
{"prompt": "41389,41390,41391,41392,41393", "answer": "41394"}
{"prompt": "22101,22102,22103,22104,22105,22106,22107,22108,22109", "answer": "22110"}
{"prompt": "33534,33535,33536,33537,33538,33539,33540,33541", "answer": "33542"}
{"prompt": "31453,31454,31455,31456,31457,31458,31459", "answer": "31460"}
{"prompt": "23410,23411,23412,23413", "answer": "23414"}
{"prompt": "37411,37412", "answer": "37413"}
{"prompt": "31701", "answer": "31702"}
{"prompt": "8512,8513,8514,8515,8516,8517", "answer": "8518"}
{"prompt": "7889,7890,7891,7892,7893,7894,7895,7896,7897,7898", "answer": "7899"}
{"prompt": "41520,41521,41522,41523,41524,41525,41526,41527", "answer": "41528"}
{"prompt": "3892,3893,3894,3895,3896,3897,3898,3899,3900,3901", "answer": "3902"}
{"prompt": "26714,26715,26716,26717,26718,26719", "answer": "26720"}
{"prompt": "38546,38547,38548,38549,38550,38551,38552,38553,38554,38555", "answer": "38556"}
{"prompt": "35343,35344,35345,35346,35347,35348,35349,35350,35351,35352", "answer": "35353"}
{"prompt": "42665,42666,42667,42668,42669,42670,42671", "answer": "42672"}
{"prompt": "16141", "answer": "16142"}
{"prompt": "18791,18792", "answer": "18793"}
{"prompt": "2202,2203,2204,2205,2206,2207,2208,2209,2210,2211", "answer": "2212"}
{"prompt": "22419,22420,22421", "answer": "22422"}
{"prompt": "28876,28877,28878", "answer": "28879"}
{"prompt": "21554,21555,21556,21557,21558", "answer": "21559"}
{"prompt": "20666,20667,20668,20669,20670", "answer": "20671"}
{"prompt": "20792,20793,20794,20795,20796", "answer": "20797"}
{"prompt": "9955,9956,9957,9958,9959,9960,9961", "answer": "9962"}
{"prompt": "37926,37927,37928,37929", "answer": "37930"}
{"prompt": "21358,21359,21360,21361,21362,21363,21364,21365,21366,21367", "answer": "21368"}
{"prompt": "32531,32532,32533,32534,32535,32536,32537", "answer": "32538"}
{"prompt": "19915,19916,19917,19918,19919,19920,19921,19922", "answer": "19923"}
{"prompt": "2055,2056,2057,2058", "answer": "2059"}
{"prompt": "17270,17271,17272", "answer": "17273"}
{"prompt": "37096,37097,37098,37099,37100,37101,37102,37103,37104", "answer": "37105"}
{"prompt": "19307,19308,19309,19310,19311,19312", "answer": "19313"}
{"prompt": "43580,43581,43582,43583,43584,43585,43586,43587,43588,43589", "answer": "43590"}
{"prompt": "39169", "answer": "39170"}
{"prompt": "35352,35353,35354,35355,35356,35357,35358", "answer": "35359"}
{"prompt": "5430,5431,5432,5433,5434", "answer": "5435"}
{"prompt": "43273,43274,43275,43276,43277", "answer": "43278"}
{"prompt": "7333,7334,7335,7336,7337,7338,7339,7340,7341", "answer": "7342"}
{"prompt": "44384,44385,44386", "answer": "44387"}
{"prompt": "40517,40518,40519,40520,40521,40522,40523,40524,40525", "answer": "40526"}
{"prompt": "33317,33318,33319,33320,33321,33322,33323,33324,33325", "answer": "33326"}
{"prompt": "36455", "answer": "36456"}
{"prompt": "9457,9458", "answer": "9459"}
{"prompt": "25749,25750,25751,25752,25753", "answer": "25754"}
{"prompt": "19982", "answer": "19983"}
{"prompt": "44443,44444,44445,44446", "answer": "44447"}
{"prompt": "41505,41506", "answer": "41507"}
{"prompt": "32186,32187,32188,32189,32190,32191,32192", "answer": "32193"}
{"prompt": "19267", "answer": "19268"}
{"prompt": "39901,39902,39903", "answer": "39904"}
{"prompt": "33226,33227,33228", "answer": "33229"}
{"prompt": "28111,28112,28113", "answer": "28114"}
{"prompt": "42258,42259,42260", "answer": "42261"}
{"prompt": "4281,4282,4283,4284,4285,4286,4287,4288,4289,4290", "answer": "4291"}
{"prompt": "44047,44048,44049,44050,44051,44052,44053", "answer": "44054"}
{"prompt": "39774,39775,39776,39777,39778,39779,39780,39781,39782", "answer": "39783"}
{"prompt": "24226,24227,24228", "answer": "24229"}
{"prompt": "12790,12791,12792,12793,12794,12795,12796,12797", "answer": "12798"}
{"prompt": "31434", "answer": "31435"}
{"prompt": "20606,20607,20608,20609,20610", "answer": "20611"}
{"prompt": "2782,2783,2784", "answer": "2785"}
{"prompt": "2053,2054,2055", "answer": "2056"}
{"prompt": "8157,8158,8159,8160,8161", "answer": "8162"}
{"prompt": "23165", "answer": "23166"}
{"prompt": "10264,10265,10266,10267,10268,10269,10270,10271,10272", "answer": "10273"}
{"prompt": "793,794,795,796,797", "answer": "798"}
{"prompt": "31770,31771,31772,31773,31774,31775,31776,31777,31778,31779", "answer": "31780"}
{"prompt": "13926,13927,13928,13929", "answer": "13930"}
{"prompt": "30540,30541,30542,30543,30544", "answer": "30545"}
{"prompt": "28741,28742,28743,28744,28745,28746", "answer": "28747"}
{"prompt": "16214,16215,16216", "answer": "16217"}
{"prompt": "17313", "answer": "17314"}
{"prompt": "39899", "answer": "39900"}
{"prompt": "21715,21716,21717,21718,21719,21720,21721,21722,21723", "answer": "21724"}
{"prompt": "16106,16107,16108,16109,16110,16111,16112", "answer": "16113"}
{"prompt": "10126,10127,10128,10129,10130", "answer": "10131"}
{"prompt": "41072,41073,41074,41075,41076,41077,41078,41079,41080,41081", "answer": "41082"}
{"prompt": "29016,29017", "answer": "29018"}
{"prompt": "25313,25314,25315,25316,25317", "answer": "25318"}
{"prompt": "8006,8007,8008,8009,8010,8011", "answer": "8012"}
{"prompt": "10536,10537,10538,10539,10540", "answer": "10541"}
{"prompt": "33465,33466,33467,33468", "answer": "33469"}
{"prompt": "16008,16009,16010,16011,16012,16013,16014", "answer": "16015"}
{"prompt": "41007,41008,41009,41010,41011,41012,41013,41014", "answer": "41015"}
{"prompt": "43460,43461", "answer": "43462"}
{"prompt": "36229,36230,36231,36232,36233,36234,36235,36236,36237,36238", "answer": "36239"}
{"prompt": "14519,14520,14521,14522,14523,14524,14525,14526", "answer": "14527"}
{"prompt": "11823", "answer": "11824"}
{"prompt": "3348", "answer": "3349"}
{"prompt": "36500,36501,36502,36503,36504", "answer": "36505"}
{"prompt": "34863,34864,34865,34866", "answer": "34867"}
{"prompt": "28681,28682,28683,28684,28685,28686,28687", "answer": "28688"}
{"prompt": "15492,15493", "answer": "15494"}
{"prompt": "41246", "answer": "41247"}
{"prompt": "33307,33308,33309,33310,33311,33312,33313,33314,33315", "answer": "33316"}
{"prompt": "16633,16634,16635,16636,16637,16638", "answer": "16639"}
{"prompt": "15372,15373", "answer": "15374"}
{"prompt": "34294,34295,34296", "answer": "34297"}
{"prompt": "42096,42097", "answer": "42098"}
{"prompt": "43114,43115,43116", "answer": "43117"}
{"prompt": "9964,9965,9966,9967,9968,9969,9970", "answer": "9971"}
{"prompt": "44330,44331,44332,44333,44334,44335", "answer": "44336"}
{"prompt": "42849,42850,42851,42852,42853", "answer": "42854"}
{"prompt": "18284,18285,18286,18287", "answer": "18288"}
{"prompt": "8065", "answer": "8066"}
{"prompt": "694,695,696,697,698", "answer": "699"}
{"prompt": "5808,5809,5810,5811,5812,5813,5814,5815,5816", "answer": "5817"}
{"prompt": "21791,21792,21793,21794,21795,21796", "answer": "21797"}
{"prompt": "25230,25231,25232,25233,25234,25235,25236,25237,25238,25239", "answer": "25240"}
{"prompt": "1716,1717,1718,1719,1720,1721,1722,1723,1724,1725", "answer": "1726"}
{"prompt": "4132,4133,4134,4135,4136,4137,4138,4139", "answer": "4140"}
{"prompt": "10076,10077,10078,10079,10080,10081", "answer": "10082"}
{"prompt": "25685,25686,25687,25688", "answer": "25689"}
{"prompt": "21510,21511,21512,21513,21514,21515,21516,21517,21518,21519", "answer": "21520"}
{"prompt": "3931", "answer": "3932"}
{"prompt": "6418,6419", "answer": "6420"}
{"prompt": "22645,22646,22647,22648,22649,22650,22651,22652,22653", "answer": "22654"}
{"prompt": "9885,9886,9887,9888,9889,9890,9891,9892", "answer": "9893"}
{"prompt": "37104,37105,37106,37107,37108,37109,37110,37111,37112,37113", "answer": "37114"}
{"prompt": "9855,9856,9857,9858,9859,9860,9861,9862,9863,9864", "answer": "9865"}
{"prompt": "38539,38540,38541,38542,38543,38544,38545,38546", "answer": "38547"}
{"prompt": "6074,6075,6076,6077,6078,6079", "answer": "6080"}
{"prompt": "32436,32437,32438,32439,32440,32441,32442,32443,32444,32445", "answer": "32446"}
{"prompt": "31936,31937", "answer": "31938"}
{"prompt": "21057,21058,21059,21060", "answer": "21061"}
{"prompt": "40127,40128,40129", "answer": "40130"}
{"prompt": "15031", "answer": "15032"}
{"prompt": "45034,45035,45036", "answer": "45037"}
{"prompt": "28320", "answer": "28321"}
{"prompt": "8474,8475,8476,8477,8478,8479", "answer": "8480"}
{"prompt": "11230", "answer": "11231"}
{"prompt": "28481,28482,28483,28484", "answer": "28485"}
{"prompt": "20109,20110,20111,20112,20113,20114,20115,20116,20117,20118", "answer": "20119"}
{"prompt": "32407,32408,32409,32410", "answer": "32411"}
{"prompt": "8109,8110,8111", "answer": "8112"}
{"prompt": "25740,25741,25742,25743,25744,25745,25746,25747,25748", "answer": "25749"}
{"prompt": "2578,2579,2580,2581,2582,2583,2584", "answer": "2585"}
{"prompt": "19420,19421,19422,19423,19424,19425", "answer": "19426"}
{"prompt": "35956,35957,35958,35959", "answer": "35960"}
{"prompt": "21308,21309,21310,21311,21312,21313", "answer": "21314"}
{"prompt": "30718,30719,30720,30721,30722,30723,30724,30725,30726", "answer": "30727"}
{"prompt": "4710,4711", "answer": "4712"}
{"prompt": "9582,9583,9584", "answer": "9585"}
{"prompt": "3635,3636", "answer": "3637"}
{"prompt": "3175,3176,3177,3178,3179", "answer": "3180"}
{"prompt": "17804,17805,17806,17807,17808,17809,17810,17811,17812,17813", "answer": "17814"}
{"prompt": "27819,27820", "answer": "27821"}
{"prompt": "28346,28347,28348,28349,28350,28351,28352,28353,28354,28355", "answer": "28356"}
{"prompt": "38042", "answer": "38043"}
{"prompt": "34638,34639,34640,34641,34642,34643,34644,34645,34646", "answer": "34647"}
{"prompt": "20280,20281,20282,20283,20284,20285", "answer": "20286"}
{"prompt": "1753,1754,1755,1756", "answer": "1757"}
{"prompt": "17395,17396,17397,17398,17399,17400,17401,17402,17403", "answer": "17404"}
{"prompt": "16093,16094,16095,16096,16097,16098,16099,16100", "answer": "16101"}
{"prompt": "8255,8256,8257,8258,8259,8260,8261", "answer": "8262"}
{"prompt": "26110,26111,26112,26113,26114,26115,26116,26117,26118,26119", "answer": "26120"}
{"prompt": "44709,44710,44711,44712,44713,44714,44715,44716,44717,44718", "answer": "44719"}
{"prompt": "41426,41427,41428,41429", "answer": "41430"}
{"prompt": "26131", "answer": "26132"}
{"prompt": "20449,20450,20451,20452,20453,20454,20455,20456,20457", "answer": "20458"}
{"prompt": "4034,4035,4036,4037,4038,4039", "answer": "4040"}
{"prompt": "43118,43119,43120,43121,43122,43123", "answer": "43124"}
{"prompt": "38240,38241,38242,38243", "answer": "38244"}
{"prompt": "17572,17573,17574", "answer": "17575"}
{"prompt": "38874", "answer": "38875"}
{"prompt": "5144,5145,5146,5147", "answer": "5148"}
{"prompt": "40225,40226,40227,40228,40229,40230,40231,40232,40233", "answer": "40234"}
{"prompt": "10690,10691,10692,10693,10694,10695,10696,10697", "answer": "10698"}
{"prompt": "40848,40849,40850,40851", "answer": "40852"}
{"prompt": "18241,18242,18243,18244,18245", "answer": "18246"}
{"prompt": "7801,7802,7803", "answer": "7804"}
{"prompt": "7440,7441,7442,7443,7444,7445,7446,7447,7448", "answer": "7449"}
{"prompt": "43944", "answer": "43945"}
{"prompt": "15234,15235,15236,15237,15238,15239,15240,15241,15242", "answer": "15243"}
{"prompt": "11804,11805,11806,11807", "answer": "11808"}
{"prompt": "25324,25325,25326,25327,25328,25329,25330,25331", "answer": "25332"}
{"prompt": "26130,26131", "answer": "26132"}
{"prompt": "16003,16004,16005", "answer": "16006"}
{"prompt": "44861,44862,44863,44864,44865,44866", "answer": "44867"}
{"prompt": "26656,26657,26658,26659,26660,26661,26662,26663", "answer": "26664"}
{"prompt": "18640,18641,18642,18643,18644,18645,18646,18647", "answer": "18648"}
{"prompt": "45204,45205,45206,45207,45208,45209,45210", "answer": "45211"}
{"prompt": "8978,8979,8980,8981,8982", "answer": "8983"}
{"prompt": "9156,9157,9158", "answer": "9159"}
{"prompt": "6750,6751,6752,6753,6754,6755,6756", "answer": "6757"}
{"prompt": "43956,43957,43958,43959,43960,43961", "answer": "43962"}
{"prompt": "8952,8953,8954,8955,8956", "answer": "8957"}
{"prompt": "2340,2341,2342,2343,2344,2345,2346,2347", "answer": "2348"}
{"prompt": "33942,33943", "answer": "33944"}
{"prompt": "34717,34718", "answer": "34719"}
{"prompt": "43318,43319,43320,43321,43322,43323", "answer": "43324"}
{"prompt": "34192,34193,34194,34195,34196,34197", "answer": "34198"}
{"prompt": "24882,24883,24884,24885,24886,24887,24888,24889,24890,24891", "answer": "24892"}
{"prompt": "34472,34473,34474,34475,34476", "answer": "34477"}
{"prompt": "8912,8913", "answer": "8914"}
{"prompt": "26591,26592", "answer": "26593"}
{"prompt": "20910,20911,20912,20913,20914,20915", "answer": "20916"}
{"prompt": "14178,14179,14180,14181,14182,14183", "answer": "14184"}
{"prompt": "34384,34385", "answer": "34386"}
{"prompt": "29487,29488,29489,29490,29491,29492", "answer": "29493"}
{"prompt": "39480,39481,39482,39483,39484,39485", "answer": "39486"}
{"prompt": "41450,41451,41452,41453,41454,41455,41456,41457,41458", "answer": "41459"}
{"prompt": "21989,21990,21991,21992,21993,21994,21995", "answer": "21996"}
{"prompt": "1776,1777,1778,1779", "answer": "1780"}
{"prompt": "20185,20186,20187,20188,20189,20190,20191", "answer": "20192"}
{"prompt": "8522,8523,8524,8525,8526,8527,8528,8529", "answer": "8530"}
{"prompt": "42475,42476,42477,42478,42479,42480,42481,42482", "answer": "42483"}
{"prompt": "19550,19551,19552,19553,19554,19555", "answer": "19556"}
{"prompt": "9844,9845,9846,9847,9848,9849,9850,9851", "answer": "9852"}
{"prompt": "2495,2496,2497,2498,2499", "answer": "2500"}
{"prompt": "15927,15928,15929,15930,15931,15932", "answer": "15933"}
{"prompt": "41921,41922,41923,41924", "answer": "41925"}
{"prompt": "6236,6237", "answer": "6238"}
{"prompt": "31795", "answer": "31796"}
{"prompt": "36400", "answer": "36401"}
{"prompt": "25938,25939,25940,25941,25942,25943", "answer": "25944"}
{"prompt": "26291,26292,26293,26294", "answer": "26295"}
{"prompt": "19105,19106,19107,19108,19109,19110,19111,19112,19113,19114", "answer": "19115"}
{"prompt": "39280,39281,39282,39283,39284,39285,39286,39287", "answer": "39288"}
{"prompt": "43631,43632,43633,43634,43635", "answer": "43636"}
{"prompt": "23128,23129,23130,23131,23132,23133", "answer": "23134"}
{"prompt": "31494", "answer": "31495"}
{"prompt": "19053,19054,19055,19056,19057,19058,19059,19060,19061,19062", "answer": "19063"}
{"prompt": "21983,21984,21985,21986,21987,21988,21989", "answer": "21990"}
{"prompt": "2283,2284,2285,2286,2287,2288,2289,2290", "answer": "2291"}
{"prompt": "43758,43759,43760,43761,43762,43763,43764", "answer": "43765"}
{"prompt": "18036,18037,18038,18039,18040,18041,18042", "answer": "18043"}
{"prompt": "39138,39139,39140,39141,39142,39143,39144", "answer": "39145"}
{"prompt": "16429,16430,16431,16432,16433,16434", "answer": "16435"}
{"prompt": "44503,44504,44505", "answer": "44506"}
{"prompt": "9377,9378,9379,9380,9381,9382,9383", "answer": "9384"}
{"prompt": "27999,28000,28001,28002,28003,28004,28005,28006,28007,28008", "answer": "28009"}
{"prompt": "17423,17424", "answer": "17425"}
{"prompt": "42733,42734,42735,42736", "answer": "42737"}
{"prompt": "23613,23614,23615,23616,23617,23618", "answer": "23619"}
{"prompt": "14706,14707,14708,14709,14710,14711,14712", "answer": "14713"}
{"prompt": "32630,32631,32632,32633,32634,32635,32636", "answer": "32637"}
{"prompt": "33602,33603,33604,33605,33606,33607,33608", "answer": "33609"}
{"prompt": "22220,22221,22222,22223,22224,22225,22226,22227,22228", "answer": "22229"}
{"prompt": "22339,22340,22341,22342,22343,22344,22345,22346,22347,22348", "answer": "22349"}
{"prompt": "33992,33993,33994,33995,33996,33997,33998,33999", "answer": "34000"}
{"prompt": "35262,35263,35264,35265,35266,35267,35268,35269", "answer": "35270"}
{"prompt": "30812,30813,30814,30815,30816,30817,30818", "answer": "30819"}
{"prompt": "12223,12224,12225,12226,12227,12228,12229", "answer": "12230"}
{"prompt": "28989,28990", "answer": "28991"}
{"prompt": "29684,29685,29686,29687,29688,29689,29690,29691,29692", "answer": "29693"}
{"prompt": "4074,4075,4076,4077,4078", "answer": "4079"}
{"prompt": "4265,4266,4267,4268", "answer": "4269"}
{"prompt": "7939,7940,7941,7942,7943,7944,7945,7946,7947,7948", "answer": "7949"}
{"prompt": "35372,35373,35374,35375,35376", "answer": "35377"}
{"prompt": "30818,30819,30820,30821,30822,30823,30824,30825,30826,30827", "answer": "30828"}
{"prompt": "37161,37162,37163,37164,37165,37166,37167,37168,37169", "answer": "37170"}
{"prompt": "31499", "answer": "31500"}
{"prompt": "14784,14785,14786,14787", "answer": "14788"}
{"prompt": "22621,22622,22623,22624,22625,22626,22627,22628", "answer": "22629"}
{"prompt": "42040,42041,42042,42043,42044,42045,42046,42047", "answer": "42048"}
{"prompt": "30090,30091,30092,30093,30094,30095,30096,30097,30098,30099", "answer": "30100"}
{"prompt": "33999,34000", "answer": "34001"}
{"prompt": "5662,5663,5664,5665,5666,5667,5668,5669,5670,5671", "answer": "5672"}
{"prompt": "4319,4320,4321", "answer": "4322"}
{"prompt": "16931", "answer": "16932"}
{"prompt": "12774,12775,12776", "answer": "12777"}
{"prompt": "33074,33075,33076,33077,33078,33079,33080,33081,33082,33083", "answer": "33084"}
{"prompt": "2835,2836,2837,2838,2839", "answer": "2840"}
{"prompt": "31071,31072,31073,31074,31075,31076,31077", "answer": "31078"}
{"prompt": "10068,10069,10070,10071,10072,10073,10074,10075,10076", "answer": "10077"}
{"prompt": "13951,13952,13953,13954,13955,13956,13957,13958", "answer": "13959"}
{"prompt": "37798,37799,37800,37801,37802,37803,37804", "answer": "37805"}
{"prompt": "23546,23547,23548,23549", "answer": "23550"}
{"prompt": "32179,32180,32181,32182,32183,32184,32185,32186", "answer": "32187"}
{"prompt": "16597,16598,16599,16600,16601,16602", "answer": "16603"}
{"prompt": "32693,32694,32695,32696,32697,32698,32699,32700,32701,32702", "answer": "32703"}
{"prompt": "28496,28497,28498,28499,28500,28501,28502,28503,28504,28505", "answer": "28506"}
{"prompt": "14169,14170,14171,14172,14173,14174,14175,14176,14177,14178", "answer": "14179"}
{"prompt": "11849,11850,11851,11852,11853,11854,11855,11856,11857,11858", "answer": "11859"}
{"prompt": "1258,1259,1260,1261", "answer": "1262"}
{"prompt": "33093,33094,33095,33096,33097,33098,33099,33100", "answer": "33101"}
{"prompt": "8011,8012", "answer": "8013"}
{"prompt": "30844,30845", "answer": "30846"}
{"prompt": "31698,31699,31700,31701", "answer": "31702"}
{"prompt": "6633,6634,6635,6636,6637,6638", "answer": "6639"}
{"prompt": "17481,17482,17483,17484,17485,17486,17487", "answer": "17488"}
{"prompt": "11050,11051", "answer": "11052"}
{"prompt": "35035,35036,35037,35038,35039,35040,35041,35042,35043,35044", "answer": "35045"}
{"prompt": "16222,16223,16224,16225", "answer": "16226"}
{"prompt": "40072,40073,40074,40075,40076,40077,40078,40079,40080,40081", "answer": "40082"}
{"prompt": "38744,38745,38746,38747", "answer": "38748"}
{"prompt": "26040,26041,26042,26043,26044", "answer": "26045"}
{"prompt": "30894,30895,30896,30897,30898,30899", "answer": "30900"}
{"prompt": "11701,11702,11703,11704", "answer": "11705"}
{"prompt": "36465,36466,36467,36468,36469", "answer": "36470"}
{"prompt": "28485,28486,28487,28488,28489,28490,28491,28492", "answer": "28493"}
{"prompt": "10560,10561,10562,10563", "answer": "10564"}
{"prompt": "21060,21061,21062,21063,21064", "answer": "21065"}
{"prompt": "21642,21643,21644,21645", "answer": "21646"}
{"prompt": "5405,5406,5407,5408,5409,5410", "answer": "5411"}
{"prompt": "34785,34786", "answer": "34787"}
{"prompt": "8295,8296,8297,8298,8299", "answer": "8300"}
{"prompt": "24701", "answer": "24702"}
{"prompt": "27900", "answer": "27901"}
{"prompt": "3296,3297,3298,3299", "answer": "3300"}
{"prompt": "38373,38374,38375,38376,38377,38378", "answer": "38379"}
{"prompt": "26143,26144,26145", "answer": "26146"}
{"prompt": "41946,41947,41948,41949,41950,41951,41952,41953", "answer": "41954"}
{"prompt": "25181,25182,25183,25184", "answer": "25185"}
{"prompt": "3616,3617,3618,3619,3620,3621", "answer": "3622"}
{"prompt": "34485,34486,34487,34488,34489,34490", "answer": "34491"}
{"prompt": "32192,32193,32194", "answer": "32195"}
{"prompt": "27474,27475,27476,27477,27478,27479,27480,27481,27482,27483", "answer": "27484"}
{"prompt": "21352,21353,21354,21355", "answer": "21356"}
{"prompt": "39407,39408,39409,39410", "answer": "39411"}
{"prompt": "3591,3592,3593,3594,3595", "answer": "3596"}
{"prompt": "30033,30034,30035,30036,30037", "answer": "30038"}
{"prompt": "38153", "answer": "38154"}
{"prompt": "7274,7275,7276,7277,7278,7279,7280,7281,7282,7283", "answer": "7284"}
{"prompt": "31577,31578,31579,31580", "answer": "31581"}
{"prompt": "31446,31447,31448,31449,31450,31451,31452,31453", "answer": "31454"}
{"prompt": "6564,6565,6566,6567", "answer": "6568"}
{"prompt": "34565,34566,34567,34568,34569,34570,34571,34572,34573", "answer": "34574"}
{"prompt": "34574,34575,34576,34577", "answer": "34578"}
{"prompt": "43376,43377,43378,43379,43380", "answer": "43381"}
{"prompt": "41351,41352,41353,41354,41355,41356", "answer": "41357"}
{"prompt": "31888,31889,31890,31891,31892,31893,31894,31895,31896,31897", "answer": "31898"}
{"prompt": "31662,31663,31664,31665,31666,31667,31668", "answer": "31669"}
{"prompt": "31494,31495,31496,31497,31498,31499", "answer": "31500"}
{"prompt": "31902,31903,31904,31905,31906,31907", "answer": "31908"}
{"prompt": "28579,28580", "answer": "28581"}
{"prompt": "19631", "answer": "19632"}
{"prompt": "10792,10793,10794,10795,10796,10797,10798,10799", "answer": "10800"}
{"prompt": "123,124,125,126,127", "answer": "128"}
{"prompt": "7362,7363", "answer": "7364"}
{"prompt": "12144,12145,12146,12147", "answer": "12148"}
{"prompt": "20782,20783,20784,20785,20786,20787", "answer": "20788"}
{"prompt": "90,91,92,93,94,95,96,97", "answer": "98"}
{"prompt": "21450,21451,21452,21453", "answer": "21454"}
{"prompt": "33450", "answer": "33451"}
{"prompt": "39676,39677,39678,39679,39680,39681,39682,39683,39684", "answer": "39685"}
{"prompt": "25117,25118", "answer": "25119"}
{"prompt": "24368,24369,24370,24371", "answer": "24372"}
{"prompt": "38", "answer": "39"}
{"prompt": "11571,11572,11573,11574", "answer": "11575"}
{"prompt": "31348,31349,31350,31351,31352,31353,31354,31355,31356", "answer": "31357"}
{"prompt": "27670,27671,27672,27673,27674,27675,27676", "answer": "27677"}
{"prompt": "1509,1510", "answer": "1511"}
{"prompt": "3888,3889,3890,3891,3892", "answer": "3893"}
{"prompt": "44823,44824,44825,44826,44827,44828,44829,44830,44831", "answer": "44832"}
{"prompt": "34080,34081,34082,34083,34084", "answer": "34085"}
{"prompt": "42017,42018,42019,42020,42021,42022,42023,42024", "answer": "42025"}
{"prompt": "43723", "answer": "43724"}
{"prompt": "24043", "answer": "24044"}
{"prompt": "36387,36388,36389,36390,36391", "answer": "36392"}
{"prompt": "21019", "answer": "21020"}
{"prompt": "36756,36757,36758,36759,36760,36761,36762,36763,36764,36765", "answer": "36766"}
{"prompt": "17190,17191", "answer": "17192"}
{"prompt": "24397", "answer": "24398"}
{"prompt": "43673,43674,43675,43676,43677,43678", "answer": "43679"}
{"prompt": "11632", "answer": "11633"}
{"prompt": "294,295,296", "answer": "297"}
{"prompt": "26551,26552,26553,26554,26555,26556,26557,26558,26559", "answer": "26560"}
{"prompt": "15333,15334,15335,15336,15337,15338,15339,15340", "answer": "15341"}
{"prompt": "4726", "answer": "4727"}
{"prompt": "25930,25931,25932,25933,25934,25935,25936,25937,25938", "answer": "25939"}
{"prompt": "25828,25829,25830,25831,25832,25833,25834", "answer": "25835"}
{"prompt": "43354,43355,43356,43357,43358,43359,43360,43361", "answer": "43362"}
{"prompt": "1234,1235,1236", "answer": "1237"}
{"prompt": "38997,38998,38999,39000", "answer": "39001"}
{"prompt": "34084,34085,34086,34087,34088", "answer": "34089"}
{"prompt": "23253,23254,23255,23256,23257,23258,23259", "answer": "23260"}
{"prompt": "10276,10277,10278", "answer": "10279"}
{"prompt": "35895,35896,35897,35898,35899,35900,35901,35902", "answer": "35903"}
{"prompt": "8503,8504,8505", "answer": "8506"}
{"prompt": "7953,7954,7955,7956,7957", "answer": "7958"}
{"prompt": "37804,37805", "answer": "37806"}
{"prompt": "2311,2312,2313", "answer": "2314"}
{"prompt": "43810,43811,43812,43813,43814,43815,43816,43817", "answer": "43818"}
{"prompt": "3075,3076", "answer": "3077"}
{"prompt": "21857,21858,21859", "answer": "21860"}
{"prompt": "27620,27621,27622,27623,27624,27625,27626,27627,27628", "answer": "27629"}
{"prompt": "651,652,653,654,655,656,657,658,659", "answer": "660"}
{"prompt": "23179,23180,23181,23182,23183,23184,23185,23186,23187", "answer": "23188"}
{"prompt": "8485,8486,8487,8488,8489,8490,8491,8492,8493,8494", "answer": "8495"}
{"prompt": "37025,37026,37027,37028,37029,37030,37031", "answer": "37032"}
{"prompt": "6527,6528,6529,6530,6531,6532,6533,6534,6535", "answer": "6536"}
{"prompt": "31077,31078,31079,31080,31081,31082,31083", "answer": "31084"}
{"prompt": "462,463,464,465,466,467", "answer": "468"}
{"prompt": "35390,35391,35392", "answer": "35393"}
{"prompt": "22050,22051,22052,22053,22054,22055", "answer": "22056"}
{"prompt": "4418,4419,4420,4421,4422,4423,4424", "answer": "4425"}
{"prompt": "35159,35160,35161,35162,35163,35164,35165", "answer": "35166"}
{"prompt": "2020,2021,2022,2023,2024", "answer": "2025"}
{"prompt": "470,471,472", "answer": "473"}
{"prompt": "35810,35811,35812,35813,35814,35815,35816,35817,35818", "answer": "35819"}
{"prompt": "28037,28038,28039,28040,28041,28042,28043,28044", "answer": "28045"}
{"prompt": "24974,24975,24976,24977,24978,24979", "answer": "24980"}
{"prompt": "28244,28245", "answer": "28246"}
{"prompt": "3458,3459,3460,3461", "answer": "3462"}
{"prompt": "35204", "answer": "35205"}
{"prompt": "19772,19773,19774,19775,19776", "answer": "19777"}
{"prompt": "36687,36688,36689", "answer": "36690"}
{"prompt": "5600,5601,5602,5603,5604", "answer": "5605"}
{"prompt": "35027", "answer": "35028"}
{"prompt": "31418,31419", "answer": "31420"}
{"prompt": "2864", "answer": "2865"}
{"prompt": "31245,31246,31247,31248,31249,31250,31251,31252,31253", "answer": "31254"}
{"prompt": "4089,4090,4091,4092,4093,4094,4095,4096", "answer": "4097"}
{"prompt": "41712,41713,41714,41715", "answer": "41716"}
{"prompt": "5459,5460,5461,5462,5463,5464,5465,5466,5467", "answer": "5468"}
{"prompt": "39573,39574,39575,39576,39577,39578,39579,39580,39581", "answer": "39582"}
{"prompt": "16951,16952,16953", "answer": "16954"}
{"prompt": "4905,4906,4907", "answer": "4908"}
{"prompt": "21584,21585,21586,21587,21588,21589,21590,21591", "answer": "21592"}
{"prompt": "2987,2988", "answer": "2989"}
{"prompt": "4836,4837", "answer": "4838"}
{"prompt": "20365", "answer": "20366"}
{"prompt": "23886,23887,23888,23889,23890", "answer": "23891"}
{"prompt": "33767,33768,33769,33770,33771,33772,33773", "answer": "33774"}
{"prompt": "26879", "answer": "26880"}
{"prompt": "38284,38285,38286,38287,38288,38289,38290,38291", "answer": "38292"}
{"prompt": "18652,18653,18654", "answer": "18655"}
{"prompt": "30122,30123,30124,30125,30126,30127,30128,30129,30130", "answer": "30131"}
{"prompt": "10123,10124,10125,10126", "answer": "10127"}
{"prompt": "16660,16661,16662", "answer": "16663"}
{"prompt": "8659,8660,8661,8662,8663,8664,8665,8666", "answer": "8667"}
{"prompt": "19062,19063,19064", "answer": "19065"}
{"prompt": "44099,44100,44101,44102,44103,44104,44105,44106", "answer": "44107"}
{"prompt": "7533,7534,7535,7536,7537", "answer": "7538"}
{"prompt": "18798,18799,18800,18801,18802,18803,18804,18805,18806", "answer": "18807"}
{"prompt": "29056,29057,29058,29059,29060", "answer": "29061"}
{"prompt": "3454,3455,3456,3457", "answer": "3458"}
{"prompt": "1518,1519,1520,1521,1522,1523,1524,1525,1526", "answer": "1527"}
{"prompt": "39702,39703,39704,39705,39706,39707,39708,39709,39710,39711", "answer": "39712"}
{"prompt": "21435,21436", "answer": "21437"}
{"prompt": "19882,19883,19884,19885,19886,19887", "answer": "19888"}
{"prompt": "10838,10839,10840,10841,10842,10843,10844,10845,10846", "answer": "10847"}
{"prompt": "31767,31768,31769", "answer": "31770"}
{"prompt": "42024", "answer": "42025"}
{"prompt": "36936,36937,36938,36939,36940,36941,36942", "answer": "36943"}
{"prompt": "15871,15872,15873,15874", "answer": "15875"}
{"prompt": "3356,3357,3358,3359,3360,3361,3362", "answer": "3363"}
{"prompt": "14791,14792", "answer": "14793"}
{"prompt": "15211,15212,15213,15214,15215", "answer": "15216"}
{"prompt": "10650,10651,10652,10653,10654,10655", "answer": "10656"}
{"prompt": "14871,14872,14873,14874,14875", "answer": "14876"}
{"prompt": "27773,27774,27775,27776,27777,27778,27779", "answer": "27780"}
{"prompt": "40623,40624,40625,40626,40627,40628", "answer": "40629"}
{"prompt": "24084,24085,24086,24087,24088,24089,24090,24091,24092", "answer": "24093"}
{"prompt": "4244,4245,4246,4247,4248,4249,4250,4251,4252", "answer": "4253"}
{"prompt": "13551,13552,13553,13554,13555,13556,13557", "answer": "13558"}
{"prompt": "15566,15567,15568,15569,15570,15571,15572,15573", "answer": "15574"}
{"prompt": "1734,1735,1736,1737,1738,1739,1740", "answer": "1741"}
{"prompt": "14426", "answer": "14427"}
{"prompt": "24683,24684,24685,24686,24687,24688,24689,24690", "answer": "24691"}
{"prompt": "1590", "answer": "1591"}
{"prompt": "13786,13787,13788", "answer": "13789"}
{"prompt": "32629,32630", "answer": "32631"}
{"prompt": "1389,1390,1391,1392,1393,1394,1395,1396", "answer": "1397"}
{"prompt": "39718,39719,39720,39721,39722,39723,39724", "answer": "39725"}
{"prompt": "12446,12447,12448,12449", "answer": "12450"}
{"prompt": "5888,5889,5890,5891,5892,5893,5894,5895,5896,5897", "answer": "5898"}
{"prompt": "30042", "answer": "30043"}
{"prompt": "26208,26209,26210,26211,26212,26213", "answer": "26214"}
{"prompt": "26294,26295,26296,26297,26298,26299,26300,26301,26302,26303", "answer": "26304"}
{"prompt": "25397,25398,25399,25400,25401", "answer": "25402"}
{"prompt": "8573", "answer": "8574"}
{"prompt": "10722,10723,10724,10725,10726", "answer": "10727"}
{"prompt": "35933,35934,35935,35936,35937,35938,35939", "answer": "35940"}
{"prompt": "32531", "answer": "32532"}
{"prompt": "14656", "answer": "14657"}
{"prompt": "44879,44880,44881,44882,44883", "answer": "44884"}
{"prompt": "12173,12174,12175,12176,12177", "answer": "12178"}
{"prompt": "36023,36024,36025,36026,36027,36028,36029,36030,36031,36032", "answer": "36033"}
{"prompt": "32401,32402,32403,32404,32405,32406,32407", "answer": "32408"}
{"prompt": "12721,12722,12723,12724,12725", "answer": "12726"}
{"prompt": "2997,2998,2999,3000", "answer": "3001"}
{"prompt": "6658,6659", "answer": "6660"}
{"prompt": "1880,1881,1882,1883,1884,1885,1886,1887,1888,1889", "answer": "1890"}
{"prompt": "34419", "answer": "34420"}
{"prompt": "15254,15255,15256", "answer": "15257"}
{"prompt": "19005,19006,19007,19008,19009", "answer": "19010"}
{"prompt": "29017,29018,29019,29020,29021,29022,29023,29024,29025", "answer": "29026"}
{"prompt": "29375,29376,29377,29378,29379,29380", "answer": "29381"}
{"prompt": "4385,4386,4387,4388,4389,4390,4391,4392", "answer": "4393"}
{"prompt": "35326,35327,35328,35329,35330,35331,35332", "answer": "35333"}
{"prompt": "13654,13655", "answer": "13656"}
{"prompt": "41061,41062,41063,41064,41065", "answer": "41066"}
{"prompt": "34573", "answer": "34574"}
{"prompt": "38441,38442,38443,38444,38445,38446,38447,38448", "answer": "38449"}
{"prompt": "1048,1049,1050,1051,1052,1053,1054,1055", "answer": "1056"}
{"prompt": "26040", "answer": "26041"}
{"prompt": "45156,45157,45158,45159", "answer": "45160"}
{"prompt": "25311,25312,25313", "answer": "25314"}
{"prompt": "43245,43246,43247,43248,43249,43250,43251,43252,43253,43254", "answer": "43255"}
{"prompt": "4147,4148,4149,4150,4151,4152", "answer": "4153"}
{"prompt": "40569,40570", "answer": "40571"}
{"prompt": "1059,1060,1061,1062,1063,1064,1065,1066", "answer": "1067"}
{"prompt": "17827,17828,17829,17830,17831,17832,17833", "answer": "17834"}
{"prompt": "18257,18258", "answer": "18259"}
{"prompt": "23486,23487,23488,23489,23490,23491", "answer": "23492"}
{"prompt": "33456,33457,33458,33459,33460,33461,33462,33463,33464,33465", "answer": "33466"}
{"prompt": "32843,32844,32845,32846,32847,32848,32849", "answer": "32850"}
{"prompt": "15082,15083", "answer": "15084"}
{"prompt": "42974,42975,42976,42977,42978,42979", "answer": "42980"}
{"prompt": "30603,30604,30605", "answer": "30606"}
{"prompt": "1935,1936,1937,1938,1939,1940,1941,1942,1943,1944", "answer": "1945"}
{"prompt": "21465,21466,21467,21468,21469,21470,21471,21472", "answer": "21473"}
{"prompt": "30205,30206,30207,30208,30209,30210,30211,30212,30213", "answer": "30214"}
{"prompt": "17272,17273", "answer": "17274"}
{"prompt": "36948,36949,36950,36951,36952", "answer": "36953"}
{"prompt": "23418,23419,23420,23421,23422,23423,23424", "answer": "23425"}
{"prompt": "21759,21760,21761", "answer": "21762"}
{"prompt": "45235,45236,45237,45238,45239,45240,45241,45242,45243", "answer": "45244"}
{"prompt": "34058,34059,34060", "answer": "34061"}
{"prompt": "1789,1790,1791,1792,1793,1794", "answer": "1795"}
{"prompt": "10689", "answer": "10690"}
{"prompt": "43323,43324,43325,43326,43327,43328,43329", "answer": "43330"}
{"prompt": "43393,43394,43395", "answer": "43396"}
{"prompt": "38758", "answer": "38759"}
{"prompt": "26731,26732,26733,26734,26735,26736,26737,26738", "answer": "26739"}
{"prompt": "21995,21996,21997,21998,21999,22000", "answer": "22001"}
{"prompt": "18094,18095,18096,18097,18098,18099,18100,18101,18102,18103", "answer": "18104"}
{"prompt": "28994,28995,28996,28997,28998,28999,29000,29001,29002,29003", "answer": "29004"}
{"prompt": "34556,34557,34558,34559", "answer": "34560"}
{"prompt": "10035,10036,10037,10038,10039,10040,10041", "answer": "10042"}
{"prompt": "2002,2003,2004,2005,2006,2007", "answer": "2008"}
{"prompt": "40373,40374", "answer": "40375"}
{"prompt": "36368,36369,36370", "answer": "36371"}
{"prompt": "4937,4938,4939,4940,4941,4942,4943,4944", "answer": "4945"}
{"prompt": "15218,15219,15220", "answer": "15221"}
{"prompt": "45101,45102,45103,45104,45105,45106,45107,45108,45109", "answer": "45110"}
{"prompt": "5441,5442,5443", "answer": "5444"}
{"prompt": "9050,9051,9052,9053,9054,9055", "answer": "9056"}
{"prompt": "378,379,380,381", "answer": "382"}
{"prompt": "5902,5903,5904,5905,5906", "answer": "5907"}
{"prompt": "22116,22117,22118", "answer": "22119"}
{"prompt": "20446,20447,20448,20449", "answer": "20450"}
{"prompt": "31758,31759,31760,31761,31762,31763,31764,31765,31766,31767", "answer": "31768"}
{"prompt": "32815,32816,32817,32818", "answer": "32819"}
{"prompt": "15110,15111,15112,15113,15114", "answer": "15115"}
{"prompt": "36806,36807,36808,36809,36810,36811,36812,36813,36814,36815", "answer": "36816"}
{"prompt": "31169,31170", "answer": "31171"}
{"prompt": "29412", "answer": "29413"}
{"prompt": "3677,3678,3679,3680", "answer": "3681"}
{"prompt": "36563,36564,36565,36566,36567,36568,36569,36570,36571,36572", "answer": "36573"}
{"prompt": "16119,16120,16121,16122", "answer": "16123"}
{"prompt": "6104,6105,6106", "answer": "6107"}
{"prompt": "35159", "answer": "35160"}
{"prompt": "32186", "answer": "32187"}
{"prompt": "40317,40318,40319", "answer": "40320"}
{"prompt": "15950,15951,15952,15953,15954", "answer": "15955"}
{"prompt": "1649,1650,1651,1652,1653,1654,1655,1656,1657,1658", "answer": "1659"}
{"prompt": "1697,1698,1699,1700,1701,1702", "answer": "1703"}
{"prompt": "24074,24075,24076,24077,24078,24079", "answer": "24080"}
{"prompt": "6098,6099", "answer": "6100"}
{"prompt": "41369,41370,41371,41372,41373,41374,41375", "answer": "41376"}
{"prompt": "5279,5280,5281,5282,5283", "answer": "5284"}
{"prompt": "44315,44316,44317,44318", "answer": "44319"}
{"prompt": "17207,17208,17209,17210,17211,17212", "answer": "17213"}
{"prompt": "2959,2960,2961,2962,2963", "answer": "2964"}
{"prompt": "11601,11602,11603,11604", "answer": "11605"}
{"prompt": "8424,8425,8426,8427,8428,8429,8430", "answer": "8431"}
{"prompt": "27245,27246,27247", "answer": "27248"}
{"prompt": "40525,40526,40527,40528,40529,40530,40531", "answer": "40532"}
{"prompt": "18315,18316,18317,18318,18319,18320", "answer": "18321"}
{"prompt": "14426,14427", "answer": "14428"}
{"prompt": "42339,42340,42341,42342,42343", "answer": "42344"}
{"prompt": "5995,5996", "answer": "5997"}
{"prompt": "5176,5177,5178,5179,5180", "answer": "5181"}
{"prompt": "28850,28851,28852,28853,28854,28855,28856,28857", "answer": "28858"}
{"prompt": "38268,38269,38270,38271,38272,38273,38274,38275,38276", "answer": "38277"}
{"prompt": "15732,15733,15734,15735,15736,15737,15738", "answer": "15739"}
{"prompt": "40856,40857,40858,40859,40860,40861", "answer": "40862"}
{"prompt": "44491,44492", "answer": "44493"}
{"prompt": "5268,5269,5270,5271,5272", "answer": "5273"}
{"prompt": "15956,15957,15958,15959,15960,15961,15962", "answer": "15963"}
{"prompt": "25684,25685", "answer": "25686"}
{"prompt": "21885,21886,21887,21888,21889", "answer": "21890"}
{"prompt": "2829,2830,2831,2832,2833,2834,2835", "answer": "2836"}
{"prompt": "28449,28450,28451,28452,28453,28454,28455,28456", "answer": "28457"}
{"prompt": "13510,13511,13512", "answer": "13513"}
{"prompt": "32266,32267,32268,32269,32270", "answer": "32271"}
{"prompt": "11163,11164,11165,11166,11167", "answer": "11168"}
{"prompt": "31588,31589", "answer": "31590"}
{"prompt": "25004,25005", "answer": "25006"}
{"prompt": "2410,2411,2412,2413,2414,2415,2416", "answer": "2417"}
{"prompt": "41164,41165", "answer": "41166"}
{"prompt": "1267,1268", "answer": "1269"}
{"prompt": "20751,20752,20753,20754,20755,20756,20757,20758,20759", "answer": "20760"}
{"prompt": "24768,24769,24770", "answer": "24771"}
{"prompt": "35973,35974,35975,35976", "answer": "35977"}
{"prompt": "40447,40448,40449,40450", "answer": "40451"}
{"prompt": "33068,33069,33070,33071,33072,33073,33074", "answer": "33075"}
{"prompt": "7503,7504,7505,7506,7507,7508,7509", "answer": "7510"}
{"prompt": "29859,29860,29861,29862,29863,29864,29865,29866,29867,29868", "answer": "29869"}
{"prompt": "43738,43739,43740,43741,43742,43743,43744", "answer": "43745"}
{"prompt": "21558,21559,21560,21561,21562,21563", "answer": "21564"}
{"prompt": "39026,39027", "answer": "39028"}
{"prompt": "40751", "answer": "40752"}
{"prompt": "27578,27579,27580,27581,27582,27583,27584,27585,27586", "answer": "27587"}
{"prompt": "28788,28789,28790,28791,28792,28793,28794,28795,28796,28797", "answer": "28798"}
{"prompt": "3581,3582", "answer": "3583"}
{"prompt": "6379,6380,6381,6382,6383,6384", "answer": "6385"}
{"prompt": "2492,2493,2494,2495", "answer": "2496"}
{"prompt": "30411,30412,30413,30414,30415,30416,30417", "answer": "30418"}
{"prompt": "7977,7978,7979,7980", "answer": "7981"}
{"prompt": "32226,32227,32228", "answer": "32229"}
{"prompt": "43830,43831,43832", "answer": "43833"}
{"prompt": "30280,30281,30282,30283,30284,30285,30286,30287", "answer": "30288"}
{"prompt": "9978,9979,9980,9981,9982,9983,9984,9985,9986,9987", "answer": "9988"}
{"prompt": "17254,17255,17256,17257", "answer": "17258"}
{"prompt": "8678,8679,8680,8681,8682,8683,8684,8685,8686", "answer": "8687"}
{"prompt": "40712,40713,40714,40715,40716", "answer": "40717"}
{"prompt": "42091", "answer": "42092"}
{"prompt": "5971,5972,5973,5974,5975,5976,5977,5978,5979", "answer": "5980"}
{"prompt": "25586,25587", "answer": "25588"}
{"prompt": "34608,34609,34610,34611,34612,34613,34614,34615", "answer": "34616"}
{"prompt": "26094,26095,26096,26097,26098,26099,26100,26101,26102", "answer": "26103"}
{"prompt": "10507,10508,10509,10510,10511,10512,10513,10514", "answer": "10515"}
{"prompt": "34669,34670", "answer": "34671"}
{"prompt": "20508,20509,20510,20511,20512,20513,20514,20515", "answer": "20516"}
{"prompt": "12646,12647,12648,12649,12650,12651,12652,12653,12654", "answer": "12655"}
{"prompt": "19877,19878,19879,19880,19881,19882", "answer": "19883"}
{"prompt": "38318,38319,38320,38321,38322,38323,38324,38325", "answer": "38326"}
{"prompt": "2621", "answer": "2622"}
{"prompt": "4855,4856,4857,4858,4859", "answer": "4860"}
{"prompt": "36519,36520,36521,36522,36523,36524,36525", "answer": "36526"}
{"prompt": "21453,21454,21455,21456,21457,21458", "answer": "21459"}
{"prompt": "537,538,539,540,541,542,543,544,545", "answer": "546"}
{"prompt": "10529,10530,10531,10532,10533,10534,10535,10536", "answer": "10537"}
{"prompt": "21732,21733,21734,21735,21736,21737", "answer": "21738"}
{"prompt": "12630,12631", "answer": "12632"}
{"prompt": "15839,15840,15841,15842,15843,15844,15845,15846", "answer": "15847"}
{"prompt": "31561,31562,31563,31564,31565,31566,31567,31568", "answer": "31569"}
{"prompt": "26138,26139,26140,26141,26142,26143", "answer": "26144"}
{"prompt": "9749,9750,9751,9752,9753,9754", "answer": "9755"}
{"prompt": "36142,36143,36144,36145,36146", "answer": "36147"}
{"prompt": "9994,9995,9996", "answer": "9997"}
{"prompt": "4531,4532,4533,4534,4535,4536,4537,4538,4539,4540", "answer": "4541"}
{"prompt": "2169,2170,2171,2172", "answer": "2173"}
{"prompt": "40062,40063", "answer": "40064"}
{"prompt": "21563,21564,21565", "answer": "21566"}
{"prompt": "35874,35875,35876", "answer": "35877"}
{"prompt": "1804", "answer": "1805"}
{"prompt": "10085,10086,10087,10088,10089,10090,10091,10092,10093,10094", "answer": "10095"}
{"prompt": "21269,21270,21271,21272,21273,21274,21275,21276,21277,21278", "answer": "21279"}
{"prompt": "1762,1763", "answer": "1764"}
{"prompt": "39386,39387,39388,39389,39390,39391,39392,39393,39394", "answer": "39395"}
{"prompt": "12573,12574", "answer": "12575"}
{"prompt": "33542,33543,33544,33545,33546,33547,33548,33549,33550", "answer": "33551"}
{"prompt": "16417,16418,16419,16420", "answer": "16421"}
{"prompt": "36647,36648,36649,36650,36651,36652,36653,36654,36655,36656", "answer": "36657"}
{"prompt": "29723,29724,29725,29726,29727,29728,29729,29730,29731,29732", "answer": "29733"}
{"prompt": "30582,30583,30584,30585,30586,30587", "answer": "30588"}
{"prompt": "41376,41377,41378,41379", "answer": "41380"}
{"prompt": "1298", "answer": "1299"}
{"prompt": "27900,27901,27902", "answer": "27903"}
{"prompt": "18785,18786,18787,18788,18789", "answer": "18790"}
{"prompt": "1801,1802,1803,1804", "answer": "1805"}
{"prompt": "40041,40042,40043,40044,40045,40046,40047,40048", "answer": "40049"}
{"prompt": "13977,13978,13979,13980,13981,13982,13983,13984", "answer": "13985"}
{"prompt": "42404,42405,42406", "answer": "42407"}
{"prompt": "16282,16283,16284,16285,16286,16287,16288,16289,16290,16291", "answer": "16292"}
{"prompt": "19622,19623,19624,19625,19626,19627", "answer": "19628"}
{"prompt": "39146,39147,39148,39149,39150,39151,39152", "answer": "39153"}
{"prompt": "42387,42388,42389,42390,42391,42392,42393,42394", "answer": "42395"}
{"prompt": "21677,21678,21679,21680,21681,21682,21683", "answer": "21684"}
{"prompt": "41014", "answer": "41015"}
{"prompt": "37415,37416,37417,37418,37419", "answer": "37420"}
{"prompt": "41207,41208,41209,41210", "answer": "41211"}
{"prompt": "8184,8185,8186,8187,8188,8189,8190", "answer": "8191"}
{"prompt": "35905,35906,35907,35908,35909,35910,35911,35912", "answer": "35913"}
{"prompt": "22198,22199,22200,22201,22202,22203,22204,22205,22206,22207", "answer": "22208"}
{"prompt": "44386,44387,44388,44389,44390", "answer": "44391"}
{"prompt": "2230,2231,2232", "answer": "2233"}
{"prompt": "17172,17173,17174,17175,17176,17177,17178,17179", "answer": "17180"}
{"prompt": "15537,15538,15539,15540,15541", "answer": "15542"}
{"prompt": "43522,43523,43524,43525,43526,43527,43528,43529,43530,43531", "answer": "43532"}
{"prompt": "19235,19236,19237,19238,19239,19240,19241,19242", "answer": "19243"}
{"prompt": "42660,42661,42662,42663,42664,42665", "answer": "42666"}
{"prompt": "14305", "answer": "14306"}
{"prompt": "32537,32538,32539,32540", "answer": "32541"}
{"prompt": "27517", "answer": "27518"}
{"prompt": "29091,29092,29093", "answer": "29094"}
{"prompt": "22886,22887,22888,22889,22890,22891,22892,22893", "answer": "22894"}
{"prompt": "2252,2253,2254,2255,2256,2257,2258,2259", "answer": "2260"}
{"prompt": "31580,31581,31582", "answer": "31583"}
{"prompt": "6162", "answer": "6163"}
{"prompt": "9158,9159,9160,9161,9162,9163,9164,9165", "answer": "9166"}
{"prompt": "1010,1011,1012,1013", "answer": "1014"}
{"prompt": "25454,25455,25456,25457,25458,25459", "answer": "25460"}
{"prompt": "26642,26643,26644,26645,26646,26647", "answer": "26648"}
{"prompt": "45169", "answer": "45170"}
{"prompt": "8929,8930,8931", "answer": "8932"}
{"prompt": "30168,30169,30170,30171,30172,30173,30174,30175,30176,30177", "answer": "30178"}
{"prompt": "6432", "answer": "6433"}
{"prompt": "32221,32222,32223,32224,32225,32226", "answer": "32227"}
{"prompt": "11704,11705,11706,11707,11708,11709,11710", "answer": "11711"}
{"prompt": "43558,43559,43560,43561,43562,43563,43564,43565,43566,43567", "answer": "43568"}
{"prompt": "17565,17566", "answer": "17567"}
{"prompt": "24551,24552,24553,24554,24555,24556,24557,24558", "answer": "24559"}
{"prompt": "34585,34586,34587,34588,34589,34590,34591,34592", "answer": "34593"}
{"prompt": "17848,17849,17850,17851,17852,17853", "answer": "17854"}
{"prompt": "41765,41766,41767,41768,41769,41770,41771,41772", "answer": "41773"}
{"prompt": "23716,23717,23718,23719,23720,23721", "answer": "23722"}
{"prompt": "6798,6799,6800,6801,6802,6803", "answer": "6804"}
{"prompt": "23757", "answer": "23758"}
{"prompt": "11365,11366,11367,11368,11369", "answer": "11370"}
{"prompt": "11528,11529,11530,11531,11532,11533,11534", "answer": "11535"}
{"prompt": "1693,1694,1695,1696", "answer": "1697"}
{"prompt": "42584,42585,42586,42587,42588", "answer": "42589"}
{"prompt": "44801,44802,44803,44804,44805,44806", "answer": "44807"}
{"prompt": "43807,43808,43809,43810", "answer": "43811"}
{"prompt": "12858,12859,12860,12861,12862,12863,12864,12865,12866,12867", "answer": "12868"}
{"prompt": "17901", "answer": "17902"}
{"prompt": "509,510,511,512,513,514,515", "answer": "516"}
{"prompt": "39177,39178,39179,39180,39181", "answer": "39182"}
{"prompt": "30831,30832,30833,30834,30835,30836", "answer": "30837"}
{"prompt": "31582,31583,31584", "answer": "31585"}
{"prompt": "24428,24429", "answer": "24430"}
{"prompt": "36867,36868", "answer": "36869"}
{"prompt": "2473,2474,2475,2476", "answer": "2477"}
{"prompt": "16901,16902", "answer": "16903"}
{"prompt": "32,33,34,35,36,37,38", "answer": "39"}
{"prompt": "3753,3754,3755,3756,3757", "answer": "3758"}
{"prompt": "15119,15120", "answer": "15121"}
{"prompt": "36382,36383,36384,36385,36386,36387", "answer": "36388"}
{"prompt": "11392,11393,11394,11395,11396", "answer": "11397"}
{"prompt": "21257,21258,21259", "answer": "21260"}
{"prompt": "30296,30297,30298,30299,30300,30301,30302,30303,30304", "answer": "30305"}
{"prompt": "28271,28272,28273", "answer": "28274"}
{"prompt": "132,133,134,135,136,137", "answer": "138"}
{"prompt": "14956,14957", "answer": "14958"}
{"prompt": "7020,7021,7022,7023,7024", "answer": "7025"}
{"prompt": "40163,40164,40165,40166,40167,40168,40169,40170,40171,40172", "answer": "40173"}
{"prompt": "44883,44884,44885,44886,44887,44888,44889,44890,44891,44892", "answer": "44893"}
{"prompt": "38909,38910,38911,38912,38913,38914,38915,38916,38917", "answer": "38918"}
{"prompt": "28251,28252,28253,28254,28255,28256,28257,28258,28259", "answer": "28260"}
{"prompt": "10303,10304,10305,10306,10307,10308,10309,10310,10311", "answer": "10312"}
{"prompt": "42783,42784", "answer": "42785"}
{"prompt": "25101", "answer": "25102"}
{"prompt": "25820,25821,25822,25823,25824,25825,25826,25827,25828", "answer": "25829"}
{"prompt": "24790,24791,24792,24793,24794,24795,24796", "answer": "24797"}
{"prompt": "16462,16463,16464,16465,16466,16467,16468,16469,16470,16471", "answer": "16472"}
{"prompt": "19117,19118,19119,19120,19121", "answer": "19122"}
{"prompt": "41863,41864,41865,41866,41867", "answer": "41868"}
{"prompt": "23413,23414,23415,23416,23417,23418", "answer": "23419"}
{"prompt": "13425,13426,13427,13428", "answer": "13429"}
{"prompt": "30143,30144,30145,30146,30147,30148", "answer": "30149"}
{"prompt": "44609,44610,44611,44612,44613", "answer": "44614"}
{"prompt": "17776,17777,17778", "answer": "17779"}
{"prompt": "22943,22944", "answer": "22945"}
{"prompt": "41312,41313,41314,41315,41316", "answer": "41317"}
{"prompt": "31157,31158,31159,31160", "answer": "31161"}
{"prompt": "20208,20209,20210,20211,20212", "answer": "20213"}
{"prompt": "28218,28219,28220,28221,28222,28223", "answer": "28224"}
{"prompt": "41177,41178,41179", "answer": "41180"}
{"prompt": "25615", "answer": "25616"}
{"prompt": "28151,28152,28153,28154,28155,28156,28157", "answer": "28158"}
{"prompt": "30700,30701,30702,30703,30704,30705,30706,30707", "answer": "30708"}
{"prompt": "18245,18246,18247,18248,18249", "answer": "18250"}
{"prompt": "15175,15176,15177,15178", "answer": "15179"}
{"prompt": "26636,26637,26638,26639,26640", "answer": "26641"}
{"prompt": "29204,29205,29206,29207,29208,29209,29210,29211", "answer": "29212"}
{"prompt": "44225,44226,44227,44228,44229,44230", "answer": "44231"}
{"prompt": "32079,32080", "answer": "32081"}
{"prompt": "22555,22556,22557,22558,22559,22560,22561,22562,22563", "answer": "22564"}
{"prompt": "19561,19562,19563", "answer": "19564"}
{"prompt": "23251,23252,23253", "answer": "23254"}
{"prompt": "6091,6092", "answer": "6093"}
{"prompt": "19991,19992", "answer": "19993"}
{"prompt": "2703,2704,2705,2706,2707,2708", "answer": "2709"}
{"prompt": "45050,45051,45052,45053,45054,45055,45056,45057,45058,45059", "answer": "45060"}
{"prompt": "6395,6396,6397,6398,6399,6400", "answer": "6401"}
{"prompt": "36035,36036,36037,36038,36039,36040,36041", "answer": "36042"}
{"prompt": "22447,22448,22449", "answer": "22450"}
{"prompt": "28079,28080,28081,28082,28083,28084,28085,28086,28087", "answer": "28088"}
{"prompt": "11388,11389,11390,11391,11392", "answer": "11393"}
{"prompt": "5115", "answer": "5116"}
{"prompt": "9413,9414,9415,9416,9417,9418", "answer": "9419"}
{"prompt": "2499,2500,2501,2502,2503,2504", "answer": "2505"}
{"prompt": "22632,22633,22634,22635,22636", "answer": "22637"}
{"prompt": "36128,36129,36130,36131,36132,36133", "answer": "36134"}
{"prompt": "23599,23600,23601,23602,23603,23604", "answer": "23605"}
{"prompt": "5410,5411,5412,5413,5414,5415,5416,5417,5418,5419", "answer": "5420"}
{"prompt": "22279,22280,22281,22282,22283", "answer": "22284"}
{"prompt": "37769,37770,37771,37772,37773,37774,37775,37776", "answer": "37777"}
{"prompt": "36536,36537", "answer": "36538"}
{"prompt": "43678,43679", "answer": "43680"}
{"prompt": "18771,18772,18773,18774", "answer": "18775"}
{"prompt": "33498,33499,33500,33501,33502,33503,33504,33505,33506,33507", "answer": "33508"}
{"prompt": "29634,29635,29636", "answer": "29637"}
{"prompt": "24765,24766,24767,24768", "answer": "24769"}
{"prompt": "31105,31106", "answer": "31107"}
{"prompt": "33051,33052", "answer": "33053"}
{"prompt": "10540,10541,10542", "answer": "10543"}
{"prompt": "5567,5568,5569,5570", "answer": "5571"}
{"prompt": "26506,26507,26508,26509", "answer": "26510"}
{"prompt": "27072,27073,27074", "answer": "27075"}
{"prompt": "40989,40990,40991", "answer": "40992"}
{"prompt": "25244", "answer": "25245"}
{"prompt": "20429,20430,20431,20432", "answer": "20433"}
{"prompt": "15808,15809,15810,15811", "answer": "15812"}
{"prompt": "14124,14125,14126,14127,14128,14129,14130", "answer": "14131"}
{"prompt": "2575", "answer": "2576"}
{"prompt": "38806,38807,38808,38809", "answer": "38810"}
{"prompt": "40224", "answer": "40225"}
{"prompt": "3739,3740,3741,3742,3743,3744,3745,3746", "answer": "3747"}
{"prompt": "6705,6706,6707,6708,6709,6710,6711", "answer": "6712"}
{"prompt": "30562,30563,30564", "answer": "30565"}
{"prompt": "12450,12451,12452,12453,12454,12455", "answer": "12456"}
{"prompt": "13480,13481", "answer": "13482"}
{"prompt": "37840", "answer": "37841"}
{"prompt": "31723,31724,31725", "answer": "31726"}
{"prompt": "13724,13725,13726,13727,13728,13729", "answer": "13730"}
{"prompt": "20382,20383,20384", "answer": "20385"}
{"prompt": "12677,12678", "answer": "12679"}
{"prompt": "2531,2532,2533", "answer": "2534"}
{"prompt": "41849,41850,41851,41852,41853,41854,41855,41856,41857,41858", "answer": "41859"}
{"prompt": "41779", "answer": "41780"}
{"prompt": "39047,39048,39049,39050", "answer": "39051"}
{"prompt": "34687,34688,34689,34690,34691,34692", "answer": "34693"}
{"prompt": "41910", "answer": "41911"}
{"prompt": "6859,6860,6861", "answer": "6862"}
{"prompt": "7752,7753,7754,7755,7756,7757", "answer": "7758"}
{"prompt": "480,481,482,483,484,485,486,487", "answer": "488"}
{"prompt": "949,950,951,952,953,954,955,956", "answer": "957"}
{"prompt": "41218,41219,41220,41221,41222,41223,41224,41225,41226,41227", "answer": "41228"}
{"prompt": "33167,33168,33169,33170,33171,33172,33173,33174", "answer": "33175"}
{"prompt": "26363,26364,26365,26366,26367,26368,26369", "answer": "26370"}
{"prompt": "11167,11168,11169,11170,11171,11172,11173,11174", "answer": "11175"}
{"prompt": "25136,25137,25138,25139,25140,25141", "answer": "25142"}
{"prompt": "11220,11221,11222", "answer": "11223"}
{"prompt": "15682", "answer": "15683"}
{"prompt": "16087,16088,16089,16090,16091,16092,16093", "answer": "16094"}
{"prompt": "13778,13779,13780,13781", "answer": "13782"}
{"prompt": "5754,5755,5756,5757,5758,5759,5760,5761,5762", "answer": "5763"}
{"prompt": "30991,30992,30993,30994,30995,30996,30997,30998,30999,31000", "answer": "31001"}
{"prompt": "3087,3088,3089,3090,3091,3092,3093,3094", "answer": "3095"}
{"prompt": "13606,13607,13608,13609", "answer": "13610"}
{"prompt": "24963,24964,24965,24966,24967", "answer": "24968"}
{"prompt": "5147,5148,5149,5150,5151,5152,5153,5154,5155,5156", "answer": "5157"}
{"prompt": "19944,19945,19946,19947", "answer": "19948"}
{"prompt": "29535,29536,29537,29538,29539,29540,29541", "answer": "29542"}
{"prompt": "25193,25194,25195,25196,25197,25198,25199,25200", "answer": "25201"}
{"prompt": "43764", "answer": "43765"}
{"prompt": "1027,1028,1029,1030,1031,1032,1033,1034", "answer": "1035"}
{"prompt": "19040,19041,19042,19043,19044", "answer": "19045"}
{"prompt": "21115", "answer": "21116"}
{"prompt": "5518,5519", "answer": "5520"}
{"prompt": "13709,13710,13711,13712,13713,13714,13715,13716,13717,13718", "answer": "13719"}
{"prompt": "14716,14717", "answer": "14718"}
{"prompt": "16020,16021,16022,16023,16024,16025,16026,16027,16028,16029", "answer": "16030"}
{"prompt": "20879,20880", "answer": "20881"}
{"prompt": "18763,18764,18765,18766,18767,18768,18769,18770,18771", "answer": "18772"}
{"prompt": "24624,24625,24626,24627,24628", "answer": "24629"}
{"prompt": "42540,42541,42542,42543", "answer": "42544"}
{"prompt": "18272,18273,18274,18275,18276", "answer": "18277"}
{"prompt": "16000,16001,16002,16003", "answer": "16004"}
{"prompt": "33158,33159,33160", "answer": "33161"}
{"prompt": "15610,15611,15612,15613,15614,15615,15616", "answer": "15617"}
{"prompt": "31151,31152,31153,31154,31155,31156,31157", "answer": "31158"}
{"prompt": "3249,3250,3251,3252,3253,3254", "answer": "3255"}
{"prompt": "16330,16331,16332,16333", "answer": "16334"}
{"prompt": "22974,22975,22976,22977", "answer": "22978"}
{"prompt": "41330,41331,41332,41333,41334,41335,41336,41337", "answer": "41338"}
{"prompt": "32349,32350", "answer": "32351"}
{"prompt": "35214,35215,35216,35217,35218", "answer": "35219"}
{"prompt": "18418,18419,18420,18421,18422,18423,18424,18425,18426", "answer": "18427"}
{"prompt": "1742,1743,1744,1745,1746,1747", "answer": "1748"}
{"prompt": "3383,3384,3385,3386,3387,3388,3389,3390", "answer": "3391"}
{"prompt": "43764", "answer": "43765"}
{"prompt": "40548", "answer": "40549"}
{"prompt": "24065,24066,24067,24068,24069,24070", "answer": "24071"}
{"prompt": "15475,15476,15477,15478", "answer": "15479"}
{"prompt": "34135,34136,34137,34138,34139,34140", "answer": "34141"}
{"prompt": "29897", "answer": "29898"}
{"prompt": "28947,28948,28949,28950,28951,28952", "answer": "28953"}
{"prompt": "17120,17121,17122,17123,17124", "answer": "17125"}
{"prompt": "20518,20519,20520,20521,20522,20523", "answer": "20524"}
{"prompt": "12301,12302,12303,12304,12305,12306,12307,12308,12309,12310", "answer": "12311"}
{"prompt": "35474,35475,35476,35477,35478", "answer": "35479"}
{"prompt": "39953,39954,39955,39956,39957,39958,39959", "answer": "39960"}
{"prompt": "19580", "answer": "19581"}
{"prompt": "31213", "answer": "31214"}
{"prompt": "30943,30944,30945,30946", "answer": "30947"}
{"prompt": "14712,14713,14714", "answer": "14715"}
{"prompt": "1676,1677,1678,1679,1680", "answer": "1681"}
{"prompt": "31291", "answer": "31292"}
{"prompt": "43303,43304,43305,43306,43307,43308", "answer": "43309"}
{"prompt": "3680,3681", "answer": "3682"}
{"prompt": "25865,25866,25867", "answer": "25868"}
{"prompt": "24649,24650,24651,24652,24653,24654,24655,24656,24657", "answer": "24658"}
{"prompt": "16225,16226,16227,16228,16229,16230,16231,16232,16233", "answer": "16234"}
{"prompt": "44132,44133,44134,44135,44136,44137,44138", "answer": "44139"}
{"prompt": "35924,35925,35926,35927,35928,35929,35930,35931,35932,35933", "answer": "35934"}
{"prompt": "3082,3083,3084,3085,3086,3087", "answer": "3088"}
{"prompt": "242,243", "answer": "244"}
{"prompt": "3214,3215,3216,3217,3218,3219,3220", "answer": "3221"}
{"prompt": "8044,8045,8046,8047,8048,8049,8050,8051,8052", "answer": "8053"}
{"prompt": "7015,7016,7017,7018,7019,7020", "answer": "7021"}
{"prompt": "11579,11580", "answer": "11581"}
{"prompt": "26768,26769,26770,26771,26772,26773,26774,26775,26776", "answer": "26777"}
{"prompt": "4965,4966,4967,4968,4969", "answer": "4970"}
{"prompt": "23139,23140,23141,23142,23143,23144,23145", "answer": "23146"}
{"prompt": "15161,15162", "answer": "15163"}
{"prompt": "17044,17045,17046,17047,17048,17049,17050,17051,17052", "answer": "17053"}
{"prompt": "32835,32836,32837,32838,32839,32840,32841,32842,32843", "answer": "32844"}
{"prompt": "1277,1278,1279,1280", "answer": "1281"}
{"prompt": "32163,32164,32165,32166,32167,32168,32169,32170", "answer": "32171"}
{"prompt": "23604,23605,23606,23607,23608,23609,23610,23611,23612,23613", "answer": "23614"}
{"prompt": "756,757,758,759,760,761,762,763,764", "answer": "765"}
{"prompt": "37676,37677,37678,37679,37680,37681,37682", "answer": "37683"}
{"prompt": "36504,36505", "answer": "36506"}
{"prompt": "139,140,141,142,143,144,145", "answer": "146"}
{"prompt": "6711,6712,6713,6714,6715,6716", "answer": "6717"}
{"prompt": "18337,18338,18339,18340,18341,18342,18343", "answer": "18344"}
{"prompt": "38604,38605,38606,38607,38608,38609,38610,38611,38612", "answer": "38613"}
{"prompt": "1674,1675,1676", "answer": "1677"}
{"prompt": "19580,19581,19582", "answer": "19583"}
{"prompt": "16141,16142,16143,16144,16145,16146,16147,16148,16149,16150", "answer": "16151"}
{"prompt": "44302,44303,44304,44305,44306", "answer": "44307"}
{"prompt": "830,831", "answer": "832"}
{"prompt": "14910,14911,14912,14913,14914,14915,14916", "answer": "14917"}
{"prompt": "14288,14289,14290,14291,14292,14293,14294,14295,14296", "answer": "14297"}
{"prompt": "23846,23847,23848", "answer": "23849"}
{"prompt": "21723,21724,21725,21726,21727,21728,21729,21730", "answer": "21731"}
{"prompt": "14540,14541,14542", "answer": "14543"}
{"prompt": "11817,11818,11819,11820,11821,11822,11823", "answer": "11824"}
{"prompt": "16492,16493,16494,16495,16496,16497,16498,16499,16500", "answer": "16501"}
{"prompt": "4748,4749,4750,4751,4752,4753", "answer": "4754"}
{"prompt": "15333", "answer": "15334"}
{"prompt": "32584,32585,32586,32587,32588,32589,32590,32591,32592,32593", "answer": "32594"}
{"prompt": "7122,7123,7124,7125,7126,7127,7128,7129,7130", "answer": "7131"}
{"prompt": "18552,18553", "answer": "18554"}
{"prompt": "21807,21808,21809,21810,21811,21812,21813,21814,21815,21816", "answer": "21817"}
{"prompt": "22193,22194,22195,22196", "answer": "22197"}
{"prompt": "13101,13102,13103,13104,13105,13106,13107", "answer": "13108"}
{"prompt": "44899,44900", "answer": "44901"}
{"prompt": "25736,25737,25738,25739,25740", "answer": "25741"}
{"prompt": "17225,17226,17227,17228,17229,17230,17231,17232", "answer": "17233"}
{"prompt": "34910,34911,34912,34913,34914,34915,34916,34917,34918,34919", "answer": "34920"}
{"prompt": "38567,38568,38569,38570,38571,38572,38573", "answer": "38574"}
{"prompt": "32853,32854", "answer": "32855"}
{"prompt": "33666,33667,33668,33669", "answer": "33670"}
{"prompt": "35788,35789,35790,35791,35792", "answer": "35793"}
{"prompt": "38428", "answer": "38429"}
{"prompt": "45115,45116,45117,45118,45119,45120,45121,45122,45123,45124", "answer": "45125"}
{"prompt": "20540,20541,20542,20543,20544,20545,20546,20547,20548,20549", "answer": "20550"}
{"prompt": "36918,36919,36920,36921", "answer": "36922"}
{"prompt": "681,682,683,684,685,686,687,688", "answer": "689"}
{"prompt": "19436,19437,19438,19439,19440,19441,19442,19443", "answer": "19444"}
{"prompt": "13096,13097,13098,13099,13100", "answer": "13101"}
{"prompt": "14010,14011,14012,14013,14014", "answer": "14015"}
{"prompt": "27765,27766,27767", "answer": "27768"}
{"prompt": "5037,5038,5039,5040,5041,5042,5043,5044", "answer": "5045"}
{"prompt": "22196", "answer": "22197"}
{"prompt": "34285,34286,34287,34288,34289,34290,34291,34292", "answer": "34293"}
{"prompt": "7106,7107,7108,7109,7110,7111,7112,7113,7114,7115", "answer": "7116"}
{"prompt": "30950,30951,30952,30953,30954", "answer": "30955"}
{"prompt": "20549,20550,20551,20552", "answer": "20553"}
{"prompt": "11466,11467,11468,11469,11470,11471,11472", "answer": "11473"}
{"prompt": "34469", "answer": "34470"}
{"prompt": "1779,1780,1781,1782", "answer": "1783"}
{"prompt": "3919,3920,3921,3922", "answer": "3923"}
{"prompt": "1441,1442,1443,1444,1445,1446", "answer": "1447"}
{"prompt": "8116,8117,8118,8119,8120,8121,8122,8123,8124", "answer": "8125"}
{"prompt": "31426,31427,31428,31429", "answer": "31430"}
{"prompt": "42807,42808,42809,42810", "answer": "42811"}
{"prompt": "11998,11999,12000,12001,12002,12003,12004", "answer": "12005"}
{"prompt": "6090,6091", "answer": "6092"}
{"prompt": "29946,29947,29948,29949,29950,29951,29952", "answer": "29953"}
{"prompt": "2301,2302", "answer": "2303"}
{"prompt": "40716,40717,40718,40719,40720,40721,40722", "answer": "40723"}
{"prompt": "43340,43341,43342,43343,43344,43345,43346,43347,43348", "answer": "43349"}
{"prompt": "39453,39454,39455,39456,39457,39458,39459,39460", "answer": "39461"}
{"prompt": "44668,44669,44670,44671,44672,44673,44674,44675,44676,44677", "answer": "44678"}
{"prompt": "16150,16151,16152,16153,16154,16155,16156,16157,16158,16159", "answer": "16160"}
{"prompt": "31030,31031,31032,31033,31034,31035,31036,31037", "answer": "31038"}
{"prompt": "2190,2191,2192,2193,2194", "answer": "2195"}
{"prompt": "45283,45284,45285,45286,45287,45288,45289,45290", "answer": "45291"}
{"prompt": "14862,14863,14864,14865,14866,14867,14868,14869,14870,14871", "answer": "14872"}
{"prompt": "11158,11159,11160", "answer": "11161"}
{"prompt": "35390", "answer": "35391"}
{"prompt": "38076,38077,38078,38079,38080,38081,38082,38083,38084,38085", "answer": "38086"}
{"prompt": "21651", "answer": "21652"}
{"prompt": "26147,26148,26149,26150,26151", "answer": "26152"}
{"prompt": "8306,8307", "answer": "8308"}
{"prompt": "40198,40199,40200,40201,40202,40203,40204,40205,40206", "answer": "40207"}
{"prompt": "20765,20766", "answer": "20767"}
{"prompt": "41600,41601,41602,41603,41604,41605,41606,41607,41608,41609", "answer": "41610"}
{"prompt": "36305,36306,36307,36308,36309,36310,36311,36312,36313,36314", "answer": "36315"}
{"prompt": "22122,22123,22124,22125,22126,22127", "answer": "22128"}
{"prompt": "33790,33791,33792", "answer": "33793"}
{"prompt": "11447,11448,11449,11450,11451,11452,11453,11454,11455", "answer": "11456"}
{"prompt": "25052,25053,25054,25055", "answer": "25056"}
{"prompt": "21356,21357,21358", "answer": "21359"}
{"prompt": "2599", "answer": "2600"}
{"prompt": "15351,15352,15353,15354,15355,15356", "answer": "15357"}
{"prompt": "27160,27161,27162", "answer": "27163"}
{"prompt": "26699,26700,26701,26702,26703,26704,26705,26706,26707,26708", "answer": "26709"}
{"prompt": "14614,14615", "answer": "14616"}
{"prompt": "5388", "answer": "5389"}
{"prompt": "44151,44152,44153,44154,44155,44156,44157,44158", "answer": "44159"}
{"prompt": "24736,24737,24738,24739", "answer": "24740"}
{"prompt": "6144,6145", "answer": "6146"}
{"prompt": "12884", "answer": "12885"}
{"prompt": "29009,29010,29011,29012,29013,29014,29015,29016", "answer": "29017"}
{"prompt": "8772,8773,8774,8775,8776,8777,8778,8779,8780", "answer": "8781"}
{"prompt": "18723,18724,18725,18726,18727,18728,18729", "answer": "18730"}
{"prompt": "15263,15264,15265,15266,15267", "answer": "15268"}
{"prompt": "7132", "answer": "7133"}
{"prompt": "38925,38926", "answer": "38927"}
{"prompt": "6786,6787,6788,6789,6790", "answer": "6791"}
{"prompt": "16316", "answer": "16317"}
{"prompt": "129,130,131,132", "answer": "133"}
{"prompt": "13114,13115,13116", "answer": "13117"}
{"prompt": "43536,43537,43538,43539,43540,43541,43542,43543", "answer": "43544"}
{"prompt": "32659,32660,32661,32662,32663", "answer": "32664"}
{"prompt": "4969,4970,4971,4972,4973,4974,4975,4976", "answer": "4977"}
{"prompt": "44698,44699,44700,44701,44702,44703,44704", "answer": "44705"}
{"prompt": "20091,20092,20093", "answer": "20094"}
{"prompt": "12256,12257,12258", "answer": "12259"}
{"prompt": "43508,43509,43510,43511,43512,43513,43514,43515", "answer": "43516"}
{"prompt": "30295,30296", "answer": "30297"}
{"prompt": "28076", "answer": "28077"}
{"prompt": "18659,18660,18661,18662,18663,18664,18665,18666", "answer": "18667"}
{"prompt": "10046,10047,10048", "answer": "10049"}
{"prompt": "34153,34154", "answer": "34155"}
{"prompt": "7760,7761,7762,7763,7764,7765,7766", "answer": "7767"}
{"prompt": "34814,34815,34816,34817,34818,34819,34820,34821", "answer": "34822"}
{"prompt": "26481,26482,26483,26484,26485,26486,26487", "answer": "26488"}
{"prompt": "18945,18946,18947,18948,18949", "answer": "18950"}
{"prompt": "28057,28058", "answer": "28059"}
{"prompt": "37589,37590,37591,37592,37593,37594,37595,37596", "answer": "37597"}
{"prompt": "42345,42346,42347,42348,42349,42350", "answer": "42351"}
{"prompt": "23107", "answer": "23108"}
{"prompt": "24573,24574,24575,24576,24577,24578,24579,24580,24581", "answer": "24582"}
{"prompt": "11998", "answer": "11999"}
{"prompt": "28605,28606,28607,28608,28609,28610,28611,28612,28613,28614", "answer": "28615"}
{"prompt": "8348,8349,8350,8351,8352", "answer": "8353"}
{"prompt": "2012,2013,2014,2015,2016,2017,2018,2019,2020", "answer": "2021"}
{"prompt": "26672,26673,26674", "answer": "26675"}
{"prompt": "39640,39641,39642,39643,39644,39645,39646,39647", "answer": "39648"}
{"prompt": "26863,26864,26865,26866,26867,26868,26869", "answer": "26870"}
{"prompt": "2734,2735,2736,2737,2738,2739,2740,2741,2742", "answer": "2743"}
{"prompt": "16918,16919,16920,16921", "answer": "16922"}
{"prompt": "8190,8191,8192,8193,8194,8195,8196,8197,8198", "answer": "8199"}
{"prompt": "11134,11135,11136", "answer": "11137"}
{"prompt": "15175", "answer": "15176"}
{"prompt": "32159,32160,32161,32162", "answer": "32163"}
{"prompt": "28878,28879", "answer": "28880"}
{"prompt": "29756,29757,29758,29759,29760,29761,29762,29763,29764,29765", "answer": "29766"}
{"prompt": "15748,15749,15750,15751,15752,15753,15754,15755,15756,15757", "answer": "15758"}
{"prompt": "22735,22736,22737,22738,22739", "answer": "22740"}
{"prompt": "37619,37620,37621,37622,37623,37624", "answer": "37625"}
{"prompt": "30886,30887,30888,30889,30890,30891,30892,30893,30894", "answer": "30895"}
{"prompt": "39314,39315,39316,39317,39318,39319", "answer": "39320"}
{"prompt": "31213,31214,31215,31216,31217,31218,31219", "answer": "31220"}
{"prompt": "17032,17033,17034,17035", "answer": "17036"}
{"prompt": "26714", "answer": "26715"}
{"prompt": "5778,5779,5780,5781,5782,5783", "answer": "5784"}
{"prompt": "5456,5457,5458,5459", "answer": "5460"}
{"prompt": "42482,42483,42484,42485,42486,42487,42488,42489", "answer": "42490"}
{"prompt": "34308,34309,34310,34311,34312", "answer": "34313"}
{"prompt": "41153,41154,41155,41156,41157,41158,41159,41160,41161,41162", "answer": "41163"}
{"prompt": "17884,17885,17886,17887,17888,17889,17890,17891,17892", "answer": "17893"}
{"prompt": "26131,26132,26133,26134,26135,26136,26137,26138", "answer": "26139"}
{"prompt": "25596,25597,25598", "answer": "25599"}
{"prompt": "12550,12551,12552,12553,12554,12555,12556", "answer": "12557"}
{"prompt": "5001,5002", "answer": "5003"}
{"prompt": "13321,13322,13323,13324,13325,13326,13327,13328,13329,13330", "answer": "13331"}
{"prompt": "31683,31684,31685,31686,31687,31688,31689,31690,31691", "answer": "31692"}
{"prompt": "38555,38556,38557,38558,38559,38560", "answer": "38561"}
{"prompt": "14260,14261,14262", "answer": "14263"}
{"prompt": "15486,15487,15488,15489,15490,15491,15492", "answer": "15493"}
{"prompt": "41692,41693", "answer": "41694"}
{"prompt": "24487,24488,24489,24490,24491,24492,24493,24494", "answer": "24495"}
{"prompt": "25767,25768,25769,25770", "answer": "25771"}
{"prompt": "7154,7155,7156", "answer": "7157"}
{"prompt": "25994,25995,25996,25997", "answer": "25998"}
{"prompt": "1730,1731,1732", "answer": "1733"}
{"prompt": "35688,35689,35690,35691,35692", "answer": "35693"}
{"prompt": "14562,14563,14564,14565", "answer": "14566"}
{"prompt": "5469,5470,5471,5472,5473,5474,5475", "answer": "5476"}
{"prompt": "4903,4904,4905", "answer": "4906"}
{"prompt": "15083,15084,15085,15086,15087,15088,15089,15090,15091", "answer": "15092"}
{"prompt": "11841,11842,11843,11844,11845,11846,11847,11848,11849", "answer": "11850"}
{"prompt": "2476,2477,2478,2479,2480", "answer": "2481"}
{"prompt": "22739,22740,22741,22742,22743", "answer": "22744"}
{"prompt": "12127,12128,12129", "answer": "12130"}
{"prompt": "13492,13493,13494,13495,13496,13497,13498,13499,13500", "answer": "13501"}
{"prompt": "9616,9617,9618,9619", "answer": "9620"}
{"prompt": "41417,41418,41419,41420,41421,41422", "answer": "41423"}
{"prompt": "20865,20866,20867,20868", "answer": "20869"}
{"prompt": "10260,10261,10262,10263,10264", "answer": "10265"}
{"prompt": "1840,1841,1842,1843,1844,1845,1846", "answer": "1847"}
{"prompt": "1763,1764,1765,1766,1767,1768,1769", "answer": "1770"}
{"prompt": "31807,31808,31809,31810,31811", "answer": "31812"}
{"prompt": "21818,21819,21820,21821,21822,21823,21824,21825,21826", "answer": "21827"}
{"prompt": "18446,18447,18448,18449,18450,18451,18452,18453,18454", "answer": "18455"}
{"prompt": "16687,16688,16689,16690,16691,16692,16693,16694,16695,16696", "answer": "16697"}
{"prompt": "19114,19115,19116,19117", "answer": "19118"}
{"prompt": "34959,34960,34961,34962,34963,34964,34965", "answer": "34966"}
{"prompt": "26570,26571,26572,26573,26574,26575,26576", "answer": "26577"}
{"prompt": "3435,3436,3437,3438,3439,3440,3441,3442", "answer": "3443"}
{"prompt": "21210,21211,21212", "answer": "21213"}
{"prompt": "23093,23094,23095,23096", "answer": "23097"}
{"prompt": "3112,3113,3114,3115,3116", "answer": "3117"}
{"prompt": "6582,6583", "answer": "6584"}
{"prompt": "17989,17990,17991", "answer": "17992"}
{"prompt": "45223,45224,45225,45226", "answer": "45227"}
{"prompt": "62", "answer": "63"}
{"prompt": "28797,28798,28799,28800,28801,28802,28803", "answer": "28804"}
{"prompt": "18630,18631,18632", "answer": "18633"}
{"prompt": "28465,28466,28467,28468,28469,28470,28471,28472,28473,28474", "answer": "28475"}
{"prompt": "1595,1596,1597", "answer": "1598"}
{"prompt": "43362,43363,43364,43365,43366,43367,43368", "answer": "43369"}
{"prompt": "9794,9795,9796,9797,9798", "answer": "9799"}
{"prompt": "2517,2518", "answer": "2519"}
{"prompt": "4603,4604,4605,4606,4607,4608,4609,4610", "answer": "4611"}
{"prompt": "42767,42768,42769,42770,42771,42772,42773,42774,42775", "answer": "42776"}
{"prompt": "29765,29766,29767", "answer": "29768"}
{"prompt": "34573,34574", "answer": "34575"}
{"prompt": "12884,12885,12886,12887,12888,12889,12890", "answer": "12891"}
{"prompt": "345,346,347,348,349,350", "answer": "351"}
{"prompt": "32663,32664,32665,32666,32667,32668,32669,32670,32671,32672", "answer": "32673"}
{"prompt": "29446,29447,29448,29449,29450,29451", "answer": "29452"}
{"prompt": "35607,35608,35609,35610,35611,35612", "answer": "35613"}
{"prompt": "44205,44206,44207,44208,44209,44210", "answer": "44211"}
{"prompt": "42310,42311,42312,42313,42314,42315,42316,42317,42318,42319", "answer": "42320"}
{"prompt": "39841,39842,39843,39844,39845,39846", "answer": "39847"}
{"prompt": "18822", "answer": "18823"}
{"prompt": "11396", "answer": "11397"}
{"prompt": "36621,36622,36623,36624,36625,36626,36627,36628,36629,36630", "answer": "36631"}
{"prompt": "26590,26591", "answer": "26592"}
{"prompt": "29004,29005,29006,29007,29008,29009", "answer": "29010"}
{"prompt": "8649,8650", "answer": "8651"}
{"prompt": "36415,36416,36417,36418,36419,36420,36421", "answer": "36422"}
{"prompt": "38575,38576,38577,38578,38579", "answer": "38580"}
{"prompt": "24720,24721,24722,24723", "answer": "24724"}
{"prompt": "35104,35105,35106,35107,35108,35109,35110,35111", "answer": "35112"}
{"prompt": "30621,30622,30623,30624,30625,30626,30627,30628,30629,30630", "answer": "30631"}
{"prompt": "3877,3878,3879,3880,3881,3882,3883,3884", "answer": "3885"}
{"prompt": "32137,32138,32139,32140", "answer": "32141"}
{"prompt": "38043,38044,38045,38046,38047,38048,38049,38050", "answer": "38051"}
{"prompt": "19967,19968,19969,19970", "answer": "19971"}
{"prompt": "20170,20171,20172,20173,20174", "answer": "20175"}
{"prompt": "11308,11309,11310", "answer": "11311"}
{"prompt": "31596,31597,31598,31599,31600,31601,31602,31603,31604,31605", "answer": "31606"}
{"prompt": "2924,2925,2926,2927,2928,2929,2930,2931,2932,2933", "answer": "2934"}
{"prompt": "30020,30021,30022,30023,30024,30025", "answer": "30026"}
{"prompt": "8743,8744,8745,8746,8747,8748,8749,8750,8751", "answer": "8752"}
{"prompt": "7291,7292,7293,7294,7295,7296,7297,7298,7299,7300", "answer": "7301"}
{"prompt": "31230,31231,31232,31233,31234,31235,31236", "answer": "31237"}
{"prompt": "6092,6093,6094,6095,6096,6097,6098", "answer": "6099"}
{"prompt": "33559,33560,33561,33562,33563,33564,33565,33566", "answer": "33567"}
{"prompt": "4630,4631,4632,4633,4634,4635,4636", "answer": "4637"}
{"prompt": "37240,37241,37242,37243,37244,37245,37246", "answer": "37247"}
{"prompt": "1644,1645,1646,1647,1648,1649", "answer": "1650"}
{"prompt": "24213,24214,24215,24216,24217", "answer": "24218"}
{"prompt": "2242,2243,2244,2245,2246,2247,2248,2249,2250,2251", "answer": "2252"}
{"prompt": "39350,39351", "answer": "39352"}
{"prompt": "33669,33670,33671,33672,33673,33674,33675,33676", "answer": "33677"}
{"prompt": "20868", "answer": "20869"}
{"prompt": "27184,27185,27186,27187", "answer": "27188"}
{"prompt": "15956", "answer": "15957"}
{"prompt": "12350", "answer": "12351"}
{"prompt": "40727,40728,40729,40730", "answer": "40731"}
{"prompt": "11163", "answer": "11164"}
{"prompt": "8738,8739,8740,8741,8742,8743", "answer": "8744"}
{"prompt": "1389", "answer": "1390"}
{"prompt": "19362,19363,19364", "answer": "19365"}
{"prompt": "38385,38386,38387,38388,38389,38390,38391", "answer": "38392"}
{"prompt": "29386,29387,29388", "answer": "29389"}
{"prompt": "35902,35903,35904,35905", "answer": "35906"}
{"prompt": "13826,13827,13828,13829,13830,13831,13832,13833,13834,13835", "answer": "13836"}
{"prompt": "19217,19218,19219,19220", "answer": "19221"}
{"prompt": "35018", "answer": "35019"}
{"prompt": "2766", "answer": "2767"}
{"prompt": "20093,20094", "answer": "20095"}
{"prompt": "10565,10566,10567,10568,10569,10570,10571,10572,10573,10574", "answer": "10575"}
{"prompt": "25229,25230", "answer": "25231"}
{"prompt": "6218,6219,6220,6221,6222,6223", "answer": "6224"}
{"prompt": "9714,9715,9716,9717,9718,9719", "answer": "9720"}
{"prompt": "10831,10832,10833,10834,10835,10836,10837,10838", "answer": "10839"}
{"prompt": "1083", "answer": "1084"}
{"prompt": "33212,33213,33214", "answer": "33215"}
{"prompt": "3996,3997,3998,3999,4000,4001,4002,4003,4004", "answer": "4005"}
{"prompt": "38950,38951,38952,38953,38954,38955,38956,38957,38958", "answer": "38959"}
{"prompt": "6645,6646,6647,6648,6649,6650,6651", "answer": "6652"}
{"prompt": "38629,38630,38631,38632,38633,38634,38635,38636,38637,38638", "answer": "38639"}
{"prompt": "20225,20226,20227,20228,20229,20230,20231,20232,20233", "answer": "20234"}
{"prompt": "29830,29831,29832,29833,29834", "answer": "29835"}
{"prompt": "17333,17334,17335,17336,17337,17338,17339,17340,17341", "answer": "17342"}
{"prompt": "3014,3015", "answer": "3016"}
{"prompt": "7156", "answer": "7157"}
{"prompt": "23816,23817,23818,23819,23820", "answer": "23821"}
{"prompt": "44660,44661,44662,44663,44664,44665,44666,44667,44668", "answer": "44669"}
{"prompt": "11215,11216,11217,11218,11219,11220", "answer": "11221"}
{"prompt": "23294,23295", "answer": "23296"}
{"prompt": "13659,13660,13661,13662,13663,13664,13665,13666", "answer": "13667"}
{"prompt": "4139,4140", "answer": "4141"}
{"prompt": "8728,8729,8730,8731", "answer": "8732"}
{"prompt": "1298,1299,1300,1301,1302,1303,1304,1305,1306,1307", "answer": "1308"}
{"prompt": "15328,15329,15330,15331,15332,15333", "answer": "15334"}
{"prompt": "44182,44183", "answer": "44184"}
{"prompt": "32540,32541,32542", "answer": "32543"}
{"prompt": "29803,29804,29805,29806,29807,29808,29809,29810,29811,29812", "answer": "29813"}
{"prompt": "12156,12157,12158,12159,12160,12161,12162,12163,12164", "answer": "12165"}
{"prompt": "22140,22141,22142,22143,22144,22145,22146", "answer": "22147"}
{"prompt": "37320,37321,37322", "answer": "37323"}
{"prompt": "6520,6521,6522,6523,6524,6525,6526,6527", "answer": "6528"}
{"prompt": "16806,16807,16808", "answer": "16809"}
{"prompt": "41894,41895,41896,41897,41898,41899,41900,41901,41902", "answer": "41903"}
{"prompt": "37325,37326,37327", "answer": "37328"}
{"prompt": "40887,40888,40889,40890,40891,40892,40893,40894,40895,40896", "answer": "40897"}
{"prompt": "26284,26285,26286,26287,26288,26289,26290", "answer": "26291"}
{"prompt": "23479,23480,23481,23482,23483,23484,23485,23486", "answer": "23487"}
{"prompt": "32483,32484,32485,32486,32487,32488,32489,32490,32491", "answer": "32492"}
{"prompt": "7868,7869,7870,7871,7872", "answer": "7873"}
{"prompt": "26531,26532,26533,26534", "answer": "26535"}
{"prompt": "33422,33423,33424,33425,33426,33427", "answer": "33428"}
{"prompt": "26467,26468,26469,26470,26471,26472,26473", "answer": "26474"}
{"prompt": "27193,27194,27195,27196,27197,27198,27199,27200,27201", "answer": "27202"}
{"prompt": "3672,3673,3674,3675,3676", "answer": "3677"}
{"prompt": "7586,7587,7588,7589,7590,7591,7592,7593", "answer": "7594"}
{"prompt": "40057,40058,40059,40060,40061,40062", "answer": "40063"}
{"prompt": "39756,39757,39758", "answer": "39759"}
{"prompt": "43872,43873,43874", "answer": "43875"}
{"prompt": "14595,14596,14597,14598,14599,14600,14601", "answer": "14602"}
{"prompt": "29177,29178", "answer": "29179"}
{"prompt": "3288", "answer": "3289"}
{"prompt": "34635,34636,34637,34638", "answer": "34639"}
{"prompt": "23568,23569,23570,23571,23572,23573,23574,23575", "answer": "23576"}
{"prompt": "41176,41177", "answer": "41178"}
{"prompt": "29579,29580", "answer": "29581"}
{"prompt": "29347,29348,29349,29350,29351,29352,29353,29354", "answer": "29355"}
{"prompt": "32150,32151,32152,32153", "answer": "32154"}
{"prompt": "35976,35977,35978", "answer": "35979"}
{"prompt": "23424,23425,23426,23427,23428,23429", "answer": "23430"}
{"prompt": "32280,32281,32282,32283,32284,32285,32286,32287", "answer": "32288"}
{"prompt": "41659,41660,41661,41662,41663,41664,41665,41666", "answer": "41667"}
{"prompt": "15985,15986,15987,15988", "answer": "15989"}
{"prompt": "35253,35254,35255,35256,35257,35258,35259,35260,35261,35262", "answer": "35263"}
{"prompt": "13253,13254,13255,13256,13257,13258,13259,13260,13261,13262", "answer": "13263"}
{"prompt": "38784,38785", "answer": "38786"}
{"prompt": "43303", "answer": "43304"}
{"prompt": "10563,10564,10565", "answer": "10566"}
{"prompt": "26102,26103,26104,26105,26106,26107,26108,26109,26110", "answer": "26111"}
{"prompt": "8862,8863,8864,8865,8866,8867,8868,8869,8870", "answer": "8871"}
{"prompt": "12575,12576,12577,12578,12579", "answer": "12580"}
{"prompt": "15399,15400,15401,15402,15403,15404,15405", "answer": "15406"}
{"prompt": "16821", "answer": "16822"}
{"prompt": "27832,27833", "answer": "27834"}
{"prompt": "7907,7908,7909,7910,7911,7912,7913,7914", "answer": "7915"}
{"prompt": "5619,5620,5621,5622,5623,5624,5625,5626,5627,5628", "answer": "5629"}
{"prompt": "33780,33781,33782,33783,33784", "answer": "33785"}
{"prompt": "575,576", "answer": "577"}
{"prompt": "44335,44336,44337,44338,44339,44340,44341,44342", "answer": "44343"}
{"prompt": "26252,26253,26254,26255,26256,26257,26258,26259,26260,26261", "answer": "26262"}
{"prompt": "11564,11565,11566,11567", "answer": "11568"}
{"prompt": "37872,37873,37874,37875,37876,37877,37878,37879,37880", "answer": "37881"}
{"prompt": "630,631,632,633,634,635,636,637,638,639", "answer": "640"}
{"prompt": "30520,30521", "answer": "30522"}
{"prompt": "9530,9531,9532,9533,9534,9535,9536", "answer": "9537"}
{"prompt": "5697,5698,5699", "answer": "5700"}
{"prompt": "24057,24058", "answer": "24059"}
{"prompt": "9028,9029,9030", "answer": "9031"}
{"prompt": "21157,21158,21159,21160,21161,21162,21163,21164,21165,21166", "answer": "21167"}
{"prompt": "26647,26648,26649,26650,26651,26652,26653,26654,26655,26656", "answer": "26657"}
{"prompt": "27052,27053,27054,27055,27056", "answer": "27057"}
{"prompt": "43174,43175,43176,43177,43178,43179,43180", "answer": "43181"}
{"prompt": "28379,28380,28381,28382,28383", "answer": "28384"}
{"prompt": "30325,30326,30327,30328,30329,30330,30331,30332,30333", "answer": "30334"}
{"prompt": "45089,45090,45091,45092,45093", "answer": "45094"}
{"prompt": "16842,16843,16844,16845,16846,16847,16848", "answer": "16849"}
{"prompt": "21650,21651", "answer": "21652"}
{"prompt": "8565,8566,8567,8568,8569", "answer": "8570"}
{"prompt": "7659,7660,7661,7662,7663,7664", "answer": "7665"}
{"prompt": "29260,29261,29262,29263,29264,29265,29266,29267", "answer": "29268"}
{"prompt": "43909,43910,43911,43912,43913,43914,43915,43916,43917", "answer": "43918"}
{"prompt": "40782,40783", "answer": "40784"}
{"prompt": "8991,8992,8993,8994,8995,8996,8997,8998,8999", "answer": "9000"}
{"prompt": "11441,11442,11443,11444,11445,11446,11447", "answer": "11448"}
{"prompt": "36585,36586,36587,36588,36589,36590,36591,36592", "answer": "36593"}
{"prompt": "30130,30131,30132,30133,30134,30135,30136,30137", "answer": "30138"}
{"prompt": "27612,27613,27614,27615,27616,27617,27618,27619,27620", "answer": "27621"}
{"prompt": "35948,35949,35950,35951,35952,35953,35954,35955,35956", "answer": "35957"}
{"prompt": "8282,8283,8284,8285,8286,8287", "answer": "8288"}
{"prompt": "1468,1469,1470,1471,1472,1473,1474,1475,1476", "answer": "1477"}
{"prompt": "33707,33708,33709", "answer": "33710"}
{"prompt": "12434,12435,12436,12437,12438,12439", "answer": "12440"}
{"prompt": "44550,44551,44552,44553,44554", "answer": "44555"}
{"prompt": "30227,30228,30229,30230,30231,30232,30233,30234,30235,30236", "answer": "30237"}
{"prompt": "36955,36956,36957,36958,36959,36960,36961,36962,36963,36964", "answer": "36965"}
{"prompt": "37421,37422,37423", "answer": "37424"}
{"prompt": "44497,44498,44499,44500", "answer": "44501"}
{"prompt": "36736,36737,36738,36739,36740,36741,36742,36743,36744,36745", "answer": "36746"}
{"prompt": "6348,6349", "answer": "6350"}
{"prompt": "21933,21934,21935,21936,21937,21938", "answer": "21939"}
{"prompt": "3362,3363,3364,3365", "answer": "3366"}
{"prompt": "7831,7832,7833,7834", "answer": "7835"}
{"prompt": "31829,31830,31831", "answer": "31832"}
{"prompt": "10457,10458", "answer": "10459"}
{"prompt": "16923,16924,16925,16926,16927,16928,16929,16930", "answer": "16931"}
{"prompt": "33154,33155,33156,33157,33158", "answer": "33159"}
{"prompt": "42175,42176,42177,42178", "answer": "42179"}
{"prompt": "23801,23802,23803,23804,23805,23806,23807,23808,23809", "answer": "23810"}
{"prompt": "25429,25430,25431", "answer": "25432"}
{"prompt": "13929,13930,13931,13932,13933,13934,13935", "answer": "13936"}
{"prompt": "41437,41438,41439,41440", "answer": "41441"}
{"prompt": "40235", "answer": "40236"}
{"prompt": "10187,10188,10189,10190,10191,10192,10193,10194,10195", "answer": "10196"}
{"prompt": "30159,30160,30161,30162,30163,30164,30165,30166,30167,30168", "answer": "30169"}
{"prompt": "8666,8667", "answer": "8668"}
{"prompt": "22946,22947,22948,22949,22950,22951,22952,22953", "answer": "22954"}
{"prompt": "31131,31132,31133", "answer": "31134"}
{"prompt": "15011,15012,15013", "answer": "15014"}
{"prompt": "32720,32721", "answer": "32722"}
{"prompt": "32977,32978,32979", "answer": "32980"}
{"prompt": "11812,11813,11814,11815,11816,11817", "answer": "11818"}
{"prompt": "53,54,55,56,57,58,59,60,61,62", "answer": "63"}
{"prompt": "44063,44064,44065,44066", "answer": "44067"}
{"prompt": "44077,44078,44079", "answer": "44080"}
{"prompt": "21955,21956,21957,21958,21959,21960,21961,21962,21963,21964", "answer": "21965"}
{"prompt": "26851,26852,26853,26854,26855", "answer": "26856"}
{"prompt": "885,886", "answer": "887"}
{"prompt": "37054", "answer": "37055"}
{"prompt": "23445", "answer": "23446"}
{"prompt": "42160,42161,42162", "answer": "42163"}
{"prompt": "16344,16345,16346,16347,16348,16349,16350,16351,16352", "answer": "16353"}
{"prompt": "20421,20422,20423,20424,20425,20426,20427,20428,20429", "answer": "20430"}
{"prompt": "5550,5551,5552,5553", "answer": "5554"}
{"prompt": "34410,34411,34412,34413,34414,34415,34416,34417,34418,34419", "answer": "34420"}
{"prompt": "26020,26021,26022,26023,26024,26025,26026,26027", "answer": "26028"}
{"prompt": "1461,1462,1463,1464,1465,1466,1467,1468", "answer": "1469"}
{"prompt": "37674,37675,37676", "answer": "37677"}
{"prompt": "25269,25270,25271,25272", "answer": "25273"}
{"prompt": "19680,19681,19682,19683,19684,19685,19686,19687,19688,19689", "answer": "19690"}
{"prompt": "15450,15451,15452,15453,15454,15455,15456,15457,15458,15459", "answer": "15460"}
{"prompt": "38435,38436,38437,38438,38439,38440,38441", "answer": "38442"}
{"prompt": "7880,7881,7882,7883", "answer": "7884"}
{"prompt": "39711,39712,39713,39714,39715,39716,39717,39718", "answer": "39719"}
{"prompt": "24723,24724,24725,24726,24727,24728,24729,24730,24731", "answer": "24732"}
{"prompt": "22617,22618,22619,22620,22621", "answer": "22622"}
{"prompt": "36711,36712,36713,36714,36715,36716,36717", "answer": "36718"}
{"prompt": "3634,3635", "answer": "3636"}
{"prompt": "42353", "answer": "42354"}
{"prompt": "33727,33728", "answer": "33729"}
{"prompt": "30694,30695,30696,30697,30698,30699,30700", "answer": "30701"}
{"prompt": "8161,8162,8163,8164", "answer": "8165"}
{"prompt": "16662,16663,16664,16665,16666,16667,16668,16669,16670", "answer": "16671"}
{"prompt": "32568,32569,32570,32571,32572,32573,32574,32575", "answer": "32576"}
{"prompt": "35539,35540,35541,35542,35543,35544,35545,35546", "answer": "35547"}
{"prompt": "32295,32296,32297,32298,32299,32300", "answer": "32301"}
{"prompt": "3406,3407,3408,3409,3410,3411", "answer": "3412"}
{"prompt": "20467,20468,20469,20470,20471,20472,20473", "answer": "20474"}
{"prompt": "35971,35972,35973", "answer": "35974"}
{"prompt": "243,244,245,246,247,248,249", "answer": "250"}
{"prompt": "33445,33446", "answer": "33447"}
{"prompt": "4366,4367,4368,4369,4370,4371,4372,4373,4374", "answer": "4375"}
{"prompt": "44395", "answer": "44396"}
{"prompt": "15070,15071,15072,15073,15074,15075,15076", "answer": "15077"}
{"prompt": "3966,3967", "answer": "3968"}
{"prompt": "44318,44319,44320,44321,44322,44323,44324,44325,44326,44327", "answer": "44328"}
{"prompt": "24367,24368", "answer": "24369"}
{"prompt": "30529,30530,30531", "answer": "30532"}
{"prompt": "18792,18793,18794,18795,18796,18797,18798", "answer": "18799"}
{"prompt": "12389,12390,12391,12392,12393,12394,12395,12396,12397,12398", "answer": "12399"}
{"prompt": "34839,34840,34841,34842,34843,34844,34845", "answer": "34846"}
{"prompt": "15064,15065,15066,15067,15068,15069,15070", "answer": "15071"}
{"prompt": "27537,27538,27539,27540,27541,27542,27543", "answer": "27544"}
{"prompt": "580,581,582,583,584,585,586", "answer": "587"}
{"prompt": "15273,15274,15275,15276,15277,15278,15279", "answer": "15280"}
{"prompt": "24770,24771,24772,24773,24774,24775,24776", "answer": "24777"}
{"prompt": "8793,8794,8795,8796,8797", "answer": "8798"}
{"prompt": "27495,27496,27497,27498,27499,27500,27501,27502", "answer": "27503"}
{"prompt": "10467,10468,10469,10470,10471,10472,10473,10474", "answer": "10475"}
{"prompt": "29573,29574,29575,29576,29577,29578,29579", "answer": "29580"}
{"prompt": "2162,2163,2164,2165,2166,2167,2168,2169", "answer": "2170"}
{"prompt": "38774,38775,38776", "answer": "38777"}
{"prompt": "32972,32973,32974,32975,32976", "answer": "32977"}
{"prompt": "9458,9459,9460,9461,9462,9463,9464", "answer": "9465"}
{"prompt": "27244,27245", "answer": "27246"}
{"prompt": "43578,43579,43580", "answer": "43581"}
{"prompt": "39846,39847,39848,39849,39850,39851,39852,39853,39854,39855", "answer": "39856"}
{"prompt": "25778,25779,25780,25781,25782,25783,25784", "answer": "25785"}
{"prompt": "17789,17790,17791,17792,17793,17794", "answer": "17795"}
{"prompt": "18280,18281,18282,18283,18284", "answer": "18285"}
{"prompt": "45007,45008,45009", "answer": "45010"}
{"prompt": "43444,43445,43446,43447,43448", "answer": "43449"}
{"prompt": "29501,29502,29503,29504,29505", "answer": "29506"}
{"prompt": "10726,10727,10728,10729,10730,10731", "answer": "10732"}
{"prompt": "32988,32989,32990,32991", "answer": "32992"}
{"prompt": "12423,12424,12425", "answer": "12426"}
{"prompt": "23117,23118", "answer": "23119"}
{"prompt": "27543,27544,27545,27546,27547,27548,27549,27550,27551,27552", "answer": "27553"}
{"prompt": "39169,39170,39171,39172,39173,39174,39175,39176,39177", "answer": "39178"}
{"prompt": "28474,28475,28476,28477", "answer": "28478"}
{"prompt": "9922,9923,9924,9925,9926,9927,9928,9929,9930,9931", "answer": "9932"}
{"prompt": "7524,7525,7526,7527,7528,7529,7530,7531,7532,7533", "answer": "7534"}
{"prompt": "39446,39447,39448,39449,39450,39451", "answer": "39452"}
{"prompt": "34303,34304,34305,34306,34307,34308", "answer": "34309"}
{"prompt": "6088,6089", "answer": "6090"}
{"prompt": "5057,5058,5059,5060,5061,5062,5063,5064", "answer": "5065"}
{"prompt": "8964,8965,8966,8967,8968,8969,8970,8971,8972", "answer": "8973"}
{"prompt": "8076,8077,8078,8079,8080", "answer": "8081"}
{"prompt": "27930,27931,27932,27933,27934", "answer": "27935"}
{"prompt": "4169,4170,4171", "answer": "4172"}
{"prompt": "4540,4541,4542,4543,4544,4545,4546,4547", "answer": "4548"}
{"prompt": "13135,13136,13137,13138,13139,13140,13141", "answer": "13142"}
{"prompt": "30768,30769,30770,30771,30772", "answer": "30773"}
{"prompt": "15659,15660,15661,15662", "answer": "15663"}
{"prompt": "40299,40300,40301,40302,40303,40304,40305,40306", "answer": "40307"}
{"prompt": "4808,4809,4810,4811,4812,4813,4814,4815,4816,4817", "answer": "4818"}
{"prompt": "38763,38764,38765,38766,38767", "answer": "38768"}
{"prompt": "13456,13457,13458,13459,13460,13461,13462,13463", "answer": "13464"}
{"prompt": "42414,42415,42416,42417,42418,42419,42420", "answer": "42421"}
{"prompt": "21616,21617,21618", "answer": "21619"}
{"prompt": "29060,29061,29062,29063,29064", "answer": "29065"}
{"prompt": "32970,32971,32972", "answer": "32973"}
{"prompt": "27595,27596,27597,27598,27599,27600,27601,27602", "answer": "27603"}
{"prompt": "33773,33774", "answer": "33775"}
{"prompt": "8686,8687,8688,8689,8690,8691,8692,8693,8694", "answer": "8695"}
{"prompt": "10600,10601,10602,10603,10604,10605,10606", "answer": "10607"}
{"prompt": "45180,45181,45182,45183,45184,45185,45186", "answer": "45187"}
{"prompt": "15279,15280,15281,15282,15283", "answer": "15284"}
{"prompt": "32649", "answer": "32650"}
{"prompt": "25667,25668,25669,25670,25671,25672", "answer": "25673"}
{"prompt": "32799,32800,32801,32802,32803,32804,32805,32806", "answer": "32807"}
{"prompt": "24341,24342,24343,24344,24345,24346,24347,24348", "answer": "24349"}
{"prompt": "27505,27506,27507,27508,27509,27510,27511", "answer": "27512"}
{"prompt": "21755,21756,21757,21758,21759", "answer": "21760"}
{"prompt": "33589,33590,33591,33592,33593,33594,33595,33596,33597", "answer": "33598"}
{"prompt": "7931", "answer": "7932"}
{"prompt": "30552,30553", "answer": "30554"}
{"prompt": "25161,25162,25163,25164,25165", "answer": "25166"}
{"prompt": "31376,31377,31378", "answer": "31379"}
{"prompt": "29281,29282,29283,29284,29285", "answer": "29286"}
{"prompt": "44036,44037,44038,44039", "answer": "44040"}
{"prompt": "18975,18976", "answer": "18977"}
{"prompt": "12113", "answer": "12114"}
{"prompt": "13039,13040", "answer": "13041"}
{"prompt": "31937,31938,31939,31940,31941,31942,31943,31944,31945,31946", "answer": "31947"}
{"prompt": "16588,16589", "answer": "16590"}
{"prompt": "37860,37861,37862,37863", "answer": "37864"}
{"prompt": "7341,7342,7343,7344,7345,7346,7347", "answer": "7348"}
{"prompt": "34402", "answer": "34403"}
{"prompt": "31511,31512,31513,31514", "answer": "31515"}
{"prompt": "1644", "answer": "1645"}
{"prompt": "12221,12222", "answer": "12223"}
{"prompt": "16895,16896,16897,16898,16899,16900,16901", "answer": "16902"}
{"prompt": "23919,23920,23921,23922", "answer": "23923"}
{"prompt": "25184,25185,25186,25187,25188,25189,25190,25191,25192,25193", "answer": "25194"}
{"prompt": "8164", "answer": "8165"}
{"prompt": "6106,6107,6108,6109,6110,6111,6112,6113,6114", "answer": "6115"}
{"prompt": "24776,24777,24778,24779,24780,24781,24782", "answer": "24783"}
{"prompt": "42527,42528,42529,42530", "answer": "42531"}
{"prompt": "15529", "answer": "15530"}
{"prompt": "44346,44347,44348,44349", "answer": "44350"}
{"prompt": "24862,24863,24864,24865,24866,24867,24868,24869,24870,24871", "answer": "24872"}
{"prompt": "43843,43844", "answer": "43845"}
{"prompt": "9876", "answer": "9877"}
{"prompt": "27878,27879,27880", "answer": "27881"}
{"prompt": "8147,8148,8149", "answer": "8150"}
{"prompt": "2211,2212,2213,2214,2215,2216", "answer": "2217"}
{"prompt": "25220,25221,25222", "answer": "25223"}
{"prompt": "16337,16338,16339,16340,16341,16342,16343,16344", "answer": "16345"}
{"prompt": "42819,42820,42821,42822,42823", "answer": "42824"}
{"prompt": "5296,5297", "answer": "5298"}
{"prompt": "32091,32092,32093,32094,32095,32096,32097,32098,32099,32100", "answer": "32101"}
{"prompt": "6423,6424,6425,6426,6427,6428,6429,6430,6431,6432", "answer": "6433"}
{"prompt": "22503,22504", "answer": "22505"}
{"prompt": "6185,6186,6187,6188,6189,6190,6191,6192,6193,6194", "answer": "6195"}
{"prompt": "28636,28637,28638,28639,28640,28641,28642,28643", "answer": "28644"}
{"prompt": "25039,25040,25041,25042,25043,25044,25045", "answer": "25046"}
{"prompt": "36543,36544,36545,36546,36547,36548,36549,36550,36551", "answer": "36552"}
{"prompt": "26195,26196,26197,26198,26199,26200,26201,26202,26203,26204", "answer": "26205"}
{"prompt": "19737", "answer": "19738"}
{"prompt": "18895,18896,18897", "answer": "18898"}
{"prompt": "41017,41018,41019,41020,41021", "answer": "41022"}
{"prompt": "20285,20286", "answer": "20287"}
{"prompt": "35027,35028,35029", "answer": "35030"}
{"prompt": "22683,22684", "answer": "22685"}
{"prompt": "19179,19180,19181,19182", "answer": "19183"}
{"prompt": "19543,19544,19545,19546,19547,19548,19549,19550", "answer": "19551"}
{"prompt": "12129,12130", "answer": "12131"}
{"prompt": "21382,21383,21384,21385,21386,21387,21388,21389,21390", "answer": "21391"}
{"prompt": "27098,27099,27100,27101", "answer": "27102"}
{"prompt": "19465,19466,19467,19468,19469", "answer": "19470"}
{"prompt": "3556,3557,3558,3559,3560", "answer": "3561"}
{"prompt": "20571,20572,20573", "answer": "20574"}
{"prompt": "41488,41489,41490,41491,41492,41493,41494,41495", "answer": "41496"}
{"prompt": "27209,27210,27211", "answer": "27212"}
{"prompt": "45315,45316,45317,45318,45319", "answer": "45320"}
{"prompt": "36050", "answer": "36051"}
{"prompt": "33571,33572,33573,33574,33575,33576,33577,33578,33579,33580", "answer": "33581"}
{"prompt": "24046,24047,24048,24049,24050", "answer": "24051"}
{"prompt": "19763,19764,19765,19766,19767,19768,19769,19770,19771,19772", "answer": "19773"}
{"prompt": "5454,5455", "answer": "5456"}
{"prompt": "22118,22119,22120", "answer": "22121"}
{"prompt": "39926,39927,39928,39929", "answer": "39930"}
{"prompt": "19516,19517,19518,19519,19520,19521,19522,19523,19524", "answer": "19525"}
{"prompt": "28355,28356,28357,28358,28359", "answer": "28360"}
{"prompt": "24936", "answer": "24937"}
{"prompt": "946,947,948,949", "answer": "950"}
{"prompt": "27140,27141,27142,27143,27144,27145", "answer": "27146"}
{"prompt": "36674,36675,36676,36677,36678,36679,36680,36681", "answer": "36682"}
{"prompt": "38973,38974,38975,38976,38977,38978", "answer": "38979"}
{"prompt": "23021,23022,23023,23024,23025", "answer": "23026"}
{"prompt": "40216,40217,40218,40219,40220,40221,40222,40223,40224", "answer": "40225"}
{"prompt": "25546,25547,25548,25549,25550,25551,25552,25553,25554", "answer": "25555"}
{"prompt": "7744,7745,7746,7747,7748,7749,7750,7751,7752", "answer": "7753"}
{"prompt": "21135,21136,21137,21138,21139,21140", "answer": "21141"}
{"prompt": "44987,44988,44989,44990,44991", "answer": "44992"}
{"prompt": "34525,34526,34527,34528,34529,34530,34531,34532,34533,34534", "answer": "34535"}
{"prompt": "19182,19183", "answer": "19184"}
{"prompt": "32999", "answer": "33000"}
{"prompt": "44197,44198,44199,44200,44201,44202,44203", "answer": "44204"}
{"prompt": "7419,7420,7421,7422,7423", "answer": "7424"}
{"prompt": "17853,17854,17855,17856,17857,17858,17859,17860,17861", "answer": "17862"}
{"prompt": "28968", "answer": "28969"}
{"prompt": "8157", "answer": "8158"}
{"prompt": "31288,31289,31290,31291", "answer": "31292"}
{"prompt": "18355,18356,18357,18358,18359,18360,18361,18362,18363,18364", "answer": "18365"}
{"prompt": "2569,2570,2571,2572,2573,2574,2575", "answer": "2576"}
{"prompt": "4518,4519,4520,4521,4522", "answer": "4523"}
{"prompt": "36921,36922,36923,36924,36925", "answer": "36926"}
{"prompt": "5604,5605,5606,5607", "answer": "5608"}
{"prompt": "31850,31851,31852,31853,31854,31855,31856", "answer": "31857"}
{"prompt": "17412,17413,17414,17415,17416,17417,17418,17419,17420,17421", "answer": "17422"}
{"prompt": "2677,2678,2679,2680", "answer": "2681"}
{"prompt": "32782,32783,32784,32785,32786,32787", "answer": "32788"}
{"prompt": "13760,13761,13762,13763,13764,13765,13766,13767,13768,13769", "answer": "13770"}
{"prompt": "17191,17192,17193,17194,17195,17196,17197,17198,17199", "answer": "17200"}
{"prompt": "38257,38258,38259", "answer": "38260"}
{"prompt": "43679,43680", "answer": "43681"}
{"prompt": "5801,5802,5803,5804,5805,5806,5807,5808", "answer": "5809"}
{"prompt": "14162,14163", "answer": "14164"}
{"prompt": "22303,22304,22305,22306,22307,22308,22309,22310", "answer": "22311"}
{"prompt": "42183,42184,42185", "answer": "42186"}
{"prompt": "40404,40405,40406,40407,40408", "answer": "40409"}
{"prompt": "7115,7116,7117,7118,7119,7120,7121,7122", "answer": "7123"}
{"prompt": "28115,28116,28117,28118,28119,28120", "answer": "28121"}
{"prompt": "2035,2036,2037,2038,2039,2040,2041", "answer": "2042"}
{"prompt": "5545", "answer": "5546"}
{"prompt": "6805,6806", "answer": "6807"}
{"prompt": "27402,27403,27404,27405,27406,27407", "answer": "27408"}
{"prompt": "38926,38927,38928", "answer": "38929"}
{"prompt": "44360,44361,44362,44363", "answer": "44364"}
{"prompt": "27439", "answer": "27440"}
{"prompt": "14134,14135,14136,14137,14138", "answer": "14139"}
{"prompt": "9358,9359,9360,9361,9362,9363,9364,9365", "answer": "9366"}
{"prompt": "17119,17120", "answer": "17121"}
{"prompt": "7593,7594,7595,7596,7597,7598,7599,7600", "answer": "7601"}
{"prompt": "37254,37255,37256,37257,37258,37259,37260,37261,37262,37263", "answer": "37264"}
{"prompt": "4678", "answer": "4679"}
{"prompt": "31769,31770", "answer": "31771"}
{"prompt": "34577,34578,34579,34580,34581,34582,34583,34584,34585", "answer": "34586"}
{"prompt": "34075,34076,34077,34078,34079,34080", "answer": "34081"}
{"prompt": "28157,28158,28159", "answer": "28160"}
{"prompt": "32721,32722,32723,32724,32725,32726,32727", "answer": "32728"}
{"prompt": "17909,17910,17911,17912", "answer": "17913"}
{"prompt": "10942,10943", "answer": "10944"}
{"prompt": "37204,37205,37206,37207,37208,37209,37210", "answer": "37211"}
{"prompt": "31797,31798", "answer": "31799"}
{"prompt": "28729", "answer": "28730"}
{"prompt": "43834,43835,43836,43837,43838,43839,43840,43841,43842,43843", "answer": "43844"}
{"prompt": "44469,44470,44471,44472,44473,44474", "answer": "44475"}
{"prompt": "43967,43968", "answer": "43969"}
{"prompt": "34296", "answer": "34297"}
{"prompt": "18461,18462", "answer": "18463"}
{"prompt": "25074,25075,25076,25077", "answer": "25078"}
{"prompt": "24957,24958,24959,24960,24961,24962,24963", "answer": "24964"}
{"prompt": "12229,12230,12231,12232,12233,12234,12235", "answer": "12236"}
{"prompt": "15179,15180,15181,15182,15183,15184,15185", "answer": "15186"}
{"prompt": "1928,1929", "answer": "1930"}
{"prompt": "17632,17633,17634,17635,17636,17637,17638", "answer": "17639"}
{"prompt": "18518,18519,18520,18521,18522,18523,18524,18525", "answer": "18526"}
{"prompt": "10347,10348,10349", "answer": "10350"}
{"prompt": "44349,44350,44351", "answer": "44352"}
{"prompt": "26928,26929,26930,26931,26932,26933,26934,26935,26936", "answer": "26937"}
{"prompt": "22218,22219,22220", "answer": "22221"}
{"prompt": "13028,13029,13030,13031,13032,13033,13034", "answer": "13035"}
{"prompt": "2356,2357,2358,2359,2360,2361,2362,2363,2364", "answer": "2365"}
{"prompt": "24643,24644,24645", "answer": "24646"}
{"prompt": "41239,41240,41241,41242,41243,41244,41245,41246", "answer": "41247"}
{"prompt": "29928", "answer": "29929"}
{"prompt": "18867,18868,18869,18870,18871,18872,18873", "answer": "18874"}
{"prompt": "33918,33919,33920", "answer": "33921"}
{"prompt": "41724,41725,41726", "answer": "41727"}
{"prompt": "36469,36470", "answer": "36471"}
{"prompt": "14542,14543,14544,14545,14546,14547,14548,14549", "answer": "14550"}
{"prompt": "34755,34756,34757,34758", "answer": "34759"}
{"prompt": "10823,10824,10825,10826,10827,10828,10829,10830,10831", "answer": "10832"}
{"prompt": "40739,40740,40741,40742,40743,40744,40745,40746,40747", "answer": "40748"}
{"prompt": "28643,28644,28645", "answer": "28646"}
{"prompt": "30430,30431,30432", "answer": "30433"}
{"prompt": "13165,13166,13167,13168,13169,13170,13171,13172,13173,13174", "answer": "13175"}
{"prompt": "17773,17774,17775,17776", "answer": "17777"}
{"prompt": "11396,11397,11398,11399,11400,11401,11402,11403,11404", "answer": "11405"}
{"prompt": "18083", "answer": "18084"}
{"prompt": "34938,34939,34940,34941,34942,34943", "answer": "34944"}
{"prompt": "15363,15364,15365,15366,15367,15368,15369,15370,15371,15372", "answer": "15373"}
{"prompt": "43935,43936,43937,43938,43939,43940,43941,43942,43943,43944", "answer": "43945"}
{"prompt": "31336,31337,31338,31339,31340,31341,31342", "answer": "31343"}
{"prompt": "20632,20633,20634,20635,20636,20637,20638,20639", "answer": "20640"}
{"prompt": "8575,8576,8577,8578,8579,8580,8581,8582", "answer": "8583"}
{"prompt": "2220,2221,2222,2223,2224", "answer": "2225"}
{"prompt": "25637,25638,25639,25640,25641,25642,25643,25644,25645", "answer": "25646"}
{"prompt": "43881,43882,43883,43884,43885,43886", "answer": "43887"}
{"prompt": "37338,37339,37340", "answer": "37341"}
{"prompt": "39653,39654,39655,39656,39657,39658,39659,39660,39661", "answer": "39662"}
{"prompt": "1180", "answer": "1181"}
{"prompt": "38612,38613,38614,38615", "answer": "38616"}
{"prompt": "3582", "answer": "3583"}
{"prompt": "280,281,282,283,284", "answer": "285"}
{"prompt": "4358,4359,4360,4361,4362,4363,4364,4365,4366", "answer": "4367"}
{"prompt": "27812,27813,27814,27815,27816,27817,27818,27819", "answer": "27820"}
{"prompt": "11163", "answer": "11164"}
{"prompt": "18090,18091,18092", "answer": "18093"}
{"prompt": "25331,25332,25333,25334,25335,25336,25337,25338,25339", "answer": "25340"}
{"prompt": "35823,35824,35825,35826", "answer": "35827"}
{"prompt": "16453,16454,16455,16456,16457,16458,16459,16460,16461,16462", "answer": "16463"}
{"prompt": "24871,24872,24873,24874,24875,24876,24877,24878", "answer": "24879"}
{"prompt": "34800,34801,34802,34803,34804,34805,34806,34807", "answer": "34808"}
{"prompt": "33486", "answer": "33487"}
{"prompt": "30060,30061,30062", "answer": "30063"}
{"prompt": "39414,39415,39416,39417,39418,39419,39420", "answer": "39421"}
{"prompt": "3015,3016,3017,3018,3019,3020,3021,3022,3023,3024", "answer": "3025"}
{"prompt": "24356,24357,24358", "answer": "24359"}
{"prompt": "7637,7638,7639,7640,7641,7642,7643,7644,7645,7646", "answer": "7647"}
{"prompt": "41794,41795,41796,41797,41798,41799,41800", "answer": "41801"}
{"prompt": "3425,3426,3427,3428,3429,3430", "answer": "3431"}
{"prompt": "36127", "answer": "36128"}
{"prompt": "8104,8105,8106,8107,8108,8109", "answer": "8110"}
{"prompt": "28015,28016,28017,28018", "answer": "28019"}
{"prompt": "42117,42118,42119,42120,42121,42122,42123,42124", "answer": "42125"}
{"prompt": "2714,2715,2716", "answer": "2717"}
{"prompt": "43171,43172,43173,43174", "answer": "43175"}
{"prompt": "4744,4745,4746,4747,4748", "answer": "4749"}
{"prompt": "12334,12335,12336,12337,12338,12339,12340,12341,12342,12343", "answer": "12344"}
{"prompt": "1414,1415", "answer": "1416"}
{"prompt": "33816,33817,33818", "answer": "33819"}
{"prompt": "880,881,882,883,884,885", "answer": "886"}
{"prompt": "11484,11485,11486", "answer": "11487"}
{"prompt": "1633,1634", "answer": "1635"}
{"prompt": "24104,24105,24106,24107,24108,24109", "answer": "24110"}
{"prompt": "42069,42070,42071,42072,42073,42074", "answer": "42075"}
{"prompt": "37612,37613,37614,37615", "answer": "37616"}
{"prompt": "35566,35567,35568,35569,35570,35571,35572,35573,35574,35575", "answer": "35576"}
{"prompt": "6747,6748,6749,6750", "answer": "6751"}
{"prompt": "25084,25085,25086,25087,25088,25089,25090", "answer": "25091"}
{"prompt": "33632", "answer": "33633"}
{"prompt": "16056,16057", "answer": "16058"}
{"prompt": "9935", "answer": "9936"}
{"prompt": "33357,33358,33359", "answer": "33360"}
{"prompt": "15172,15173,15174,15175", "answer": "15176"}
{"prompt": "3057,3058,3059,3060,3061,3062", "answer": "3063"}
{"prompt": "39429,39430,39431,39432,39433,39434", "answer": "39435"}
{"prompt": "22009,22010", "answer": "22011"}
{"prompt": "26919,26920,26921,26922,26923,26924,26925,26926,26927,26928", "answer": "26929"}
{"prompt": "30593,30594,30595,30596", "answer": "30597"}
{"prompt": "31487,31488,31489,31490,31491,31492,31493,31494", "answer": "31495"}
{"prompt": "34871,34872,34873,34874", "answer": "34875"}
{"prompt": "45009,45010,45011,45012,45013", "answer": "45014"}
{"prompt": "31589,31590,31591,31592,31593,31594,31595,31596", "answer": "31597"}
{"prompt": "8129,8130,8131", "answer": "8132"}
{"prompt": "14688,14689", "answer": "14690"}
{"prompt": "7879,7880", "answer": "7881"}
{"prompt": "40087,40088,40089,40090,40091,40092,40093", "answer": "40094"}
{"prompt": "24379,24380", "answer": "24381"}
{"prompt": "15387", "answer": "15388"}
{"prompt": "19044,19045,19046,19047,19048,19049,19050,19051,19052,19053", "answer": "19054"}
{"prompt": "24807,24808,24809,24810,24811,24812,24813,24814,24815,24816", "answer": "24817"}
{"prompt": "32593", "answer": "32594"}
{"prompt": "25496,25497,25498,25499,25500,25501,25502,25503,25504,25505", "answer": "25506"}
{"prompt": "38398,38399,38400,38401,38402,38403,38404,38405,38406,38407", "answer": "38408"}
{"prompt": "360,361", "answer": "362"}
{"prompt": "15989,15990,15991,15992,15993,15994,15995,15996", "answer": "15997"}
{"prompt": "29421,29422,29423,29424,29425,29426", "answer": "29427"}
{"prompt": "4514", "answer": "4515"}
{"prompt": "15440,15441,15442,15443,15444,15445", "answer": "15446"}
{"prompt": "13624,13625,13626,13627,13628,13629,13630,13631,13632", "answer": "13633"}
{"prompt": "24929,24930,24931,24932,24933,24934,24935,24936", "answer": "24937"}
{"prompt": "40730,40731,40732,40733,40734,40735,40736,40737,40738,40739", "answer": "40740"}
{"prompt": "35204", "answer": "35205"}
{"prompt": "20286,20287,20288,20289,20290,20291", "answer": "20292"}
{"prompt": "32739,32740,32741,32742,32743,32744,32745,32746,32747,32748", "answer": "32749"}
{"prompt": "28522,28523,28524,28525,28526,28527", "answer": "28528"}
{"prompt": "24170,24171,24172,24173,24174,24175", "answer": "24176"}
{"prompt": "23766,23767,23768,23769,23770,23771,23772,23773,23774,23775", "answer": "23776"}
{"prompt": "37361,37362,37363,37364,37365,37366,37367,37368", "answer": "37369"}
{"prompt": "29480,29481,29482,29483,29484,29485,29486", "answer": "29487"}
{"prompt": "41289,41290,41291,41292,41293,41294,41295,41296", "answer": "41297"}
{"prompt": "40388", "answer": "40389"}
{"prompt": "3049,3050,3051,3052,3053,3054,3055,3056,3057", "answer": "3058"}
{"prompt": "7001,7002,7003,7004,7005,7006,7007,7008", "answer": "7009"}
{"prompt": "32798,32799", "answer": "32800"}
{"prompt": "28305,28306,28307,28308", "answer": "28309"}
{"prompt": "43515,43516,43517,43518,43519,43520,43521,43522", "answer": "43523"}
{"prompt": "3794", "answer": "3795"}
{"prompt": "8209", "answer": "8210"}
{"prompt": "17912,17913,17914,17915,17916,17917,17918,17919", "answer": "17920"}
{"prompt": "40815,40816,40817,40818,40819,40820,40821,40822,40823", "answer": "40824"}
{"prompt": "15804,15805,15806,15807,15808", "answer": "15809"}
{"prompt": "24133,24134,24135,24136,24137,24138,24139,24140,24141,24142", "answer": "24143"}
{"prompt": "39824,39825,39826,39827,39828,39829,39830,39831,39832,39833", "answer": "39834"}
{"prompt": "29471,29472,29473,29474,29475,29476,29477,29478,29479", "answer": "29480"}
{"prompt": "9798,9799,9800,9801,9802,9803,9804,9805", "answer": "9806"}
{"prompt": "28416,28417,28418,28419,28420,28421,28422,28423,28424,28425", "answer": "28426"}
{"prompt": "40761,40762,40763,40764,40765,40766,40767,40768,40769,40770", "answer": "40771"}
{"prompt": "21031", "answer": "21032"}
{"prompt": "5048,5049,5050,5051", "answer": "5052"}
{"prompt": "20181,20182,20183", "answer": "20184"}
{"prompt": "35529,35530,35531,35532,35533,35534,35535", "answer": "35536"}
{"prompt": "34438,34439,34440,34441,34442,34443,34444,34445,34446,34447", "answer": "34448"}
{"prompt": "29952,29953,29954,29955,29956,29957", "answer": "29958"}
{"prompt": "2742", "answer": "2743"}
{"prompt": "16485,16486,16487,16488,16489,16490,16491,16492", "answer": "16493"}
{"prompt": "31746,31747,31748", "answer": "31749"}
{"prompt": "34130,34131,34132,34133,34134,34135", "answer": "34136"}
{"prompt": "25317,25318,25319,25320,25321,25322,25323,25324", "answer": "25325"}
{"prompt": "1760,1761,1762", "answer": "1763"}
{"prompt": "12147,12148,12149,12150,12151,12152,12153,12154,12155,12156", "answer": "12157"}
{"prompt": "12060,12061,12062,12063,12064,12065,12066,12067", "answer": "12068"}
{"prompt": "41939,41940,41941,41942,41943,41944,41945,41946", "answer": "41947"}
{"prompt": "7189,7190,7191,7192,7193,7194,7195,7196,7197,7198", "answer": "7199"}
{"prompt": "23232,23233,23234,23235,23236,23237,23238", "answer": "23239"}
{"prompt": "15792,15793,15794,15795,15796,15797", "answer": "15798"}
{"prompt": "5709,5710,5711,5712,5713", "answer": "5714"}
{"prompt": "24906,24907,24908", "answer": "24909"}
{"prompt": "41316,41317,41318,41319,41320,41321,41322", "answer": "41323"}
{"prompt": "14038,14039,14040,14041,14042,14043,14044,14045,14046,14047", "answer": "14048"}
{"prompt": "5194", "answer": "5195"}
{"prompt": "38677,38678,38679,38680,38681,38682,38683,38684,38685,38686", "answer": "38687"}
{"prompt": "28758,28759,28760,28761,28762,28763", "answer": "28764"}
{"prompt": "27966,27967,27968,27969,27970", "answer": "27971"}
{"prompt": "34402,34403,34404,34405,34406,34407,34408,34409,34410", "answer": "34411"}
{"prompt": "40950,40951,40952,40953,40954,40955,40956,40957", "answer": "40958"}
{"prompt": "4065,4066,4067,4068,4069,4070,4071,4072,4073,4074", "answer": "4075"}
{"prompt": "25165,25166,25167,25168,25169,25170,25171,25172,25173,25174", "answer": "25175"}
{"prompt": "23477,23478,23479", "answer": "23480"}
{"prompt": "15417,15418,15419,15420,15421,15422,15423", "answer": "15424"}
{"prompt": "27945,27946,27947,27948,27949", "answer": "27950"}
{"prompt": "19071,19072,19073,19074,19075,19076,19077,19078,19079", "answer": "19080"}
{"prompt": "5002,5003,5004,5005,5006,5007,5008,5009", "answer": "5010"}
{"prompt": "10689,10690", "answer": "10691"}
{"prompt": "30265,30266", "answer": "30267"}
{"prompt": "18432,18433", "answer": "18434"}
{"prompt": "284,285", "answer": "286"}
{"prompt": "10169,10170,10171,10172,10173", "answer": "10174"}
{"prompt": "3733,3734,3735,3736,3737,3738,3739", "answer": "3740"}
{"prompt": "25787,25788,25789,25790", "answer": "25791"}
{"prompt": "3116,3117,3118,3119,3120,3121,3122,3123,3124,3125", "answer": "3126"}
{"prompt": "4048,4049,4050,4051,4052", "answer": "4053"}
{"prompt": "15946,15947,15948,15949,15950", "answer": "15951"}
{"prompt": "10958,10959,10960,10961,10962,10963,10964,10965", "answer": "10966"}
{"prompt": "40636,40637,40638", "answer": "40639"}
{"prompt": "16828,16829,16830,16831", "answer": "16832"}
{"prompt": "2767,2768,2769,2770,2771,2772,2773", "answer": "2774"}
{"prompt": "4366", "answer": "4367"}
{"prompt": "42433,42434,42435,42436,42437,42438,42439,42440", "answer": "42441"}
{"prompt": "12633,12634,12635,12636,12637,12638,12639", "answer": "12640"}
{"prompt": "16869,16870,16871,16872,16873,16874,16875,16876", "answer": "16877"}
{"prompt": "43479,43480,43481,43482,43483,43484,43485,43486,43487", "answer": "43488"}
{"prompt": "36745,36746,36747,36748", "answer": "36749"}
{"prompt": "18976,18977", "answer": "18978"}
{"prompt": "19533,19534", "answer": "19535"}
{"prompt": "32128,32129,32130,32131", "answer": "32132"}
{"prompt": "5283,5284,5285,5286,5287,5288", "answer": "5289"}
{"prompt": "43261", "answer": "43262"}
{"prompt": "27609,27610,27611,27612", "answer": "27613"}
{"prompt": "1951,1952,1953,1954,1955,1956,1957", "answer": "1958"}
{"prompt": "26804,26805,26806", "answer": "26807"}
{"prompt": "39748,39749,39750,39751,39752,39753,39754,39755,39756", "answer": "39757"}
{"prompt": "41635,41636,41637,41638,41639,41640,41641,41642,41643,41644", "answer": "41645"}
{"prompt": "26252", "answer": "26253"}
{"prompt": "42024,42025,42026,42027,42028,42029,42030,42031", "answer": "42032"}
{"prompt": "40359,40360,40361", "answer": "40362"}
{"prompt": "19243,19244,19245", "answer": "19246"}
{"prompt": "11867,11868,11869,11870,11871,11872,11873", "answer": "11874"}
{"prompt": "4980,4981,4982,4983,4984,4985,4986,4987", "answer": "4988"}
{"prompt": "15977,15978,15979,15980,15981,15982,15983,15984,15985", "answer": "15986"}
{"prompt": "14486,14487,14488,14489,14490,14491", "answer": "14492"}
{"prompt": "26906,26907", "answer": "26908"}
{"prompt": "13100,13101", "answer": "13102"}
{"prompt": "1236", "answer": "1237"}
{"prompt": "722,723", "answer": "724"}
{"prompt": "41679,41680,41681,41682,41683,41684,41685,41686,41687,41688", "answer": "41689"}
{"prompt": "43429,43430,43431,43432,43433,43434,43435,43436,43437", "answer": "43438"}
{"prompt": "32871,32872,32873,32874,32875,32876,32877,32878", "answer": "32879"}
{"prompt": "45171,45172,45173,45174,45175,45176,45177,45178", "answer": "45179"}
{"prompt": "24836,24837,24838,24839,24840,24841,24842", "answer": "24843"}
{"prompt": "24745,24746,24747,24748,24749,24750,24751,24752,24753", "answer": "24754"}
{"prompt": "25748,25749", "answer": "25750"}
{"prompt": "32943,32944", "answer": "32945"}
{"prompt": "8124,8125,8126,8127,8128,8129", "answer": "8130"}
{"prompt": "13856,13857,13858,13859,13860,13861,13862,13863,13864", "answer": "13865"}
{"prompt": "33367,33368,33369,33370,33371,33372,33373,33374,33375", "answer": "33376"}
{"prompt": "26746,26747,26748,26749,26750,26751,26752,26753,26754", "answer": "26755"}
{"prompt": "36370,36371,36372,36373,36374,36375", "answer": "36376"}
{"prompt": "31304,31305", "answer": "31306"}
{"prompt": "18042", "answer": "18043"}
{"prompt": "28629,28630,28631,28632,28633,28634,28635,28636", "answer": "28637"}
{"prompt": "26907,26908,26909,26910,26911,26912", "answer": "26913"}
{"prompt": "25438,25439,25440,25441,25442", "answer": "25443"}
{"prompt": "17957,17958", "answer": "17959"}
{"prompt": "37610,37611,37612", "answer": "37613"}
{"prompt": "34278,34279", "answer": "34280"}
{"prompt": "43783,43784,43785,43786,43787,43788,43789,43790", "answer": "43791"}
{"prompt": "16563,16564,16565,16566,16567,16568", "answer": "16569"}
{"prompt": "13772,13773,13774,13775,13776,13777", "answer": "13778"}
{"prompt": "9204,9205,9206,9207,9208,9209", "answer": "9210"}
{"prompt": "15811,15812", "answer": "15813"}
{"prompt": "3475,3476,3477", "answer": "3478"}
{"prompt": "34536,34537,34538,34539,34540,34541,34542,34543,34544,34545", "answer": "34546"}
{"prompt": "32132,32133,32134,32135,32136,32137", "answer": "32138"}
{"prompt": "29580,29581,29582,29583,29584,29585", "answer": "29586"}
{"prompt": "34670,34671,34672,34673,34674,34675,34676,34677,34678", "answer": "34679"}
{"prompt": "28845,28846,28847,28848,28849,28850", "answer": "28851"}
{"prompt": "2224,2225,2226,2227", "answer": "2228"}
{"prompt": "21401,21402,21403,21404", "answer": "21405"}
{"prompt": "34943,34944,34945,34946,34947,34948,34949,34950", "answer": "34951"}
{"prompt": "40361,40362,40363,40364,40365", "answer": "40366"}
{"prompt": "38832,38833,38834,38835,38836,38837", "answer": "38838"}
{"prompt": "2658,2659,2660,2661,2662,2663,2664,2665,2666,2667", "answer": "2668"}
{"prompt": "14375,14376,14377,14378,14379,14380,14381", "answer": "14382"}
{"prompt": "32780,32781,32782", "answer": "32783"}
{"prompt": "38701,38702,38703", "answer": "38704"}
{"prompt": "10636,10637,10638,10639", "answer": "10640"}
{"prompt": "28952,28953,28954", "answer": "28955"}
{"prompt": "8982,8983,8984,8985,8986,8987,8988,8989,8990,8991", "answer": "8992"}
{"prompt": "38929,38930,38931,38932", "answer": "38933"}
{"prompt": "17882,17883,17884", "answer": "17885"}
{"prompt": "17421,17422,17423", "answer": "17424"}
{"prompt": "9248,9249", "answer": "9250"}
{"prompt": "45109,45110,45111,45112,45113,45114,45115", "answer": "45116"}
{"prompt": "12677", "answer": "12678"}
{"prompt": "41026,41027,41028,41029", "answer": "41030"}
{"prompt": "14267,14268,14269,14270,14271", "answer": "14272"}
{"prompt": "11964,11965,11966,11967,11968,11969,11970,11971,11972", "answer": "11973"}
{"prompt": "5419,5420,5421,5422", "answer": "5423"}
{"prompt": "24183,24184,24185,24186,24187,24188,24189,24190", "answer": "24191"}
{"prompt": "41274,41275,41276,41277,41278,41279,41280,41281,41282", "answer": "41283"}
{"prompt": "24789,24790", "answer": "24791"}
{"prompt": "17919,17920,17921,17922,17923,17924", "answer": "17925"}
{"prompt": "37419,37420,37421", "answer": "37422"}
{"prompt": "3766,3767,3768,3769,3770,3771,3772", "answer": "3773"}
{"prompt": "20610,20611,20612", "answer": "20613"}
{"prompt": "32617,32618,32619,32620,32621,32622", "answer": "32623"}
{"prompt": "43589,43590,43591,43592,43593,43594,43595", "answer": "43596"}
{"prompt": "37670,37671", "answer": "37672"}
{"prompt": "32938,32939,32940,32941,32942,32943", "answer": "32944"}
{"prompt": "28954,28955", "answer": "28956"}
{"prompt": "24567,24568,24569,24570,24571,24572,24573", "answer": "24574"}
{"prompt": "29513,29514,29515,29516,29517,29518,29519,29520", "answer": "29521"}
{"prompt": "32976,32977", "answer": "32978"}
{"prompt": "40880,40881,40882,40883,40884,40885", "answer": "40886"}
{"prompt": "25035", "answer": "25036"}
{"prompt": "32859,32860,32861,32862,32863,32864", "answer": "32865"}
{"prompt": "36329,36330,36331,36332,36333,36334", "answer": "36335"}
{"prompt": "33143,33144,33145,33146,33147,33148,33149,33150,33151,33152", "answer": "33153"}
{"prompt": "22636,22637,22638,22639,22640,22641,22642,22643,22644,22645", "answer": "22646"}
{"prompt": "6207,6208,6209,6210,6211,6212,6213,6214", "answer": "6215"}
{"prompt": "19784,19785,19786,19787,19788,19789,19790,19791,19792", "answer": "19793"}
{"prompt": "43797,43798", "answer": "43799"}
{"prompt": "6450,6451,6452,6453,6454,6455,6456,6457", "answer": "6458"}
{"prompt": "38465,38466,38467,38468,38469,38470,38471,38472,38473,38474", "answer": "38475"}
{"prompt": "36512,36513,36514,36515,36516,36517,36518,36519", "answer": "36520"}
{"prompt": "35627,35628,35629,35630,35631,35632", "answer": "35633"}
{"prompt": "21659", "answer": "21660"}
{"prompt": "5764,5765,5766,5767,5768,5769,5770,5771", "answer": "5772"}
{"prompt": "4207", "answer": "4208"}
{"prompt": "9563,9564,9565,9566,9567,9568,9569,9570,9571,9572", "answer": "9573"}
{"prompt": "44292", "answer": "44293"}
{"prompt": "5366,5367,5368,5369,5370,5371,5372", "answer": "5373"}
{"prompt": "36301,36302,36303,36304,36305", "answer": "36306"}
{"prompt": "4980", "answer": "4981"}
{"prompt": "16262,16263,16264,16265,16266,16267,16268,16269,16270", "answer": "16271"}
{"prompt": "26833,26834,26835", "answer": "26836"}
{"prompt": "22899,22900,22901,22902,22903,22904,22905,22906,22907", "answer": "22908"}
{"prompt": "9636,9637,9638,9639,9640,9641,9642", "answer": "9643"}
{"prompt": "9970,9971,9972,9973,9974,9975,9976,9977,9978", "answer": "9979"}
{"prompt": "6346,6347,6348", "answer": "6349"}
{"prompt": "17133,17134,17135,17136,17137,17138,17139,17140", "answer": "17141"}
{"prompt": "1603,1604,1605,1606,1607,1608,1609,1610", "answer": "1611"}
{"prompt": "19662,19663,19664,19665", "answer": "19666"}
{"prompt": "12662,12663,12664,12665,12666,12667,12668,12669,12670", "answer": "12671"}
{"prompt": "44599,44600,44601,44602,44603,44604,44605,44606", "answer": "44607"}
{"prompt": "27570,27571,27572,27573,27574,27575,27576,27577,27578", "answer": "27579"}
{"prompt": "23745,23746,23747,23748,23749,23750,23751,23752", "answer": "23753"}
{"prompt": "30195,30196,30197,30198,30199", "answer": "30200"}
{"prompt": "23196,23197,23198,23199,23200,23201", "answer": "23202"}
{"prompt": "23700,23701,23702,23703,23704,23705,23706,23707,23708", "answer": "23709"}
{"prompt": "31691,31692,31693", "answer": "31694"}
{"prompt": "9064", "answer": "9065"}
{"prompt": "25466,25467,25468,25469,25470,25471,25472,25473,25474", "answer": "25475"}
{"prompt": "33695,33696,33697,33698,33699,33700,33701", "answer": "33702"}
{"prompt": "26821,26822,26823,26824,26825,26826,26827,26828,26829", "answer": "26830"}
{"prompt": "29451,29452,29453,29454,29455,29456,29457,29458,29459,29460", "answer": "29461"}
{"prompt": "44683,44684,44685", "answer": "44686"}
{"prompt": "10027,10028,10029,10030,10031,10032,10033,10034,10035", "answer": "10036"}
{"prompt": "15830,15831,15832", "answer": "15833"}
{"prompt": "29107,29108,29109,29110,29111,29112,29113,29114,29115", "answer": "29116"}
{"prompt": "15996,15997", "answer": "15998"}
{"prompt": "44079,44080,44081,44082,44083,44084,44085", "answer": "44086"}
{"prompt": "7317,7318,7319", "answer": "7320"}
{"prompt": "5164,5165,5166,5167", "answer": "5168"}
{"prompt": "15616", "answer": "15617"}
{"prompt": "12514,12515,12516,12517,12518,12519", "answer": "12520"}
{"prompt": "13481,13482,13483,13484,13485,13486", "answer": "13487"}
{"prompt": "31055,31056,31057,31058,31059,31060", "answer": "31061"}
{"prompt": "17533,17534,17535,17536,17537,17538,17539,17540,17541,17542", "answer": "17543"}
{"prompt": "43968", "answer": "43969"}
{"prompt": "7772,7773,7774,7775", "answer": "7776"}
{"prompt": "545,546,547,548,549", "answer": "550"}
{"prompt": "35604,35605,35606,35607", "answer": "35608"}
{"prompt": "16000", "answer": "16001"}
{"prompt": "1332,1333,1334,1335,1336,1337,1338,1339,1340", "answer": "1341"}
{"prompt": "32051", "answer": "32052"}
{"prompt": "5340,5341", "answer": "5342"}
{"prompt": "23050,23051,23052,23053", "answer": "23054"}
{"prompt": "15648,15649,15650,15651", "answer": "15652"}
{"prompt": "43731,43732,43733,43734,43735,43736,43737,43738", "answer": "43739"}
{"prompt": "2863,2864", "answer": "2865"}
{"prompt": "32922,32923,32924,32925,32926,32927,32928,32929", "answer": "32930"}
{"prompt": "42751,42752,42753,42754,42755,42756,42757,42758,42759", "answer": "42760"}
{"prompt": "33737,33738,33739,33740,33741,33742,33743,33744", "answer": "33745"}
{"prompt": "8904,8905,8906,8907,8908,8909,8910,8911,8912", "answer": "8913"}
{"prompt": "18753,18754,18755,18756,18757,18758", "answer": "18759"}
{"prompt": "21897", "answer": "21898"}
{"prompt": "25770,25771,25772,25773,25774,25775,25776,25777,25778", "answer": "25779"}
{"prompt": "25184", "answer": "25185"}
{"prompt": "34821,34822,34823,34824,34825,34826,34827,34828,34829", "answer": "34830"}
{"prompt": "6923,6924,6925,6926,6927,6928,6929,6930,6931,6932", "answer": "6933"}
{"prompt": "34545,34546,34547,34548,34549,34550,34551,34552,34553", "answer": "34554"}
{"prompt": "42929,42930,42931,42932,42933,42934,42935,42936,42937", "answer": "42938"}
{"prompt": "20923,20924,20925,20926,20927,20928,20929,20930,20931", "answer": "20932"}
{"prompt": "16568,16569,16570", "answer": "16571"}
{"prompt": "42588,42589,42590,42591,42592,42593,42594,42595,42596", "answer": "42597"}
{"prompt": "14787,14788", "answer": "14789"}
{"prompt": "15772,15773,15774,15775,15776", "answer": "15777"}
{"prompt": "31083,31084,31085,31086,31087,31088", "answer": "31089"}
{"prompt": "4864,4865,4866,4867,4868,4869", "answer": "4870"}
{"prompt": "14626,14627", "answer": "14628"}
{"prompt": "41124,41125,41126,41127,41128,41129,41130,41131,41132", "answer": "41133"}
{"prompt": "11721,11722,11723,11724,11725,11726", "answer": "11727"}
{"prompt": "24371,24372,24373", "answer": "24374"}
{"prompt": "11751,11752,11753,11754,11755,11756", "answer": "11757"}
{"prompt": "21070,21071,21072,21073,21074,21075,21076", "answer": "21077"}
{"prompt": "35130,35131,35132,35133,35134,35135,35136,35137,35138", "answer": "35139"}
{"prompt": "36616,36617,36618,36619,36620,36621", "answer": "36622"}
{"prompt": "1268,1269,1270,1271,1272,1273,1274,1275,1276,1277", "answer": "1278"}
{"prompt": "17149,17150,17151,17152,17153", "answer": "17154"}
{"prompt": "8870,8871,8872,8873,8874,8875", "answer": "8876"}
{"prompt": "38594,38595,38596,38597,38598,38599,38600,38601", "answer": "38602"}
{"prompt": "2630,2631,2632,2633,2634,2635,2636", "answer": "2637"}
{"prompt": "9486", "answer": "9487"}
{"prompt": "45145,45146,45147,45148,45149,45150", "answer": "45151"}
{"prompt": "32247,32248,32249,32250", "answer": "32251"}
{"prompt": "1245,1246,1247", "answer": "1248"}
{"prompt": "20338,20339,20340,20341,20342", "answer": "20343"}
{"prompt": "41210,41211,41212,41213,41214,41215,41216,41217,41218", "answer": "41219"}
{"prompt": "11882,11883,11884,11885,11886,11887", "answer": "11888"}
{"prompt": "10372,10373,10374,10375,10376", "answer": "10377"}
{"prompt": "15563,15564,15565,15566", "answer": "15567"}
{"prompt": "3140,3141,3142,3143,3144,3145,3146,3147", "answer": "3148"}
{"prompt": "1740", "answer": "1741"}
{"prompt": "14587,14588", "answer": "14589"}
{"prompt": "16777,16778", "answer": "16779"}
{"prompt": "33890", "answer": "33891"}
{"prompt": "18966,18967,18968,18969,18970,18971,18972,18973,18974,18975", "answer": "18976"}
{"prompt": "3467,3468,3469,3470,3471,3472,3473,3474,3475", "answer": "3476"}
{"prompt": "40189,40190,40191,40192,40193,40194,40195,40196,40197,40198", "answer": "40199"}
{"prompt": "16063,16064,16065,16066,16067,16068,16069,16070", "answer": "16071"}
{"prompt": "4510,4511,4512,4513,4514", "answer": "4515"}
{"prompt": "14595", "answer": "14596"}
{"prompt": "2480,2481,2482,2483,2484,2485,2486,2487", "answer": "2488"}
{"prompt": "33288,33289,33290,33291,33292,33293", "answer": "33294"}
{"prompt": "43105,43106,43107,43108,43109,43110,43111,43112,43113,43114", "answer": "43115"}
{"prompt": "37532,37533", "answer": "37534"}
{"prompt": "14578,14579,14580,14581,14582,14583", "answer": "14584"}
{"prompt": "15384", "answer": "15385"}
{"prompt": "9805,9806,9807,9808,9809,9810", "answer": "9811"}
{"prompt": "32555,32556,32557,32558,32559,32560,32561,32562", "answer": "32563"}
{"prompt": "27363,27364,27365,27366,27367,27368", "answer": "27369"}
{"prompt": "19815,19816,19817,19818,19819,19820,19821,19822", "answer": "19823"}
{"prompt": "22045,22046,22047,22048,22049,22050", "answer": "22051"}
{"prompt": "6873,6874,6875", "answer": "6876"}
{"prompt": "25896,25897,25898,25899,25900,25901,25902,25903,25904", "answer": "25905"}
{"prompt": "19619,19620,19621,19622", "answer": "19623"}
{"prompt": "38325,38326,38327,38328,38329,38330,38331,38332", "answer": "38333"}
{"prompt": "36656,36657,36658,36659,36660,36661,36662", "answer": "36663"}
{"prompt": "2680,2681,2682,2683,2684", "answer": "2685"}
{"prompt": "21390,21391", "answer": "21392"}
{"prompt": "4290,4291,4292,4293,4294,4295,4296,4297", "answer": "4298"}
{"prompt": "18600,18601,18602,18603", "answer": "18604"}
{"prompt": "10482,10483,10484,10485,10486,10487,10488,10489,10490", "answer": "10491"}
{"prompt": "37725,37726,37727", "answer": "37728"}
{"prompt": "7700,7701,7702,7703,7704,7705,7706,7707,7708", "answer": "7709"}
{"prompt": "34069,34070,34071,34072,34073,34074,34075", "answer": "34076"}
{"prompt": "3411,3412,3413,3414,3415,3416,3417", "answer": "3418"}
{"prompt": "1173,1174,1175,1176,1177", "answer": "1178"}
{"prompt": "8875,8876,8877", "answer": "8878"}
{"prompt": "35546,35547,35548,35549,35550,35551,35552,35553,35554,35555", "answer": "35556"}
{"prompt": "12295", "answer": "12296"}
{"prompt": "13158,13159,13160,13161,13162,13163,13164,13165", "answer": "13166"}
{"prompt": "20200,20201,20202,20203,20204,20205,20206,20207,20208", "answer": "20209"}
{"prompt": "42265,42266,42267,42268", "answer": "42269"}
{"prompt": "3602,3603,3604,3605,3606,3607,3608,3609", "answer": "3610"}
{"prompt": "3446,3447,3448,3449,3450", "answer": "3451"}
{"prompt": "31327,31328,31329,31330,31331,31332", "answer": "31333"}
{"prompt": "44495,44496,44497", "answer": "44498"}
{"prompt": "2933,2934,2935,2936,2937,2938,2939,2940,2941,2942", "answer": "2943"}
{"prompt": "32760,32761,32762,32763,32764,32765,32766,32767,32768", "answer": "32769"}
{"prompt": "26424,26425,26426", "answer": "26427"}
{"prompt": "13390,13391,13392,13393,13394", "answer": "13395"}
{"prompt": "39568,39569,39570,39571,39572,39573", "answer": "39574"}
{"prompt": "9438,9439,9440,9441,9442,9443,9444,9445", "answer": "9446"}
{"prompt": "18774", "answer": "18775"}
{"prompt": "8803,8804,8805,8806,8807,8808,8809,8810", "answer": "8811"}
{"prompt": "36057,36058,36059,36060,36061,36062,36063,36064", "answer": "36065"}
{"prompt": "23145,23146,23147,23148,23149,23150,23151,23152,23153,23154", "answer": "23155"}
{"prompt": "23964", "answer": "23965"}
{"prompt": "13751,13752,13753,13754,13755,13756,13757,13758,13759,13760", "answer": "13761"}
{"prompt": "12942,12943,12944", "answer": "12945"}
{"prompt": "7836,7837,7838,7839,7840,7841,7842,7843,7844", "answer": "7845"}
{"prompt": "31170,31171,31172,31173,31174,31175,31176,31177", "answer": "31178"}
{"prompt": "27288,27289,27290,27291", "answer": "27292"}
{"prompt": "5183,5184,5185,5186,5187", "answer": "5188"}
{"prompt": "588,589,590,591,592,593,594,595", "answer": "596"}
{"prompt": "15320,15321,15322,15323,15324,15325,15326,15327,15328", "answer": "15329"}
{"prompt": "28580,28581,28582,28583,28584,28585", "answer": "28586"}
{"prompt": "32374,32375,32376,32377,32378,32379,32380,32381,32382,32383", "answer": "32384"}
{"prompt": "10212,10213,10214", "answer": "10215"}
{"prompt": "27656,27657,27658,27659", "answer": "27660"}
{"prompt": "22992,22993,22994,22995,22996,22997,22998", "answer": "22999"}
{"prompt": "9816,9817,9818,9819,9820,9821,9822", "answer": "9823"}
{"prompt": "43024,43025,43026", "answer": "43027"}
{"prompt": "42003,42004,42005,42006,42007,42008,42009", "answer": "42010"}
{"prompt": "6790,6791,6792,6793,6794,6795", "answer": "6796"}
{"prompt": "9227,9228,9229,9230,9231,9232", "answer": "9233"}
{"prompt": "8145,8146,8147", "answer": "8148"}
{"prompt": "12985,12986,12987,12988,12989,12990", "answer": "12991"}
{"prompt": "10542", "answer": "10543"}
{"prompt": "35073,35074", "answer": "35075"}
{"prompt": "37222,37223,37224", "answer": "37225"}
{"prompt": "2518,2519,2520", "answer": "2521"}
{"prompt": "32051,32052", "answer": "32053"}
{"prompt": "19807,19808,19809,19810,19811,19812", "answer": "19813"}
{"prompt": "2045,2046,2047,2048,2049,2050,2051,2052,2053", "answer": "2054"}
{"prompt": "8242,8243,8244,8245,8246,8247,8248", "answer": "8249"}
{"prompt": "4215,4216,4217,4218,4219,4220", "answer": "4221"}
{"prompt": "9165,9166,9167,9168,9169,9170,9171", "answer": "9172"}
{"prompt": "18758", "answer": "18759"}
{"prompt": "25482", "answer": "25483"}
{"prompt": "30485,30486,30487,30488,30489", "answer": "30490"}
{"prompt": "24025,24026,24027,24028,24029,24030,24031,24032,24033,24034", "answer": "24035"}
{"prompt": "5608,5609,5610,5611,5612,5613,5614,5615", "answer": "5616"}
{"prompt": "40505", "answer": "40506"}
{"prompt": "6988,6989,6990,6991,6992,6993,6994,6995,6996", "answer": "6997"}
{"prompt": "3232,3233,3234,3235,3236,3237", "answer": "3238"}
{"prompt": "12256", "answer": "12257"}
{"prompt": "33744,33745,33746,33747,33748,33749,33750,33751,33752", "answer": "33753"}
{"prompt": "87,88,89,90", "answer": "91"}
{"prompt": "30025,30026,30027,30028,30029,30030,30031", "answer": "30032"}
{"prompt": "36683,36684,36685,36686,36687", "answer": "36688"}
{"prompt": "31913", "answer": "31914"}
{"prompt": "3649,3650", "answer": "3651"}
{"prompt": "18659", "answer": "18660"}
{"prompt": "14690,14691,14692,14693,14694,14695", "answer": "14696"}
{"prompt": "1920,1921,1922,1923,1924,1925,1926,1927,1928", "answer": "1929"}
{"prompt": "22404,22405,22406,22407", "answer": "22408"}
{"prompt": "32849,32850,32851,32852,32853", "answer": "32854"}
{"prompt": "42241,42242,42243,42244,42245,42246,42247,42248,42249,42250", "answer": "42251"}
{"prompt": "30645,30646,30647,30648,30649,30650,30651", "answer": "30652"}
{"prompt": "30168", "answer": "30169"}
{"prompt": "2945,2946,2947,2948,2949", "answer": "2950"}
{"prompt": "5443", "answer": "5444"}
{"prompt": "35456,35457,35458,35459", "answer": "35460"}
{"prompt": "16589,16590,16591,16592,16593,16594,16595,16596,16597", "answer": "16598"}
{"prompt": "9128,9129,9130,9131,9132,9133,9134,9135", "answer": "9136"}
{"prompt": "9628,9629,9630,9631,9632,9633,9634,9635,9636", "answer": "9637"}
{"prompt": "2072,2073,2074,2075,2076,2077,2078,2079,2080,2081", "answer": "2082"}
{"prompt": "10997", "answer": "10998"}
{"prompt": "24308,24309,24310,24311,24312", "answer": "24313"}
{"prompt": "875", "answer": "876"}
{"prompt": "24979,24980,24981,24982,24983,24984,24985,24986", "answer": "24987"}
{"prompt": "30406,30407,30408,30409,30410,30411", "answer": "30412"}
{"prompt": "7220,7221,7222,7223,7224,7225,7226", "answer": "7227"}
{"prompt": "39539,39540,39541,39542,39543,39544,39545,39546,39547,39548", "answer": "39549"}
{"prompt": "5111,5112,5113,5114,5115", "answer": "5116"}
{"prompt": "18144,18145,18146,18147,18148,18149,18150,18151", "answer": "18152"}
{"prompt": "3324,3325,3326,3327", "answer": "3328"}
{"prompt": "9334,9335,9336", "answer": "9337"}
{"prompt": "1211,1212,1213,1214,1215,1216,1217,1218", "answer": "1219"}
{"prompt": "29646,29647,29648,29649,29650,29651,29652,29653", "answer": "29654"}
{"prompt": "38668,38669,38670,38671,38672,38673,38674,38675", "answer": "38676"}
{"prompt": "28803,28804,28805", "answer": "28806"}
{"prompt": "29003,29004", "answer": "29005"}
{"prompt": "2296,2297,2298,2299", "answer": "2300"}
{"prompt": "34517,34518,34519,34520,34521,34522,34523,34524,34525", "answer": "34526"}
{"prompt": "35336,35337,35338,35339,35340,35341,35342,35343", "answer": "35344"}
{"prompt": "7652,7653,7654,7655,7656,7657,7658,7659", "answer": "7660"}
{"prompt": "11501,11502,11503,11504", "answer": "11505"}
{"prompt": "29544,29545,29546,29547,29548,29549,29550,29551,29552,29553", "answer": "29554"}
{"prompt": "8378,8379,8380", "answer": "8381"}
{"prompt": "27061,27062,27063,27064,27065,27066", "answer": "27067"}
{"prompt": "5718", "answer": "5719"}
{"prompt": "14593,14594,14595", "answer": "14596"}
{"prompt": "599,600,601,602,603,604,605,606,607", "answer": "608"}
{"prompt": "20183,20184,20185", "answer": "20186"}
{"prompt": "11294,11295,11296,11297", "answer": "11298"}
{"prompt": "4458,4459,4460,4461,4462,4463,4464", "answer": "4465"}
{"prompt": "41039,41040,41041,41042,41043", "answer": "41044"}
{"prompt": "7035,7036,7037,7038,7039,7040,7041,7042,7043,7044", "answer": "7045"}
{"prompt": "8443,8444,8445", "answer": "8446"}
{"prompt": "1666,1667,1668", "answer": "1669"}
{"prompt": "11837", "answer": "11838"}
{"prompt": "37922,37923,37924,37925,37926", "answer": "37927"}
{"prompt": "41527", "answer": "41528"}
{"prompt": "45036,45037", "answer": "45038"}
{"prompt": "10214,10215,10216,10217,10218", "answer": "10219"}
{"prompt": "44059,44060", "answer": "44061"}
{"prompt": "41527,41528,41529,41530,41531", "answer": "41532"}
{"prompt": "1545,1546,1547,1548", "answer": "1549"}
{"prompt": "15781,15782,15783,15784,15785,15786,15787", "answer": "15788"}
{"prompt": "688,689", "answer": "690"}
{"prompt": "21430,21431,21432", "answer": "21433"}
{"prompt": "29172,29173,29174,29175", "answer": "29176"}
{"prompt": "23068", "answer": "23069"}
{"prompt": "18780,18781,18782,18783,18784,18785", "answer": "18786"}
{"prompt": "11623,11624,11625,11626,11627,11628,11629,11630,11631,11632", "answer": "11633"}
{"prompt": "11022,11023,11024,11025,11026", "answer": "11027"}
{"prompt": "40306,40307,40308,40309,40310,40311", "answer": "40312"}
{"prompt": "1727,1728,1729,1730", "answer": "1731"}
{"prompt": "10111,10112,10113,10114,10115,10116,10117,10118,10119", "answer": "10120"}
{"prompt": "7132,7133,7134,7135,7136,7137,7138,7139", "answer": "7140"}
{"prompt": "40270,40271,40272,40273,40274,40275,40276,40277,40278,40279", "answer": "40280"}
{"prompt": "44060,44061,44062,44063", "answer": "44064"}
{"prompt": "12977,12978,12979", "answer": "12980"}
{"prompt": "6511,6512,6513,6514,6515,6516,6517,6518,6519,6520", "answer": "6521"}
{"prompt": "5899,5900", "answer": "5901"}
{"prompt": "36017,36018,36019", "answer": "36020"}
{"prompt": "26950,26951,26952,26953,26954,26955,26956,26957", "answer": "26958"}
{"prompt": "9135,9136,9137,9138", "answer": "9139"}
{"prompt": "41781,41782,41783,41784,41785", "answer": "41786"}
{"prompt": "13242,13243,13244", "answer": "13245"}
{"prompt": "29072,29073,29074,29075,29076,29077", "answer": "29078"}
{"prompt": "42961,42962,42963,42964,42965,42966,42967,42968", "answer": "42969"}
{"prompt": "35190,35191,35192,35193,35194,35195,35196,35197", "answer": "35198"}
{"prompt": "8885,8886,8887,8888,8889,8890,8891,8892,8893,8894", "answer": "8895"}
{"prompt": "45150,45151,45152", "answer": "45153"}
{"prompt": "16629,16630,16631,16632,16633", "answer": "16634"}
{"prompt": "37671,37672,37673,37674", "answer": "37675"}
{"prompt": "5628,5629,5630,5631,5632,5633", "answer": "5634"}
{"prompt": "3831,3832,3833", "answer": "3834"}
{"prompt": "35159", "answer": "35160"}
{"prompt": "7214,7215,7216,7217,7218,7219,7220", "answer": "7221"}
{"prompt": "6349,6350,6351,6352,6353,6354,6355,6356,6357", "answer": "6358"}
{"prompt": "16765,16766,16767,16768", "answer": "16769"}
{"prompt": "22799,22800,22801,22802,22803,22804,22805,22806,22807", "answer": "22808"}
{"prompt": "28864,28865,28866,28867,28868,28869,28870,28871,28872", "answer": "28873"}
{"prompt": "42310", "answer": "42311"}
{"prompt": "19121,19122,19123,19124,19125,19126,19127,19128,19129", "answer": "19130"}
{"prompt": "26309", "answer": "26310"}
{"prompt": "44955", "answer": "44956"}
{"prompt": "2108,2109,2110,2111,2112", "answer": "2113"}
{"prompt": "32918,32919,32920,32921,32922", "answer": "32923"}
{"prompt": "38785,38786,38787,38788,38789,38790", "answer": "38791"}
{"prompt": "15376,15377,15378,15379,15380,15381,15382,15383,15384", "answer": "15385"}
{"prompt": "18903,18904,18905,18906", "answer": "18907"}
{"prompt": "29220,29221", "answer": "29222"}
{"prompt": "29500,29501", "answer": "29502"}
{"prompt": "14687,14688", "answer": "14689"}
{"prompt": "2155,2156,2157,2158,2159,2160,2161,2162", "answer": "2163"}
{"prompt": "31116,31117,31118,31119,31120,31121,31122,31123,31124,31125", "answer": "31126"}
{"prompt": "37625,37626,37627,37628,37629,37630,37631,37632,37633", "answer": "37634"}
{"prompt": "265,266,267", "answer": "268"}
{"prompt": "14556,14557,14558,14559,14560,14561,14562", "answer": "14563"}
{"prompt": "28067,28068,28069,28070,28071,28072,28073,28074,28075,28076", "answer": "28077"}
{"prompt": "31356,31357,31358,31359,31360,31361", "answer": "31362"}
{"prompt": "23668,23669,23670,23671,23672,23673,23674,23675,23676,23677", "answer": "23678"}
{"prompt": "10173,10174,10175,10176,10177", "answer": "10178"}
{"prompt": "15573,15574,15575,15576,15577,15578", "answer": "15579"}
{"prompt": "40325", "answer": "40326"}
{"prompt": "7558,7559,7560,7561,7562", "answer": "7563"}
{"prompt": "4467,4468,4469,4470,4471,4472,4473,4474,4475,4476", "answer": "4477"}
{"prompt": "17106,17107,17108", "answer": "17109"}
{"prompt": "13803,13804,13805,13806,13807,13808,13809", "answer": "13810"}
{"prompt": "29994,29995,29996,29997,29998,29999,30000,30001", "answer": "30002"}
{"prompt": "20523,20524,20525,20526,20527,20528,20529,20530,20531,20532", "answer": "20533"}
{"prompt": "25513,25514", "answer": "25515"}
{"prompt": "20384", "answer": "20385"}
{"prompt": "42724", "answer": "42725"}
{"prompt": "34704,34705", "answer": "34706"}
{"prompt": "19827,19828,19829,19830,19831,19832,19833,19834,19835", "answer": "19836"}
{"prompt": "24280,24281,24282,24283,24284,24285", "answer": "24286"}
{"prompt": "28535,28536,28537,28538", "answer": "28539"}
{"prompt": "8423,8424", "answer": "8425"}
{"prompt": "42440,42441,42442,42443,42444,42445,42446,42447,42448", "answer": "42449"}
{"prompt": "22883,22884,22885,22886", "answer": "22887"}
{"prompt": "20977,20978,20979,20980,20981,20982,20983,20984,20985", "answer": "20986"}
{"prompt": "20070,20071,20072,20073,20074,20075,20076,20077,20078", "answer": "20079"}
{"prompt": "23848,23849,23850,23851,23852,23853,23854,23855", "answer": "23856"}
{"prompt": "23225,23226,23227,23228,23229,23230,23231,23232", "answer": "23233"}
{"prompt": "43982,43983", "answer": "43984"}
{"prompt": "31193,31194,31195,31196,31197", "answer": "31198"}
{"prompt": "36717,36718,36719,36720,36721,36722", "answer": "36723"}
{"prompt": "45268,45269,45270", "answer": "45271"}
{"prompt": "28174,28175,28176,28177,28178,28179,28180,28181,28182,28183", "answer": "28184"}
{"prompt": "18934,18935,18936,18937,18938,18939", "answer": "18940"}
{"prompt": "23899,23900,23901,23902,23903,23904,23905,23906,23907,23908", "answer": "23909"}
{"prompt": "23365,23366,23367,23368,23369,23370,23371,23372", "answer": "23373"}
{"prompt": "15632", "answer": "15633"}
{"prompt": "34432,34433,34434,34435,34436", "answer": "34437"}
{"prompt": "18632,18633,18634,18635,18636,18637", "answer": "18638"}
{"prompt": "25317", "answer": "25318"}
{"prompt": "32346,32347,32348,32349", "answer": "32350"}
{"prompt": "43888,43889,43890,43891", "answer": "43892"}
{"prompt": "4176,4177,4178,4179,4180,4181,4182", "answer": "4183"}
{"prompt": "21218,21219,21220,21221,21222,21223,21224,21225,21226", "answer": "21227"}
{"prompt": "12439,12440", "answer": "12441"}
{"prompt": "35411", "answer": "35412"}
{"prompt": "22530,22531,22532,22533,22534,22535,22536", "answer": "22537"}
{"prompt": "37293,37294,37295,37296,37297,37298,37299,37300", "answer": "37301"}
{"prompt": "26369,26370,26371,26372,26373,26374,26375,26376", "answer": "26377"}
{"prompt": "1807,1808,1809,1810,1811,1812,1813", "answer": "1814"}
{"prompt": "9681,9682,9683,9684,9685,9686,9687,9688,9689,9690", "answer": "9691"}
{"prompt": "733,734,735", "answer": "736"}
{"prompt": "10218", "answer": "10219"}
{"prompt": "21737,21738,21739,21740,21741,21742,21743", "answer": "21744"}
{"prompt": "38050,38051,38052", "answer": "38053"}
{"prompt": "7790", "answer": "7791"}
{"prompt": "39765,39766,39767,39768,39769,39770,39771,39772", "answer": "39773"}
{"prompt": "43575,43576,43577,43578", "answer": "43579"}
{"prompt": "33359,33360,33361,33362,33363,33364,33365,33366,33367", "answer": "33368"}
{"prompt": "19414,19415,19416,19417,19418,19419,19420", "answer": "19421"}
{"prompt": "39731,39732,39733,39734,39735,39736,39737,39738", "answer": "39739"}
{"prompt": "35220,35221,35222,35223,35224,35225,35226,35227", "answer": "35228"}
{"prompt": "17724,17725,17726,17727,17728,17729", "answer": "17730"}
{"prompt": "20255,20256,20257,20258,20259,20260", "answer": "20261"}
{"prompt": "10134,10135,10136,10137", "answer": "10138"}
{"prompt": "6330,6331,6332,6333,6334,6335,6336,6337,6338,6339", "answer": "6340"}
{"prompt": "44440,44441,44442,44443", "answer": "44444"}
{"prompt": "2626,2627,2628,2629,2630", "answer": "2631"}
{"prompt": "11710,11711,11712,11713", "answer": "11714"}
{"prompt": "9418,9419,9420,9421,9422", "answer": "9423"}
{"prompt": "39931,39932,39933,39934,39935,39936,39937,39938", "answer": "39939"}
{"prompt": "26720,26721,26722,26723,26724", "answer": "26725"}
{"prompt": "24417,24418,24419,24420,24421,24422,24423,24424,24425,24426", "answer": "24427"}
{"prompt": "20384,20385,20386,20387,20388", "answer": "20389"}
{"prompt": "10119,10120,10121,10122,10123", "answer": "10124"}
{"prompt": "16081,16082,16083,16084,16085,16086,16087", "answer": "16088"}
{"prompt": "8657,8658,8659", "answer": "8660"}
{"prompt": "35434,35435,35436,35437,35438,35439", "answer": "35440"}
{"prompt": "19873,19874", "answer": "19875"}
{"prompt": "24204,24205,24206,24207,24208,24209,24210,24211,24212,24213", "answer": "24214"}
{"prompt": "14601,14602,14603,14604,14605", "answer": "14606"}
{"prompt": "28652,28653,28654", "answer": "28655"}
{"prompt": "27395,27396,27397,27398,27399,27400,27401,27402", "answer": "27403"}
{"prompt": "1536,1537,1538,1539,1540,1541,1542,1543,1544,1545", "answer": "1546"}
{"prompt": "31092,31093,31094,31095,31096", "answer": "31097"}
{"prompt": "35044,35045,35046,35047,35048,35049", "answer": "35050"}
{"prompt": "44351,44352,44353,44354,44355,44356,44357", "answer": "44358"}
{"prompt": "10178,10179,10180,10181,10182,10183,10184,10185,10186,10187", "answer": "10188"}
{"prompt": "25856,25857,25858,25859,25860,25861,25862", "answer": "25863"}
{"prompt": "29910", "answer": "29911"}
{"prompt": "12595,12596,12597,12598,12599,12600", "answer": "12601"}
{"prompt": "15091,15092,15093,15094,15095,15096,15097,15098,15099", "answer": "15100"}
{"prompt": "35006,35007,35008,35009,35010,35011,35012,35013", "answer": "35014"}
{"prompt": "40000,40001,40002,40003,40004,40005,40006", "answer": "40007"}
{"prompt": "23567,23568", "answer": "23569"}
{"prompt": "20239,20240,20241,20242", "answer": "20243"}
{"prompt": "45059,45060", "answer": "45061"}
{"prompt": "38367,38368,38369,38370,38371,38372,38373", "answer": "38374"}
{"prompt": "3174,3175", "answer": "3176"}
{"prompt": "16930,16931", "answer": "16932"}
{"prompt": "19364,19365", "answer": "19366"}
{"prompt": "26812,26813,26814,26815,26816,26817,26818,26819,26820,26821", "answer": "26822"}
{"prompt": "17236,17237,17238,17239,17240,17241,17242,17243", "answer": "17244"}
{"prompt": "2636,2637,2638,2639,2640,2641,2642", "answer": "2643"}
{"prompt": "38247,38248,38249,38250", "answer": "38251"}
{"prompt": "43287,43288,43289,43290,43291,43292,43293,43294,43295", "answer": "43296"}
{"prompt": "36996", "answer": "36997"}
{"prompt": "12326,12327,12328,12329,12330,12331,12332,12333,12334", "answer": "12335"}
{"prompt": "39000,39001,39002,39003,39004,39005,39006,39007", "answer": "39008"}
{"prompt": "2963,2964,2965,2966,2967,2968,2969,2970,2971,2972", "answer": "2973"}
{"prompt": "10222,10223", "answer": "10224"}
{"prompt": "8760,8761,8762,8763,8764,8765", "answer": "8766"}
{"prompt": "8463,8464,8465", "answer": "8466"}
{"prompt": "37888,37889", "answer": "37890"}
{"prompt": "11208,11209,11210,11211,11212,11213,11214,11215", "answer": "11216"}
{"prompt": "26565,26566", "answer": "26567"}
{"prompt": "6740,6741,6742,6743,6744,6745,6746", "answer": "6747"}
{"prompt": "41056,41057,41058,41059,41060,41061", "answer": "41062"}
{"prompt": "23324,23325,23326,23327,23328", "answer": "23329"}
{"prompt": "35204,35205,35206", "answer": "35207"}
{"prompt": "42467,42468,42469,42470,42471,42472,42473,42474,42475", "answer": "42476"}
{"prompt": "15445,15446,15447,15448,15449", "answer": "15450"}
{"prompt": "45325", "answer": "45326"}
{"prompt": "10463,10464,10465,10466,10467", "answer": "10468"}
{"prompt": "41487,41488", "answer": "41489"}
{"prompt": "15217,15218", "answer": "15219"}
{"prompt": "13994,13995,13996,13997,13998,13999,14000,14001,14002,14003", "answer": "14004"}
{"prompt": "12184,12185,12186,12187,12188,12189", "answer": "12190"}
{"prompt": "14,15,16,17,18,19,20,21,22", "answer": "23"}
{"prompt": "29788,29789,29790,29791,29792,29793,29794", "answer": "29795"}
{"prompt": "12895,12896,12897,12898,12899,12900,12901,12902,12903,12904", "answer": "12905"}
{"prompt": "14252,14253,14254,14255,14256,14257,14258,14259,14260", "answer": "14261"}
{"prompt": "15222,15223,15224,15225,15226,15227,15228,15229", "answer": "15230"}
{"prompt": "5051,5052,5053,5054,5055,5056,5057", "answer": "5058"}
{"prompt": "37217,37218,37219,37220,37221,37222", "answer": "37223"}
{"prompt": "23210,23211,23212,23213", "answer": "23214"}
{"prompt": "4958,4959,4960,4961,4962,4963,4964,4965", "answer": "4966"}
{"prompt": "23166,23167", "answer": "23168"}
{"prompt": "18517,18518", "answer": "18519"}
{"prompt": "36974,36975,36976,36977,36978,36979", "answer": "36980"}
{"prompt": "35916,35917,35918,35919,35920,35921,35922,35923,35924", "answer": "35925"}
{"prompt": "31529,31530,31531,31532,31533,31534,31535,31536,31537", "answer": "31538"}
{"prompt": "33665,33666", "answer": "33667"}
{"prompt": "15608,15609,15610", "answer": "15611"}
{"prompt": "17064,17065,17066,17067,17068", "answer": "17069"}
{"prompt": "782,783,784,785,786,787,788,789,790", "answer": "791"}
{"prompt": "24502,24503,24504,24505,24506", "answer": "24507"}
{"prompt": "31098,31099,31100,31101,31102,31103,31104,31105", "answer": "31106"}
{"prompt": "41518,41519,41520", "answer": "41521"}
{"prompt": "30227", "answer": "30228"}
{"prompt": "8646,8647", "answer": "8648"}
{"prompt": "8052", "answer": "8053"}
{"prompt": "30509,30510", "answer": "30511"}
{"prompt": "659,660,661,662,663,664,665,666,667", "answer": "668"}
{"prompt": "21926,21927,21928,21929,21930,21931,21932,21933", "answer": "21934"}
{"prompt": "6997,6998,6999,7000,7001", "answer": "7002"}
{"prompt": "16114,16115,16116,16117,16118,16119", "answer": "16120"}
{"prompt": "7396,7397,7398,7399,7400,7401", "answer": "7402"}
{"prompt": "16793,16794,16795,16796", "answer": "16797"}
{"prompt": "19508,19509,19510,19511,19512,19513,19514,19515,19516", "answer": "19517"}
{"prompt": "39899,39900,39901", "answer": "39902"}
{"prompt": "34039,34040,34041,34042,34043,34044", "answer": "34045"}
{"prompt": "21316,21317,21318,21319,21320,21321,21322", "answer": "21323"}
{"prompt": "1112,1113,1114,1115,1116,1117,1118", "answer": "1119"}
{"prompt": "37947,37948,37949,37950,37951,37952,37953,37954,37955,37956", "answer": "37957"}
{"prompt": "10542,10543,10544,10545,10546,10547", "answer": "10548"}
{"prompt": "16408,16409,16410,16411,16412,16413", "answer": "16414"}
{"prompt": "373,374,375,376,377,378", "answer": "379"}
{"prompt": "5014,5015,5016,5017,5018,5019,5020,5021,5022,5023", "answer": "5024"}
{"prompt": "5074,5075,5076,5077,5078,5079,5080,5081,5082,5083", "answer": "5084"}
{"prompt": "43832,43833,43834", "answer": "43835"}
{"prompt": "39077,39078,39079,39080,39081,39082,39083", "answer": "39084"}
{"prompt": "40941,40942", "answer": "40943"}
{"prompt": "20566,20567,20568", "answer": "20569"}
{"prompt": "4339,4340", "answer": "4341"}
{"prompt": "15632,15633,15634,15635,15636,15637", "answer": "15638"}
{"prompt": "1528,1529,1530,1531,1532", "answer": "1533"}
{"prompt": "14296,14297", "answer": "14298"}
{"prompt": "42014,42015,42016", "answer": "42017"}
{"prompt": "3186,3187,3188,3189", "answer": "3190"}
{"prompt": "32864,32865,32866,32867,32868,32869,32870,32871", "answer": "32872"}
{"prompt": "40096,40097,40098,40099,40100,40101,40102", "answer": "40103"}
{"prompt": "39126,39127", "answer": "39128"}
{"prompt": "18525", "answer": "18526"}
{"prompt": "2134,2135,2136,2137,2138,2139,2140,2141,2142,2143", "answer": "2144"}
{"prompt": "17068,17069,17070,17071,17072", "answer": "17073"}
{"prompt": "8469,8470,8471,8472,8473,8474", "answer": "8475"}
{"prompt": "4869,4870,4871,4872,4873,4874,4875", "answer": "4876"}
{"prompt": "39918", "answer": "39919"}
{"prompt": "5607,5608", "answer": "5609"}
{"prompt": "2125,2126,2127,2128,2129,2130,2131,2132,2133,2134", "answer": "2135"}
{"prompt": "18670,18671,18672,18673", "answer": "18674"}
{"prompt": "43834", "answer": "43835"}
{"prompt": "364,365,366,367,368,369,370,371,372,373", "answer": "374"}
{"prompt": "19631,19632,19633,19634,19635,19636,19637,19638,19639", "answer": "19640"}
{"prompt": "32316,32317,32318", "answer": "32319"}
{"prompt": "37776,37777,37778,37779,37780", "answer": "37781"}
{"prompt": "18880,18881,18882,18883,18884,18885,18886,18887", "answer": "18888"}
{"prompt": "27254", "answer": "27255"}
{"prompt": "42127,42128,42129,42130,42131,42132,42133,42134,42135,42136", "answer": "42137"}
{"prompt": "29442,29443,29444,29445,29446", "answer": "29447"}
{"prompt": "15229,15230,15231,15232,15233,15234", "answer": "15235"}
{"prompt": "34678,34679,34680", "answer": "34681"}
{"prompt": "14473,14474,14475,14476,14477", "answer": "14478"}
{"prompt": "956,957,958,959,960,961,962", "answer": "963"}
{"prompt": "1710,1711,1712,1713,1714,1715,1716", "answer": "1717"}
{"prompt": "2884,2885,2886", "answer": "2887"}
{"prompt": "10630,10631,10632,10633,10634,10635,10636", "answer": "10637"}
{"prompt": "39438,39439,39440,39441,39442,39443,39444,39445,39446", "answer": "39447"}
{"prompt": "15946", "answer": "15947"}
{"prompt": "32999,33000,33001,33002,33003", "answer": "33004"}
{"prompt": "36944", "answer": "36945"}
{"prompt": "36885,36886,36887,36888,36889,36890,36891,36892", "answer": "36893"}
{"prompt": "33330", "answer": "33331"}
{"prompt": "28200,28201,28202", "answer": "28203"}
{"prompt": "23276,23277", "answer": "23278"}
{"prompt": "11604", "answer": "11605"}
{"prompt": "19157,19158,19159,19160,19161,19162,19163,19164", "answer": "19165"}
{"prompt": "43950,43951,43952,43953", "answer": "43954"}
{"prompt": "1866,1867,1868,1869,1870,1871,1872,1873,1874,1875", "answer": "1876"}
{"prompt": "11556,11557,11558", "answer": "11559"}
{"prompt": "1383,1384,1385,1386,1387,1388", "answer": "1389"}
{"prompt": "4618,4619,4620,4621", "answer": "4622"}
{"prompt": "17951,17952,17953,17954,17955,17956,17957", "answer": "17958"}
{"prompt": "42190,42191,42192", "answer": "42193"}
{"prompt": "11182,11183,11184,11185,11186,11187,11188", "answer": "11189"}
{"prompt": "10514,10515,10516,10517,10518", "answer": "10519"}
{"prompt": "44203,44204,44205", "answer": "44206"}
{"prompt": "20372,20373,20374", "answer": "20375"}
{"prompt": "26426,26427,26428,26429,26430,26431", "answer": "26432"}
{"prompt": "39605,39606", "answer": "39607"}
{"prompt": "7270,7271,7272,7273,7274", "answer": "7275"}
{"prompt": "39251,39252,39253,39254", "answer": "39255"}
{"prompt": "16935", "answer": "16936"}
{"prompt": "17223,17224,17225", "answer": "17226"}
{"prompt": "22874,22875,22876,22877,22878,22879,22880", "answer": "22881"}
{"prompt": "44016,44017,44018,44019,44020,44021,44022,44023,44024", "answer": "44025"}
{"prompt": "16062,16063", "answer": "16064"}
{"prompt": "21596,21597,21598,21599,21600", "answer": "21601"}
{"prompt": "38531,38532,38533,38534,38535,38536,38537,38538", "answer": "38539"}
{"prompt": "20399,20400,20401,20402,20403,20404", "answer": "20405"}
{"prompt": "27000", "answer": "27001"}
{"prompt": "42562,42563,42564,42565,42566,42567,42568", "answer": "42569"}
{"prompt": "20348,20349,20350,20351,20352,20353,20354,20355,20356", "answer": "20357"}
{"prompt": "19271,19272,19273,19274,19275,19276", "answer": "19277"}
{"prompt": "9509,9510,9511,9512", "answer": "9513"}
{"prompt": "43114", "answer": "43115"}
{"prompt": "31060,31061,31062,31063,31064", "answer": "31065"}
{"prompt": "17341,17342,17343,17344,17345,17346,17347,17348", "answer": "17349"}
{"prompt": "4236,4237,4238,4239,4240,4241,4242,4243,4244", "answer": "4245"}
{"prompt": "36776,36777,36778,36779", "answer": "36780"}
{"prompt": "12139,12140,12141", "answer": "12142"}
{"prompt": "41520", "answer": "41521"}
{"prompt": "15997,15998,15999", "answer": "16000"}
{"prompt": "6679,6680,6681,6682,6683,6684,6685,6686,6687,6688", "answer": "6689"}
{"prompt": "17619,17620,17621,17622,17623,17624,17625,17626,17627", "answer": "17628"}
{"prompt": "11118,11119,11120,11121,11122,11123,11124,11125,11126", "answer": "11127"}
{"prompt": "3930,3931", "answer": "3932"}
{"prompt": "34060", "answer": "34061"}
{"prompt": "28814,28815", "answer": "28816"}
{"prompt": "5545,5546,5547,5548,5549,5550", "answer": "5551"}
{"prompt": "14054,14055,14056,14057,14058,14059,14060,14061,14062", "answer": "14063"}
{"prompt": "13824,13825,13826", "answer": "13827"}
{"prompt": "10677,10678,10679,10680,10681", "answer": "10682"}
{"prompt": "14531,14532", "answer": "14533"}
{"prompt": "3794,3795,3796,3797,3798,3799,3800,3801,3802,3803", "answer": "3804"}
{"prompt": "44114,44115,44116,44117,44118,44119,44120,44121,44122,44123", "answer": "44124"}
{"prompt": "1860,1861,1862,1863,1864", "answer": "1865"}
{"prompt": "33415,33416,33417,33418,33419,33420,33421,33422", "answer": "33423"}
{"prompt": "40785,40786,40787,40788,40789,40790,40791,40792,40793", "answer": "40794"}
{"prompt": "1976,1977,1978,1979,1980,1981", "answer": "1982"}
{"prompt": "25370,25371,25372", "answer": "25373"}
{"prompt": "28654,28655,28656,28657,28658,28659,28660,28661", "answer": "28662"}
{"prompt": "7547,7548,7549,7550,7551,7552,7553,7554,7555", "answer": "7556"}
{"prompt": "30858,30859,30860,30861,30862,30863,30864", "answer": "30865"}
{"prompt": "41337,41338,41339,41340,41341,41342", "answer": "41343"}
{"prompt": "23295,23296,23297,23298,23299,23300,23301,23302,23303", "answer": "23304"}
{"prompt": "11287,11288,11289,11290,11291,11292,11293,11294", "answer": "11295"}
{"prompt": "26220,26221,26222", "answer": "26223"}
{"prompt": "34919,34920,34921,34922,34923,34924,34925,34926,34927,34928", "answer": "34929"}
{"prompt": "8380,8381,8382,8383,8384,8385,8386,8387", "answer": "8388"}
{"prompt": "21785,21786,21787,21788,21789,21790,21791", "answer": "21792"}
{"prompt": "39379,39380,39381,39382,39383,39384", "answer": "39385"}
{"prompt": "2112,2113,2114,2115,2116", "answer": "2117"}
{"prompt": "7307,7308,7309,7310,7311", "answer": "7312"}
{"prompt": "4837,4838,4839,4840,4841,4842,4843,4844", "answer": "4845"}
{"prompt": "26456,26457,26458,26459,26460,26461,26462", "answer": "26463"}
{"prompt": "3582,3583,3584,3585,3586,3587,3588,3589,3590,3591", "answer": "3592"}
{"prompt": "6202,6203,6204,6205", "answer": "6206"}
{"prompt": "33480,33481", "answer": "33482"}
{"prompt": "11371,11372,11373,11374,11375,11376,11377,11378,11379", "answer": "11380"}
{"prompt": "16250,16251,16252,16253,16254,16255", "answer": "16256"}
{"prompt": "3681,3682,3683,3684,3685,3686,3687,3688,3689", "answer": "3690"}
{"prompt": "39808,39809,39810", "answer": "39811"}
{"prompt": "16970,16971", "answer": "16972"}
{"prompt": "15423,15424,15425,15426", "answer": "15427"}
{"prompt": "6942,6943,6944", "answer": "6945"}
{"prompt": "37596,37597,37598,37599,37600,37601", "answer": "37602"}
{"prompt": "4925,4926,4927,4928,4929,4930,4931,4932,4933,4934", "answer": "4935"}
{"prompt": "37688,37689,37690,37691,37692", "answer": "37693"}
{"prompt": "41702,41703", "answer": "41704"}
{"prompt": "17761,17762,17763,17764,17765", "answer": "17766"}
{"prompt": "11764,11765,11766,11767,11768,11769", "answer": "11770"}
{"prompt": "118,119,120,121,122,123", "answer": "124"}
{"prompt": "15250,15251,15252,15253,15254", "answer": "15255"}
{"prompt": "2775,2776,2777,2778,2779,2780,2781,2782", "answer": "2783"}
{"prompt": "26432,26433,26434,26435,26436,26437,26438,26439", "answer": "26440"}
{"prompt": "30752,30753,30754", "answer": "30755"}
{"prompt": "42192,42193,42194,42195,42196,42197,42198", "answer": "42199"}
{"prompt": "9470,9471,9472,9473,9474,9475", "answer": "9476"}
{"prompt": "18428,18429,18430,18431,18432", "answer": "18433"}
{"prompt": "32197,32198,32199,32200,32201,32202,32203,32204,32205,32206", "answer": "32207"}
{"prompt": "1439,1440,1441", "answer": "1442"}
{"prompt": "13149,13150,13151,13152,13153,13154,13155,13156,13157,13158", "answer": "13159"}
{"prompt": "6479,6480,6481,6482,6483", "answer": "6484"}
{"prompt": "112,113,114,115,116,117,118", "answer": "119"}
{"prompt": "29822,29823,29824,29825", "answer": "29826"}
{"prompt": "18506,18507,18508,18509,18510", "answer": "18511"}
{"prompt": "43335,43336,43337", "answer": "43338"}
{"prompt": "33375,33376,33377,33378,33379,33380", "answer": "33381"}
{"prompt": "31343,31344,31345,31346,31347,31348", "answer": "31349"}
{"prompt": "41556", "answer": "41557"}
{"prompt": "41566,41567,41568,41569,41570,41571,41572", "answer": "41573"}
{"prompt": "29336,29337,29338,29339,29340", "answer": "29341"}
{"prompt": "14807,14808,14809,14810,14811,14812", "answer": "14813"}
{"prompt": "44849,44850,44851,44852,44853,44854,44855", "answer": "44856"}
{"prompt": "27336,27337,27338,27339,27340,27341,27342,27343,27344,27345", "answer": "27346"}
{"prompt": "20588", "answer": "20589"}
{"prompt": "38772,38773,38774", "answer": "38775"}
{"prompt": "12541,12542,12543,12544,12545,12546,12547,12548,12549,12550", "answer": "12551"}
{"prompt": "31870,31871,31872,31873,31874,31875,31876,31877,31878,31879", "answer": "31880"}
{"prompt": "19088,19089", "answer": "19090"}
{"prompt": "17627,17628,17629,17630,17631,17632", "answer": "17633"}
{"prompt": "33848", "answer": "33849"}
{"prompt": "41115,41116,41117,41118,41119,41120,41121,41122", "answer": "41123"}
{"prompt": "42830,42831,42832,42833,42834,42835,42836,42837,42838,42839", "answer": "42840"}
{"prompt": "26128,26129,26130", "answer": "26131"}
{"prompt": "12557,12558,12559,12560,12561,12562,12563,12564,12565,12566", "answer": "12567"}
{"prompt": "11905,11906,11907,11908", "answer": "11909"}
{"prompt": "24319,24320,24321,24322,24323,24324", "answer": "24325"}
{"prompt": "36952,36953,36954,36955", "answer": "36956"}
{"prompt": "14998,14999,15000,15001,15002,15003", "answer": "15004"}
{"prompt": "5897,5898,5899", "answer": "5900"}
{"prompt": "40663,40664,40665,40666,40667,40668,40669,40670", "answer": "40671"}
{"prompt": "2488,2489,2490,2491,2492", "answer": "2493"}
{"prompt": "15988,15989", "answer": "15990"}
{"prompt": "19143,19144,19145,19146,19147", "answer": "19148"}
{"prompt": "26334,26335,26336,26337,26338,26339,26340,26341,26342,26343", "answer": "26344"}
{"prompt": "31045,31046,31047,31048,31049", "answer": "31050"}
{"prompt": "30153,30154,30155,30156,30157,30158,30159", "answer": "30160"}
{"prompt": "742,743,744,745,746,747,748,749,750", "answer": "751"}
{"prompt": "30596,30597,30598,30599,30600,30601,30602,30603", "answer": "30604"}
{"prompt": "37083,37084,37085,37086,37087,37088,37089,37090,37091,37092", "answer": "37093"}
{"prompt": "22544,22545,22546,22547,22548,22549,22550", "answer": "22551"}
{"prompt": "19276,19277,19278,19279,19280,19281", "answer": "19282"}
{"prompt": "36909,36910,36911,36912,36913,36914,36915,36916,36917,36918", "answer": "36919"}
{"prompt": "24190,24191,24192,24193,24194,24195,24196,24197", "answer": "24198"}
{"prompt": "25200,25201,25202,25203,25204,25205,25206,25207,25208,25209", "answer": "25210"}
{"prompt": "16270,16271,16272,16273,16274,16275,16276,16277", "answer": "16278"}
{"prompt": "31554,31555,31556,31557,31558,31559,31560,31561", "answer": "31562"}
{"prompt": "998,999,1000,1001,1002,1003,1004", "answer": "1005"}
{"prompt": "24348,24349,24350,24351,24352,24353,24354", "answer": "24355"}
{"prompt": "30137,30138,30139,30140,30141,30142,30143", "answer": "30144"}
{"prompt": "4846,4847,4848,4849,4850", "answer": "4851"}
{"prompt": "14350,14351,14352,14353,14354", "answer": "14355"}
{"prompt": "2030,2031,2032,2033,2034,2035", "answer": "2036"}
{"prompt": "32622,32623,32624,32625,32626,32627,32628,32629", "answer": "32630"}
{"prompt": "41838,41839,41840,41841,41842,41843,41844,41845", "answer": "41846"}
{"prompt": "20368,20369,20370,20371,20372", "answer": "20373"}
{"prompt": "26207,26208", "answer": "26209"}
{"prompt": "18139,18140,18141,18142,18143,18144", "answer": "18145"}
{"prompt": "28713,28714,28715,28716,28717,28718,28719,28720,28721", "answer": "28722"}
{"prompt": "20737,20738,20739,20740,20741,20742,20743", "answer": "20744"}
{"prompt": "21649,21650", "answer": "21651"}
{"prompt": "12023,12024,12025,12026,12027,12028,12029,12030", "answer": "12031"}
{"prompt": "15704,15705,15706,15707,15708,15709,15710,15711", "answer": "15712"}
{"prompt": "40311,40312,40313,40314,40315,40316,40317", "answer": "40318"}
{"prompt": "39152", "answer": "39153"}
{"prompt": "10228,10229,10230,10231,10232,10233,10234,10235", "answer": "10236"}
{"prompt": "7448", "answer": "7449"}
{"prompt": "21938,21939", "answer": "21940"}
{"prompt": "37263,37264,37265,37266,37267", "answer": "37268"}
{"prompt": "40501,40502,40503,40504,40505", "answer": "40506"}
{"prompt": "23514,23515,23516,23517", "answer": "23518"}
{"prompt": "36971,36972,36973,36974", "answer": "36975"}
{"prompt": "30521,30522,30523,30524,30525", "answer": "30526"}
{"prompt": "24302,24303,24304,24305,24306,24307,24308", "answer": "24309"}
{"prompt": "6600,6601,6602,6603,6604,6605,6606", "answer": "6607"}
{"prompt": "41395", "answer": "41396"}
{"prompt": "45036", "answer": "45037"}
{"prompt": "23213,23214,23215,23216,23217,23218,23219,23220,23221,23222", "answer": "23223"}
{"prompt": "20771,20772,20773,20774", "answer": "20775"}
{"prompt": "42233,42234,42235,42236,42237,42238,42239,42240,42241", "answer": "42242"}
{"prompt": "42350,42351,42352,42353", "answer": "42354"}
{"prompt": "9762,9763,9764,9765,9766,9767,9768,9769,9770", "answer": "9771"}
{"prompt": "28131,28132,28133,28134,28135,28136,28137,28138,28139,28140", "answer": "28141"}
{"prompt": "2766,2767", "answer": "2768"}
{"prompt": "43974", "answer": "43975"}
{"prompt": "1197", "answer": "1198"}
{"prompt": "1118,1119,1120", "answer": "1121"}
{"prompt": "9240,9241,9242,9243,9244,9245,9246,9247,9248", "answer": "9249"}
{"prompt": "2349,2350,2351,2352,2353,2354,2355,2356", "answer": "2357"}
{"prompt": "43019,43020,43021,43022,43023,43024", "answer": "43025"}
{"prompt": "20643,20644,20645,20646,20647,20648", "answer": "20649"}
{"prompt": "43548,43549,43550,43551,43552", "answer": "43553"}
{"prompt": "997", "answer": "998"}
{"prompt": "9517,9518,9519,9520,9521,9522,9523,9524,9525", "answer": "9526"}
{"prompt": "21981,21982,21983", "answer": "21984"}
{"prompt": "30589,30590,30591,30592,30593", "answer": "30594"}
{"prompt": "14231,14232,14233,14234,14235,14236,14237,14238,14239", "answer": "14240"}
{"prompt": "10599,10600", "answer": "10601"}
{"prompt": "40408,40409,40410,40411,40412,40413,40414", "answer": "40415"}
{"prompt": "19425,19426,19427,19428,19429,19430,19431,19432,19433,19434", "answer": "19435"}
{"prompt": "36430,36431", "answer": "36432"}
{"prompt": "29585,29586,29587,29588", "answer": "29589"}
{"prompt": "30654,30655,30656,30657,30658,30659,30660,30661", "answer": "30662"}
{"prompt": "11486,11487,11488,11489,11490,11491,11492,11493,11494", "answer": "11495"}
{"prompt": "15193,15194,15195,15196,15197,15198,15199,15200,15201,15202", "answer": "15203"}
{"prompt": "38663,38664,38665,38666,38667,38668", "answer": "38669"}
{"prompt": "7363,7364,7365,7366,7367,7368,7369", "answer": "7370"}
{"prompt": "21627,21628", "answer": "21629"}
{"prompt": "30355,30356,30357,30358,30359,30360", "answer": "30361"}
{"prompt": "8080", "answer": "8081"}
{"prompt": "26738,26739,26740,26741,26742,26743", "answer": "26744"}
{"prompt": "432,433,434,435,436,437,438,439,440,441", "answer": "442"}
{"prompt": "44395,44396,44397,44398,44399,44400,44401,44402,44403", "answer": "44404"}
{"prompt": "36881,36882,36883,36884,36885", "answer": "36886"}
{"prompt": "32255,32256,32257", "answer": "32258"}
{"prompt": "5819,5820,5821,5822,5823,5824,5825,5826,5827,5828", "answer": "5829"}
{"prompt": "34383,34384", "answer": "34385"}
{"prompt": "33132,33133,33134,33135,33136,33137,33138,33139", "answer": "33140"}
{"prompt": "29505,29506,29507,29508,29509,29510,29511,29512,29513", "answer": "29514"}
{"prompt": "36827,36828,36829", "answer": "36830"}
{"prompt": "28981,28982,28983,28984,28985,28986,28987,28988,28989", "answer": "28990"}
{"prompt": "22555", "answer": "22556"}
{"prompt": "41726,41727,41728,41729,41730,41731,41732,41733,41734", "answer": "41735"}
{"prompt": "22666", "answer": "22667"}
{"prompt": "26738", "answer": "26739"}
{"prompt": "21395,21396", "answer": "21397"}
{"prompt": "26082,26083,26084,26085,26086", "answer": "26087"}
{"prompt": "32768,32769", "answer": "32770"}
{"prompt": "21048,21049,21050,21051,21052,21053,21054,21055,21056,21057", "answer": "21058"}
{"prompt": "25159", "answer": "25160"}
{"prompt": "11357,11358,11359,11360,11361,11362", "answer": "11363"}
{"prompt": "16526,16527,16528,16529", "answer": "16530"}
{"prompt": "29738,29739,29740,29741,29742,29743", "answer": "29744"}
{"prompt": "5133,5134,5135,5136,5137,5138,5139,5140", "answer": "5141"}
{"prompt": "31037,31038", "answer": "31039"}
{"prompt": "31008,31009,31010,31011,31012,31013,31014,31015,31016,31017", "answer": "31018"}
{"prompt": "1879", "answer": "1880"}
{"prompt": "42530,42531,42532,42533", "answer": "42534"}
{"prompt": "39071,39072,39073,39074,39075,39076,39077", "answer": "39078"}
{"prompt": "41976,41977,41978,41979,41980,41981,41982,41983,41984,41985", "answer": "41986"}
{"prompt": "11133,11134", "answer": "11135"}
{"prompt": "32071,32072,32073,32074,32075,32076,32077,32078,32079", "answer": "32080"}
{"prompt": "10406,10407,10408", "answer": "10409"}
{"prompt": "22287,22288,22289,22290,22291,22292,22293,22294", "answer": "22295"}
{"prompt": "30014,30015,30016,30017,30018,30019,30020", "answer": "30021"}
{"prompt": "33566,33567,33568,33569,33570,33571", "answer": "33572"}
{"prompt": "31539,31540,31541,31542,31543,31544,31545,31546,31547,31548", "answer": "31549"}
{"prompt": "37749,37750,37751,37752,37753,37754,37755,37756", "answer": "37757"}
{"prompt": "16005,16006,16007,16008", "answer": "16009"}
{"prompt": "32504,32505", "answer": "32506"}
{"prompt": "1396,1397,1398,1399,1400,1401,1402,1403,1404,1405", "answer": "1406"}
{"prompt": "42136,42137,42138,42139,42140,42141", "answer": "42142"}
{"prompt": "25716,25717,25718,25719,25720,25721,25722", "answer": "25723"}
{"prompt": "18106,18107,18108,18109,18110", "answer": "18111"}
{"prompt": "41609", "answer": "41610"}
{"prompt": "45273,45274,45275,45276,45277", "answer": "45278"}
{"prompt": "26376,26377,26378,26379,26380,26381,26382,26383,26384,26385", "answer": "26386"}
{"prompt": "44654,44655,44656,44657,44658,44659,44660", "answer": "44661"}
{"prompt": "2608,2609,2610,2611,2612,2613,2614", "answer": "2615"}
{"prompt": "3757,3758,3759,3760,3761,3762,3763,3764,3765,3766", "answer": "3767"}
{"prompt": "4850", "answer": "4851"}
{"prompt": "5541,5542,5543,5544,5545", "answer": "5546"}
{"prompt": "169,170,171,172,173,174,175,176", "answer": "177"}
{"prompt": "17108", "answer": "17109"}
{"prompt": "32170,32171,32172,32173,32174,32175,32176,32177,32178,32179", "answer": "32180"}
{"prompt": "19259,19260,19261,19262,19263,19264,19265", "answer": "19266"}
{"prompt": "14812,14813,14814,14815,14816,14817,14818", "answer": "14819"}
{"prompt": "24697,24698,24699,24700,24701", "answer": "24702"}
{"prompt": "43771,43772,43773,43774,43775,43776", "answer": "43777"}
{"prompt": "31183,31184", "answer": "31185"}
{"prompt": "24723", "answer": "24724"}
{"prompt": "44429,44430,44431,44432", "answer": "44433"}
{"prompt": "27934,27935,27936,27937,27938", "answer": "27939"}
{"prompt": "20123,20124,20125,20126,20127,20128,20129,20130,20131", "answer": "20132"}
{"prompt": "22780,22781,22782,22783,22784", "answer": "22785"}
{"prompt": "18289,18290,18291,18292,18293,18294,18295,18296,18297", "answer": "18298"}
{"prompt": "5475,5476,5477,5478,5479,5480,5481,5482", "answer": "5483"}
{"prompt": "28554,28555,28556,28557,28558", "answer": "28559"}
{"prompt": "32080,32081", "answer": "32082"}
{"prompt": "21017,21018,21019", "answer": "21020"}
{"prompt": "42740,42741", "answer": "42742"}
{"prompt": "31386,31387,31388,31389,31390,31391,31392", "answer": "31393"}
{"prompt": "38042,38043", "answer": "38044"}
{"prompt": "34028,34029,34030,34031,34032,34033,34034,34035,34036,34037", "answer": "34038"}
{"prompt": "29750", "answer": "29751"}
{"prompt": "36765,36766,36767,36768", "answer": "36769"}
{"prompt": "43011,43012,43013,43014,43015,43016,43017,43018,43019", "answer": "43020"}
{"prompt": "8999,9000", "answer": "9001"}
{"prompt": "5900,5901,5902", "answer": "5903"}
{"prompt": "23923,23924,23925,23926,23927", "answer": "23928"}
{"prompt": "14689,14690", "answer": "14691"}
{"prompt": "44066,44067", "answer": "44068"}
{"prompt": "43874,43875,43876,43877,43878,43879,43880,43881", "answer": "43882"}
{"prompt": "29486,29487", "answer": "29488"}
{"prompt": "36041,36042,36043,36044", "answer": "36045"}
{"prompt": "39193,39194,39195,39196,39197,39198,39199,39200,39201", "answer": "39202"}
{"prompt": "6070,6071,6072,6073,6074", "answer": "6075"}
{"prompt": "38", "answer": "39"}
{"prompt": "20559,20560,20561,20562,20563,20564,20565,20566", "answer": "20567"}
{"prompt": "33261,33262,33263,33264,33265", "answer": "33266"}
{"prompt": "4576,4577,4578,4579,4580,4581", "answer": "4582"}
{"prompt": "8791,8792", "answer": "8793"}
{"prompt": "30044,30045,30046,30047,30048,30049,30050,30051", "answer": "30052"}
{"prompt": "31064,31065,31066", "answer": "31067"}
{"prompt": "6739,6740", "answer": "6741"}
{"prompt": "2584,2585,2586,2587,2588,2589,2590", "answer": "2591"}
{"prompt": "13377,13378,13379,13380,13381,13382", "answer": "13383"}
{"prompt": "39801,39802,39803,39804,39805,39806,39807,39808", "answer": "39809"}
{"prompt": "42651,42652,42653,42654,42655,42656,42657,42658,42659,42660", "answer": "42661"}
{"prompt": "39855,39856,39857,39858,39859", "answer": "39860"}
{"prompt": "20131,20132,20133,20134,20135,20136,20137", "answer": "20138"}
{"prompt": "14605,14606,14607,14608", "answer": "14609"}
{"prompt": "36942,36943,36944", "answer": "36945"}
{"prompt": "20363,20364,20365", "answer": "20366"}
{"prompt": "31605,31606,31607", "answer": "31608"}
{"prompt": "20374,20375,20376,20377,20378", "answer": "20379"}
{"prompt": "20212,20213,20214,20215,20216,20217,20218,20219,20220", "answer": "20221"}
{"prompt": "35172,35173,35174,35175,35176,35177,35178,35179", "answer": "35180"}
{"prompt": "44820,44821,44822,44823", "answer": "44824"}
{"prompt": "38889,38890", "answer": "38891"}
{"prompt": "28050,28051,28052,28053,28054,28055,28056,28057", "answer": "28058"}
{"prompt": "1447,1448,1449,1450", "answer": "1451"}
{"prompt": "26402,26403", "answer": "26404"}
{"prompt": "26350,26351,26352,26353,26354,26355,26356,26357,26358", "answer": "26359"}
{"prompt": "2697,2698,2699,2700,2701,2702,2703", "answer": "2704"}
{"prompt": "22425,22426,22427,22428,22429,22430,22431,22432,22433", "answer": "22434"}
{"prompt": "44328,44329,44330", "answer": "44331"}
{"prompt": "20627", "answer": "20628"}
{"prompt": "22146,22147,22148,22149,22150,22151", "answer": "22152"}
{"prompt": "31647,31648", "answer": "31649"}
{"prompt": "322,323,324,325,326", "answer": "327"}
{"prompt": "35581,35582,35583,35584,35585,35586", "answer": "35587"}
{"prompt": "17924,17925,17926,17927", "answer": "17928"}
{"prompt": "37003,37004,37005", "answer": "37006"}
{"prompt": "4636,4637,4638,4639", "answer": "4640"}
{"prompt": "34831,34832,34833", "answer": "34834"}
{"prompt": "15220,15221,15222", "answer": "15223"}
{"prompt": "16778,16779,16780,16781,16782,16783,16784,16785", "answer": "16786"}
{"prompt": "29885,29886,29887,29888,29889,29890,29891", "answer": "29892"}
{"prompt": "17748,17749,17750,17751,17752,17753", "answer": "17754"}
{"prompt": "35269,35270,35271,35272,35273,35274,35275,35276,35277", "answer": "35278"}
{"prompt": "18977,18978,18979,18980,18981,18982,18983", "answer": "18984"}
{"prompt": "40903", "answer": "40904"}
{"prompt": "40861,40862,40863,40864", "answer": "40865"}
{"prompt": "14662,14663,14664,14665,14666,14667,14668", "answer": "14669"}
{"prompt": "5952,5953,5954,5955,5956,5957,5958,5959,5960", "answer": "5961"}
{"prompt": "45025,45026,45027,45028,45029,45030,45031,45032,45033,45034", "answer": "45035"}
{"prompt": "3568,3569,3570,3571,3572", "answer": "3573"}
{"prompt": "13089,13090,13091,13092,13093,13094,13095,13096", "answer": "13097"}
{"prompt": "21260", "answer": "21261"}
{"prompt": "42827,42828,42829,42830", "answer": "42831"}
{"prompt": "29211,29212,29213", "answer": "29214"}
{"prompt": "28308,28309,28310,28311", "answer": "28312"}
{"prompt": "24034", "answer": "24035"}
{"prompt": "21148,21149", "answer": "21150"}
{"prompt": "14743,14744,14745", "answer": "14746"}
{"prompt": "8840,8841,8842", "answer": "8843"}
{"prompt": "40602,40603,40604,40605,40606,40607,40608,40609", "answer": "40610"}
{"prompt": "5762,5763", "answer": "5764"}
{"prompt": "4311,4312,4313,4314,4315,4316,4317,4318,4319", "answer": "4320"}
{"prompt": "24358,24359,24360", "answer": "24361"}
{"prompt": "23647,23648,23649,23650,23651,23652,23653,23654,23655", "answer": "23656"}
{"prompt": "3846,3847,3848,3849,3850,3851,3852,3853,3854,3855", "answer": "3856"}
{"prompt": "22433,22434,22435,22436,22437,22438,22439,22440,22441", "answer": "22442"}
{"prompt": "42178,42179,42180", "answer": "42181"}
{"prompt": "37732,37733", "answer": "37734"}
{"prompt": "35792,35793,35794,35795,35796,35797,35798,35799,35800", "answer": "35801"}
{"prompt": "32680,32681,32682,32683,32684,32685,32686,32687,32688,32689", "answer": "32690"}
{"prompt": "1109,1110,1111,1112", "answer": "1113"}
{"prompt": "39031,39032,39033,39034,39035,39036", "answer": "39037"}
{"prompt": "22869,22870,22871,22872,22873,22874", "answer": "22875"}
{"prompt": "35486,35487,35488,35489,35490,35491,35492,35493,35494", "answer": "35495"}
{"prompt": "38997", "answer": "38998"}
{"prompt": "12880,12881,12882,12883,12884", "answer": "12885"}
{"prompt": "16731,16732,16733,16734,16735,16736,16737,16738,16739,16740", "answer": "16741"}
{"prompt": "19711,19712,19713,19714,19715,19716", "answer": "19717"}
{"prompt": "42556,42557,42558,42559,42560,42561,42562", "answer": "42563"}
{"prompt": "44176,44177,44178", "answer": "44179"}
{"prompt": "5231,5232,5233", "answer": "5234"}
{"prompt": "9919,9920,9921,9922", "answer": "9923"}
{"prompt": "42747,42748,42749,42750,42751", "answer": "42752"}
{"prompt": "11226,11227,11228,11229", "answer": "11230"}
{"prompt": "16832,16833,16834,16835,16836,16837", "answer": "16838"}
{"prompt": "19267,19268,19269", "answer": "19270"}
{"prompt": "37129,37130,37131,37132,37133,37134", "answer": "37135"}
{"prompt": "31419,31420,31421,31422,31423,31424,31425,31426", "answer": "31427"}
{"prompt": "12797,12798,12799", "answer": "12800"}
{"prompt": "5735,5736,5737,5738,5739,5740", "answer": "5741"}
{"prompt": "11823,11824,11825,11826,11827,11828,11829,11830,11831,11832", "answer": "11833"}
{"prompt": "17642,17643,17644,17645,17646,17647,17648", "answer": "17649"}
{"prompt": "25801,25802,25803,25804,25805,25806,25807,25808,25809,25810", "answer": "25811"}
{"prompt": "11837,11838,11839,11840,11841", "answer": "11842"}
{"prompt": "37317,37318,37319,37320", "answer": "37321"}
{"prompt": "25580,25581,25582,25583,25584,25585", "answer": "25586"}
{"prompt": "18560,18561,18562,18563", "answer": "18564"}
{"prompt": "7757,7758,7759,7760", "answer": "7761"}
{"prompt": "39810,39811,39812,39813,39814,39815,39816,39817,39818", "answer": "39819"}
{"prompt": "15052,15053,15054,15055,15056", "answer": "15057"}
{"prompt": "9188,9189,9190,9191,9192,9193", "answer": "9194"}
{"prompt": "27461,27462,27463,27464", "answer": "27465"}
{"prompt": "29064,29065,29066,29067,29068,29069,29070,29071,29072", "answer": "29073"}
{"prompt": "34037,34038,34039", "answer": "34040"}
{"prompt": "5377,5378", "answer": "5379"}
{"prompt": "11379,11380,11381,11382", "answer": "11383"}
{"prompt": "8847,8848", "answer": "8849"}
{"prompt": "13244,13245,13246,13247,13248,13249,13250,13251,13252,13253", "answer": "13254"}
{"prompt": "5994,5995", "answer": "5996"}
{"prompt": "28149,28150", "answer": "28151"}
{"prompt": "35842,35843,35844,35845,35846,35847,35848,35849,35850,35851", "answer": "35852"}
{"prompt": "31399,31400,31401,31402,31403,31404,31405", "answer": "31406"}
{"prompt": "40242,40243,40244,40245", "answer": "40246"}
{"prompt": "12455,12456,12457,12458,12459,12460,12461,12462,12463,12464", "answer": "12465"}
{"prompt": "34217,34218", "answer": "34219"}
{"prompt": "38428,38429,38430,38431,38432,38433,38434,38435", "answer": "38436"}
{"prompt": "8091,8092,8093,8094", "answer": "8095"}
{"prompt": "8052,8053,8054,8055,8056,8057,8058", "answer": "8059"}
{"prompt": "9281,9282", "answer": "9283"}
{"prompt": "31897,31898", "answer": "31899"}
{"prompt": "33930", "answer": "33931"}
{"prompt": "38740,38741,38742,38743,38744", "answer": "38745"}
{"prompt": "3494,3495,3496,3497,3498,3499,3500,3501,3502,3503", "answer": "3504"}
{"prompt": "17443,17444,17445,17446,17447,17448,17449", "answer": "17450"}
{"prompt": "40692,40693,40694,40695,40696,40697,40698,40699", "answer": "40700"}
{"prompt": "43037,43038,43039,43040,43041", "answer": "43042"}
{"prompt": "22100,22101", "answer": "22102"}
{"prompt": "24460,24461,24462,24463,24464,24465,24466,24467,24468", "answer": "24469"}
{"prompt": "17542,17543,17544,17545,17546,17547,17548,17549,17550,17551", "answer": "17552"}
{"prompt": "7300,7301,7302", "answer": "7303"}
{"prompt": "20639,20640,20641", "answer": "20642"}
{"prompt": "21035,21036,21037,21038,21039", "answer": "21040"}
{"prompt": "17903,17904,17905,17906", "answer": "17907"}
{"prompt": "6250,6251,6252,6253", "answer": "6254"}
{"prompt": "30871,30872,30873,30874", "answer": "30875"}
{"prompt": "25784,25785,25786,25787", "answer": "25788"}
{"prompt": "26835,26836,26837,26838,26839", "answer": "26840"}
{"prompt": "30799,30800,30801,30802,30803,30804,30805,30806,30807", "answer": "30808"}
{"prompt": "267,268,269,270,271,272", "answer": "273"}
{"prompt": "40376,40377,40378,40379,40380", "answer": "40381"}
{"prompt": "39410,39411,39412,39413,39414", "answer": "39415"}
{"prompt": "33718,33719,33720,33721,33722,33723,33724,33725,33726,33727", "answer": "33728"}
{"prompt": "34563,34564,34565", "answer": "34566"}
{"prompt": "43620,43621,43622,43623,43624,43625,43626", "answer": "43627"}
{"prompt": "27663,27664,27665,27666,27667,27668,27669,27670", "answer": "27671"}
{"prompt": "34348,34349,34350", "answer": "34351"}
{"prompt": "16544,16545,16546,16547,16548,16549", "answer": "16550"}
{"prompt": "25259,25260", "answer": "25261"}
{"prompt": "36525,36526,36527,36528,36529,36530", "answer": "36531"}
{"prompt": "231,232,233,234", "answer": "235"}
{"prompt": "6771,6772,6773,6774,6775,6776,6777,6778,6779", "answer": "6780"}
{"prompt": "27841,27842,27843,27844,27845,27846", "answer": "27847"}
{"prompt": "2716,2717,2718,2719,2720,2721,2722,2723", "answer": "2724"}
{"prompt": "11858,11859,11860,11861,11862,11863,11864,11865,11866,11867", "answer": "11868"}
{"prompt": "7082,7083,7084,7085,7086,7087,7088,7089", "answer": "7090"}
{"prompt": "5847", "answer": "5848"}
{"prompt": "26754,26755,26756,26757", "answer": "26758"}
{"prompt": "2520,2521,2522", "answer": "2523"}
{"prompt": "26403,26404,26405,26406", "answer": "26407"}
{"prompt": "22113,22114,22115,22116", "answer": "22117"}
{"prompt": "7159,7160,7161,7162,7163,7164,7165,7166", "answer": "7167"}
{"prompt": "25290,25291,25292,25293,25294,25295,25296,25297", "answer": "25298"}
{"prompt": "13874,13875,13876", "answer": "13877"}
{"prompt": "19899,19900,19901,19902,19903,19904,19905,19906,19907", "answer": "19908"}
{"prompt": "33515,33516,33517,33518", "answer": "33519"}
{"prompt": "23206,23207,23208,23209,23210", "answer": "23211"}
{"prompt": "44455,44456,44457,44458,44459,44460,44461", "answer": "44462"}
{"prompt": "28574,28575,28576,28577,28578,28579", "answer": "28580"}
{"prompt": "45314,45315", "answer": "45316"}
{"prompt": "44967,44968,44969,44970", "answer": "44971"}
{"prompt": "26592,26593,26594,26595,26596,26597,26598", "answer": "26599"}
{"prompt": "6007,6008,6009,6010,6011,6012,6013", "answer": "6014"}
{"prompt": "8569,8570,8571,8572", "answer": "8573"}
{"prompt": "29371,29372,29373,29374,29375", "answer": "29376"}
{"prompt": "38231,38232,38233,38234,38235", "answer": "38236"}
{"prompt": "41227,41228,41229,41230,41231", "answer": "41232"}
{"prompt": "27712", "answer": "27713"}
{"prompt": "37286,37287,37288", "answer": "37289"}
{"prompt": "17433,17434,17435", "answer": "17436"}
{"prompt": "11026", "answer": "11027"}
{"prompt": "44090", "answer": "44091"}
{"prompt": "42353,42354,42355,42356,42357", "answer": "42358"}
{"prompt": "14010", "answer": "14011"}
{"prompt": "43647,43648", "answer": "43649"}
{"prompt": "37484,37485,37486,37487,37488,37489,37490", "answer": "37491"}
{"prompt": "36748,36749,36750,36751,36752,36753,36754,36755,36756", "answer": "36757"}
{"prompt": "43348,43349,43350,43351,43352,43353,43354", "answer": "43355"}
{"prompt": "27720,27721,27722", "answer": "27723"}
{"prompt": "21746,21747,21748,21749,21750,21751,21752,21753,21754,21755", "answer": "21756"}
{"prompt": "6852,6853,6854,6855,6856", "answer": "6857"}
{"prompt": "8921,8922,8923", "answer": "8924"}
{"prompt": "15186,15187,15188,15189,15190,15191,15192,15193", "answer": "15194"}
{"prompt": "13958,13959,13960,13961,13962,13963,13964", "answer": "13965"}
{"prompt": "28233,28234,28235,28236,28237,28238", "answer": "28239"}
{"prompt": "8363,8364,8365,8366,8367,8368,8369,8370,8371,8372", "answer": "8373"}
{"prompt": "34377,34378,34379,34380,34381,34382,34383", "answer": "34384"}
{"prompt": "21900,21901,21902,21903,21904,21905,21906,21907,21908", "answer": "21909"}
{"prompt": "28144,28145,28146,28147,28148,28149", "answer": "28150"}
{"prompt": "29868,29869,29870,29871,29872,29873,29874,29875,29876,29877", "answer": "29878"}
{"prompt": "10655,10656,10657,10658,10659", "answer": "10660"}
{"prompt": "24161,24162,24163,24164,24165", "answer": "24166"}
{"prompt": "12678,12679,12680,12681,12682,12683", "answer": "12684"}
{"prompt": "23997,23998,23999,24000,24001,24002", "answer": "24003"}
{"prompt": "37368,37369,37370,37371,37372,37373", "answer": "37374"}
{"prompt": "42596,42597", "answer": "42598"}
{"prompt": "20699,20700", "answer": "20701"}
{"prompt": "27386,27387,27388,27389,27390,27391,27392,27393,27394,27395", "answer": "27396"}
{"prompt": "11039", "answer": "11040"}
{"prompt": "17124,17125,17126,17127,17128,17129,17130,17131,17132,17133", "answer": "17134"}
{"prompt": "1575,1576,1577,1578,1579", "answer": "1580"}
{"prompt": "21529,21530,21531,21532,21533,21534,21535", "answer": "21536"}
{"prompt": "14003", "answer": "14004"}
{"prompt": "192,193,194,195,196,197,198,199,200", "answer": "201"}
{"prompt": "39833,39834,39835,39836,39837,39838,39839", "answer": "39840"}
{"prompt": "44505,44506,44507,44508,44509,44510,44511,44512,44513,44514", "answer": "44515"}
{"prompt": "38033,38034", "answer": "38035"}
{"prompt": "24358", "answer": "24359"}
{"prompt": "1424,1425,1426,1427", "answer": "1428"}
{"prompt": "23277,23278,23279,23280,23281,23282,23283,23284,23285", "answer": "23286"}
{"prompt": "31514,31515,31516,31517,31518,31519,31520,31521,31522", "answer": "31523"}
{"prompt": "32235,32236,32237,32238", "answer": "32239"}
{"prompt": "20143,20144,20145,20146,20147,20148,20149,20150,20151,20152", "answer": "20153"}
{"prompt": "1066,1067,1068,1069,1070,1071,1072,1073,1074", "answer": "1075"}
{"prompt": "24659,24660,24661,24662,24663,24664", "answer": "24665"}
{"prompt": "20582,20583,20584,20585,20586,20587,20588", "answer": "20589"}
{"prompt": "43629,43630,43631", "answer": "43632"}
{"prompt": "27275,27276,27277,27278,27279,27280,27281,27282", "answer": "27283"}
{"prompt": "1083,1084", "answer": "1085"}
{"prompt": "39386", "answer": "39387"}
{"prompt": "34097,34098,34099,34100,34101,34102,34103,34104,34105", "answer": "34106"}
{"prompt": "19031,19032", "answer": "19033"}
{"prompt": "22159,22160,22161,22162,22163,22164,22165,22166", "answer": "22167"}
{"prompt": "24354,24355,24356", "answer": "24357"}
{"prompt": "12786,12787,12788,12789,12790", "answer": "12791"}
{"prompt": "21039,21040,21041,21042,21043,21044,21045,21046,21047", "answer": "21048"}
{"prompt": "26614,26615,26616,26617", "answer": "26618"}
{"prompt": "17824,17825,17826,17827", "answer": "17828"}
{"prompt": "4448,4449,4450,4451,4452,4453,4454,4455,4456", "answer": "4457"}
{"prompt": "33757,33758", "answer": "33759"}
{"prompt": "33865,33866,33867,33868,33869,33870,33871,33872", "answer": "33873"}
{"prompt": "37575,37576,37577,37578,37579,37580", "answer": "37581"}
{"prompt": "4669,4670,4671", "answer": "4672"}
{"prompt": "7923,7924,7925,7926,7927,7928,7929,7930,7931", "answer": "7932"}
{"prompt": "4011,4012,4013,4014,4015,4016,4017,4018", "answer": "4019"}
{"prompt": "34450,34451,34452,34453,34454,34455,34456,34457,34458,34459", "answer": "34460"}
{"prompt": "34776,34777,34778,34779,34780,34781,34782", "answer": "34783"}
{"prompt": "9422,9423,9424,9425,9426,9427,9428,9429", "answer": "9430"}
{"prompt": "18042,18043,18044", "answer": "18045"}
{"prompt": "38776,38777,38778,38779,38780,38781,38782,38783,38784", "answer": "38785"}
{"prompt": "34180,34181,34182,34183,34184,34185,34186,34187,34188", "answer": "34189"}
{"prompt": "20440,20441,20442,20443,20444,20445,20446", "answer": "20447"}
{"prompt": "32044,32045,32046,32047,32048,32049,32050,32051", "answer": "32052"}
{"prompt": "28920,28921,28922,28923", "answer": "28924"}
{"prompt": "29140,29141,29142,29143,29144,29145,29146,29147,29148", "answer": "29149"}
{"prompt": "32979,32980,32981,32982,32983,32984,32985,32986", "answer": "32987"}
{"prompt": "4199,4200,4201,4202,4203,4204,4205,4206,4207", "answer": "4208"}
{"prompt": "14226,14227,14228,14229,14230,14231", "answer": "14232"}
{"prompt": "5937,5938,5939,5940,5941,5942,5943", "answer": "5944"}
{"prompt": "22477,22478,22479,22480,22481,22482,22483,22484,22485,22486", "answer": "22487"}
{"prompt": "38247", "answer": "38248"}
{"prompt": "19704,19705,19706,19707,19708,19709,19710,19711", "answer": "19712"}
{"prompt": "1349,1350,1351,1352", "answer": "1353"}
{"prompt": "14323,14324,14325,14326", "answer": "14327"}
{"prompt": "13180,13181,13182,13183,13184,13185,13186,13187,13188", "answer": "13189"}
{"prompt": "34858,34859,34860,34861,34862,34863", "answer": "34864"}
{"prompt": "13120,13121,13122,13123", "answer": "13124"}
{"prompt": "28857,28858,28859,28860,28861", "answer": "28862"}
{"prompt": "10764,10765,10766,10767,10768,10769,10770,10771,10772,10773", "answer": "10774"}
{"prompt": "22468,22469,22470,22471,22472,22473,22474,22475,22476,22477", "answer": "22478"}
{"prompt": "35539", "answer": "35540"}
{"prompt": "29115,29116,29117,29118,29119,29120,29121,29122,29123", "answer": "29124"}
{"prompt": "40703,40704,40705,40706,40707,40708,40709,40710,40711,40712", "answer": "40713"}
{"prompt": "43189,43190,43191,43192,43193,43194,43195", "answer": "43196"}
{"prompt": "23077,23078,23079,23080,23081,23082,23083,23084,23085", "answer": "23086"}
{"prompt": "16575", "answer": "16576"}
{"prompt": "97,98,99,100,101,102,103,104,105,106", "answer": "107"}
{"prompt": "9449,9450,9451,9452,9453,9454,9455,9456,9457", "answer": "9458"}
{"prompt": "27445,27446,27447,27448,27449", "answer": "27450"}
{"prompt": "30243,30244,30245,30246,30247,30248", "answer": "30249"}
{"prompt": "1075,1076,1077,1078,1079,1080,1081,1082,1083", "answer": "1084"}
{"prompt": "31267,31268,31269,31270,31271,31272,31273", "answer": "31274"}
{"prompt": "38705,38706,38707,38708", "answer": "38709"}
{"prompt": "37929,37930,37931,37932,37933,37934,37935,37936,37937", "answer": "37938"}
{"prompt": "45221,45222,45223", "answer": "45224"}
{"prompt": "13747,13748,13749,13750,13751", "answer": "13752"}
{"prompt": "5341,5342,5343,5344,5345,5346,5347,5348", "answer": "5349"}
{"prompt": "8702,8703,8704", "answer": "8705"}
{"prompt": "29653,29654", "answer": "29655"}
{"prompt": "13253", "answer": "13254"}
{"prompt": "33468,33469,33470,33471,33472,33473,33474,33475", "answer": "33476"}
{"prompt": "9209,9210,9211,9212,9213,9214", "answer": "9215"}
{"prompt": "13281,13282,13283,13284,13285", "answer": "13286"}
{"prompt": "34245,34246,34247,34248,34249,34250,34251,34252,34253,34254", "answer": "34255"}
{"prompt": "23388,23389,23390,23391,23392,23393,23394,23395", "answer": "23396"}
{"prompt": "8839,8840", "answer": "8841"}
{"prompt": "45044,45045,45046,45047,45048,45049,45050", "answer": "45051"}
{"prompt": "20499,20500,20501,20502,20503,20504,20505,20506,20507,20508", "answer": "20509"}
{"prompt": "11713,11714,11715,11716,11717,11718,11719,11720,11721", "answer": "11722"}
{"prompt": "21134,21135", "answer": "21136"}
{"prompt": "38191,38192,38193,38194,38195,38196,38197,38198", "answer": "38199"}
{"prompt": "34437,34438", "answer": "34439"}
{"prompt": "13470,13471,13472,13473,13474,13475", "answer": "13476"}
{"prompt": "40823,40824,40825,40826,40827,40828", "answer": "40829"}
{"prompt": "20902", "answer": "20903"}
{"prompt": "30990,30991", "answer": "30992"}
{"prompt": "12822,12823,12824,12825,12826,12827,12828,12829", "answer": "12830"}
{"prompt": "38579,38580,38581,38582", "answer": "38583"}
{"prompt": "17082,17083,17084,17085,17086,17087,17088,17089,17090,17091", "answer": "17092"}
{"prompt": "42,43,44,45", "answer": "46"}
{"prompt": "17367,17368,17369,17370,17371", "answer": "17372"}
{"prompt": "13481", "answer": "13482"}
{"prompt": "33657,33658,33659,33660,33661,33662,33663,33664,33665", "answer": "33666"}
{"prompt": "22367,22368,22369,22370,22371", "answer": "22372"}
{"prompt": "25920,25921,25922,25923,25924,25925", "answer": "25926"}
{"prompt": "39160,39161,39162,39163,39164,39165,39166,39167,39168,39169", "answer": "39170"}
{"prompt": "24940,24941,24942", "answer": "24943"}
{"prompt": "36180,36181,36182,36183,36184,36185,36186,36187,36188", "answer": "36189"}
{"prompt": "34427,34428,34429,34430,34431", "answer": "34432"}
{"prompt": "998", "answer": "999"}
{"prompt": "2180,2181,2182,2183,2184,2185,2186,2187", "answer": "2188"}
{"prompt": "18553,18554,18555,18556,18557,18558,18559,18560", "answer": "18561"}
{"prompt": "19913", "answer": "19914"}
{"prompt": "29469,29470,29471", "answer": "29472"}
{"prompt": "14725,14726,14727,14728,14729,14730,14731,14732,14733,14734", "answer": "14735"}
{"prompt": "6123,6124,6125,6126,6127,6128,6129,6130,6131", "answer": "6132"}
{"prompt": "16236,16237,16238,16239,16240,16241,16242,16243,16244", "answer": "16245"}
{"prompt": "27918,27919,27920", "answer": "27921"}
{"prompt": "22790,22791,22792,22793", "answer": "22794"}
{"prompt": "31499,31500,31501,31502,31503,31504", "answer": "31505"}
{"prompt": "29240,29241,29242", "answer": "29243"}
{"prompt": "10926,10927,10928,10929,10930,10931,10932,10933,10934,10935", "answer": "10936"}
{"prompt": "2847", "answer": "2848"}
{"prompt": "34431", "answer": "34432"}
{"prompt": "38276,38277,38278,38279", "answer": "38280"}
{"prompt": "28434,28435,28436,28437,28438,28439,28440,28441", "answer": "28442"}
{"prompt": "6326,6327,6328", "answer": "6329"}
{"prompt": "26015,26016,26017,26018,26019,26020", "answer": "26021"}
{"prompt": "13841,13842,13843,13844,13845,13846,13847", "answer": "13848"}
{"prompt": "41445", "answer": "41446"}
{"prompt": "43404,43405,43406,43407,43408,43409,43410,43411,43412,43413", "answer": "43414"}
{"prompt": "146,147,148,149,150,151", "answer": "152"}
{"prompt": "1340,1341,1342,1343,1344,1345", "answer": "1346"}
{"prompt": "20713,20714,20715,20716", "answer": "20717"}
{"prompt": "1553,1554,1555,1556", "answer": "1557"}
{"prompt": "35332,35333,35334,35335,35336", "answer": "35337"}
{"prompt": "4374,4375,4376,4377,4378,4379,4380", "answer": "4381"}
{"prompt": "25834,25835", "answer": "25836"}
{"prompt": "38624,38625,38626,38627,38628,38629", "answer": "38630"}
{"prompt": "2802,2803,2804,2805,2806,2807,2808,2809", "answer": "2810"}
{"prompt": "41990,41991,41992,41993,41994,41995,41996,41997,41998,41999", "answer": "42000"}
{"prompt": "6914,6915,6916,6917,6918,6919,6920,6921,6922,6923", "answer": "6924"}
{"prompt": "17293,17294,17295,17296,17297,17298,17299,17300,17301,17302", "answer": "17303"}
{"prompt": "1308,1309,1310,1311,1312,1313,1314", "answer": "1315"}
{"prompt": "35838,35839,35840,35841,35842", "answer": "35843"}
{"prompt": "41030,41031,41032,41033,41034,41035,41036,41037,41038,41039", "answer": "41040"}
{"prompt": "35197,35198,35199,35200,35201,35202,35203,35204", "answer": "35205"}
{"prompt": "27847,27848,27849,27850,27851,27852,27853,27854,27855", "answer": "27856"}
{"prompt": "40747,40748,40749,40750,40751", "answer": "40752"}
{"prompt": "15185,15186", "answer": "15187"}
{"prompt": "41356,41357", "answer": "41358"}
{"prompt": "26687,26688,26689,26690,26691,26692", "answer": "26693"}
{"prompt": "19334,19335,19336,19337,19338", "answer": "19339"}
{"prompt": "9466,9467,9468,9469,9470", "answer": "9471"}
{"prompt": "36979,36980,36981,36982,36983,36984,36985,36986,36987,36988", "answer": "36989"}
{"prompt": "26788,26789,26790,26791,26792,26793,26794,26795", "answer": "26796"}
{"prompt": "40189", "answer": "40190"}
{"prompt": "18412,18413,18414,18415,18416", "answer": "18417"}
{"prompt": "41408", "answer": "41409"}
{"prompt": "31000,31001,31002", "answer": "31003"}
{"prompt": "8343,8344,8345,8346,8347,8348", "answer": "8349"}
{"prompt": "31997,31998,31999,32000,32001,32002,32003,32004", "answer": "32005"}
{"prompt": "22880,22881,22882", "answer": "22883"}
{"prompt": "5228,5229,5230,5231", "answer": "5232"}
{"prompt": "9078,9079,9080,9081", "answer": "9082"}
{"prompt": "21486,21487,21488,21489,21490", "answer": "21491"}
{"prompt": "17533", "answer": "17534"}
{"prompt": "4850,4851,4852,4853,4854,4855", "answer": "4856"}
{"prompt": "34514,34515,34516,34517", "answer": "34518"}
{"prompt": "6419", "answer": "6420"}
{"prompt": "2364,2365,2366,2367,2368,2369,2370,2371,2372", "answer": "2373"}
{"prompt": "6345,6346", "answer": "6347"}
{"prompt": "30989,30990", "answer": "30991"}
{"prompt": "27265,27266,27267,27268,27269,27270,27271", "answer": "27272"}
{"prompt": "7880", "answer": "7881"}
{"prompt": "18165,18166,18167,18168,18169", "answer": "18170"}
{"prompt": "33792,33793,33794,33795,33796,33797,33798,33799,33800", "answer": "33801"}
{"prompt": "9536,9537,9538,9539,9540,9541,9542,9543,9544", "answer": "9545"}
{"prompt": "15038,15039,15040,15041,15042,15043,15044", "answer": "15045"}
{"prompt": "34553,34554,34555,34556", "answer": "34557"}
{"prompt": "6217,6218", "answer": "6219"}
{"prompt": "6952,6953,6954,6955,6956,6957,6958,6959", "answer": "6960"}
{"prompt": "13061,13062,13063,13064,13065,13066,13067,13068,13069", "answer": "13070"}
{"prompt": "5023,5024,5025,5026,5027", "answer": "5028"}
{"prompt": "12581,12582,12583,12584,12585,12586,12587", "answer": "12588"}
{"prompt": "29751,29752,29753,29754", "answer": "29755"}
{"prompt": "639,640,641,642", "answer": "643"}
{"prompt": "29157,29158,29159", "answer": "29160"}
{"prompt": "24017,24018,24019,24020,24021,24022,24023,24024,24025", "answer": "24026"}
{"prompt": "33265,33266,33267,33268,33269,33270", "answer": "33271"}
{"prompt": "35612,35613,35614,35615,35616,35617,35618,35619", "answer": "35620"}
{"prompt": "37511,37512", "answer": "37513"}
{"prompt": "30874,30875,30876,30877,30878,30879,30880,30881,30882,30883", "answer": "30884"}
{"prompt": "5615,5616", "answer": "5617"}
{"prompt": "44704,44705", "answer": "44706"}
{"prompt": "10731,10732,10733,10734,10735,10736,10737,10738,10739,10740", "answer": "10741"}
{"prompt": "35416,35417,35418,35419,35420,35421,35422", "answer": "35423"}
{"prompt": "169", "answer": "170"}
{"prompt": "43316,43317,43318", "answer": "43319"}
{"prompt": "18845,18846,18847,18848,18849,18850,18851,18852,18853,18854", "answer": "18855"}
{"prompt": "23096,23097,23098,23099,23100,23101,23102,23103,23104,23105", "answer": "23106"}
{"prompt": "557", "answer": "558"}
{"prompt": "10339", "answer": "10340"}
{"prompt": "28274,28275,28276,28277,28278", "answer": "28279"}
{"prompt": "44360", "answer": "44361"}
{"prompt": "28884,28885,28886,28887", "answer": "28888"}
{"prompt": "8494,8495,8496,8497,8498,8499,8500,8501,8502,8503", "answer": "8504"}
{"prompt": "12295,12296,12297,12298", "answer": "12299"}
{"prompt": "33252,33253,33254", "answer": "33255"}
{"prompt": "14113,14114,14115,14116,14117,14118,14119,14120,14121", "answer": "14122"}
{"prompt": "35800,35801,35802,35803,35804", "answer": "35805"}
{"prompt": "29812,29813,29814,29815,29816,29817,29818,29819", "answer": "29820"}
{"prompt": "6253,6254,6255,6256,6257,6258,6259", "answer": "6260"}
{"prompt": "42102,42103,42104,42105,42106,42107,42108,42109,42110", "answer": "42111"}
{"prompt": "29089,29090,29091", "answer": "29092"}
{"prompt": "4875,4876,4877", "answer": "4878"}
{"prompt": "5677,5678,5679,5680,5681,5682", "answer": "5683"}
{"prompt": "33935,33936,33937,33938,33939,33940,33941,33942", "answer": "33943"}
{"prompt": "18931,18932,18933", "answer": "18934"}
{"prompt": "37210,37211,37212", "answer": "37213"}
{"prompt": "919,920,921", "answer": "922"}
{"prompt": "23910,23911,23912,23913,23914,23915,23916,23917,23918,23919", "answer": "23920"}
{"prompt": "37465", "answer": "37466"}
{"prompt": "27305,27306,27307,27308,27309,27310,27311,27312,27313,27314", "answer": "27315"}
{"prompt": "24845,24846", "answer": "24847"}
{"prompt": "43048,43049,43050,43051,43052,43053", "answer": "43054"}
{"prompt": "17001", "answer": "17002"}
{"prompt": "40478,40479,40480,40481,40482,40483,40484,40485,40486", "answer": "40487"}
{"prompt": "9700,9701,9702,9703,9704,9705", "answer": "9706"}
{"prompt": "32100,32101,32102,32103,32104,32105,32106,32107,32108,32109", "answer": "32110"}
{"prompt": "9559,9560,9561,9562,9563", "answer": "9564"}
{"prompt": "31160,31161,31162,31163,31164,31165,31166,31167,31168,31169", "answer": "31170"}
{"prompt": "31657,31658,31659,31660,31661,31662", "answer": "31663"}
{"prompt": "15874,15875,15876,15877,15878,15879,15880,15881", "answer": "15882"}
{"prompt": "21367,21368,21369,21370,21371,21372,21373,21374,21375", "answer": "21376"}
{"prompt": "33201,33202,33203", "answer": "33204"}
{"prompt": "18300", "answer": "18301"}
{"prompt": "11067", "answer": "11068"}
{"prompt": "16570,16571,16572,16573,16574,16575", "answer": "16576"}
{"prompt": "43492,43493,43494,43495,43496,43497,43498,43499,43500,43501", "answer": "43502"}
{"prompt": "30840,30841,30842,30843,30844", "answer": "30845"}
{"prompt": "30512,30513,30514,30515,30516,30517,30518,30519,30520", "answer": "30521"}
{"prompt": "14983,14984,14985,14986,14987,14988,14989,14990,14991,14992", "answer": "14993"}
{"prompt": "38125,38126,38127,38128,38129,38130,38131,38132,38133,38134", "answer": "38135"}
{"prompt": "22151,22152", "answer": "22153"}
{"prompt": "28943,28944,28945,28946,28947", "answer": "28948"}
{"prompt": "28477,28478,28479,28480,28481", "answer": "28482"}
{"prompt": "14853,14854,14855,14856,14857,14858,14859,14860,14861,14862", "answer": "14863"}
{"prompt": "13367,13368,13369,13370,13371,13372,13373,13374,13375", "answer": "13376"}
{"prompt": "5434,5435,5436,5437,5438,5439,5440", "answer": "5441"}
{"prompt": "32215,32216,32217,32218,32219,32220,32221", "answer": "32222"}
{"prompt": "11896,11897,11898,11899,11900,11901,11902,11903,11904,11905", "answer": "11906"}
{"prompt": "20777,20778,20779,20780,20781,20782", "answer": "20783"}
{"prompt": "12527,12528,12529,12530,12531,12532,12533", "answer": "12534"}
{"prompt": "36189,36190,36191,36192,36193,36194,36195,36196,36197", "answer": "36198"}
{"prompt": "1947,1948,1949,1950,1951", "answer": "1952"}
{"prompt": "34279,34280,34281,34282,34283,34284,34285", "answer": "34286"}
{"prompt": "33037,33038,33039,33040,33041,33042,33043,33044", "answer": "33045"}
{"prompt": "7328,7329", "answer": "7330"}
{"prompt": "12676,12677", "answer": "12678"}
{"prompt": "24239,24240,24241,24242,24243,24244,24245,24246,24247,24248", "answer": "24249"}
{"prompt": "11689,11690,11691,11692", "answer": "11693"}
{"prompt": "24109", "answer": "24110"}
{"prompt": "20945", "answer": "20946"}
{"prompt": "1202,1203,1204,1205,1206,1207,1208,1209,1210,1211", "answer": "1212"}
{"prompt": "6849,6850", "answer": "6851"}
{"prompt": "16504,16505,16506", "answer": "16507"}
{"prompt": "42059,42060,42061,42062", "answer": "42063"}
{"prompt": "18666,18667,18668,18669,18670", "answer": "18671"}
{"prompt": "16482,16483,16484,16485", "answer": "16486"}
{"prompt": "6366,6367,6368,6369,6370,6371,6372", "answer": "6373"}
{"prompt": "37327,37328,37329,37330,37331,37332,37333,37334", "answer": "37335"}
{"prompt": "18742", "answer": "18743"}
{"prompt": "44109,44110", "answer": "44111"}
{"prompt": "17424,17425,17426,17427,17428,17429,17430,17431", "answer": "17432"}
{"prompt": "16614,16615,16616,16617,16618,16619,16620,16621,16622,16623", "answer": "16624"}
{"prompt": "38280,38281,38282,38283,38284", "answer": "38285"}
{"prompt": "42089,42090,42091", "answer": "42092"}
{"prompt": "10701,10702,10703", "answer": "10704"}
{"prompt": "33550,33551,33552,33553,33554,33555,33556", "answer": "33557"}
{"prompt": "8176,8177,8178,8179,8180,8181,8182,8183,8184", "answer": "8185"}
{"prompt": "17257,17258,17259,17260,17261", "answer": "17262"}
{"prompt": "19872,19873", "answer": "19874"}
{"prompt": "30375,30376,30377,30378,30379,30380,30381,30382", "answer": "30383"}
{"prompt": "20641,20642,20643", "answer": "20644"}
{"prompt": "22109,22110,22111,22112,22113", "answer": "22114"}
{"prompt": "334,335,336,337", "answer": "338"}
{"prompt": "14439,14440", "answer": "14441"}
{"prompt": "3094,3095,3096", "answer": "3097"}
{"prompt": "38243,38244", "answer": "38245"}
{"prompt": "7025,7026", "answer": "7027"}
{"prompt": "8765,8766,8767,8768,8769,8770,8771,8772", "answer": "8773"}
{"prompt": "7074,7075,7076,7077,7078,7079,7080,7081,7082", "answer": "7083"}
{"prompt": "23267,23268", "answer": "23269"}
{"prompt": "2451,2452,2453,2454", "answer": "2455"}
{"prompt": "43651,43652,43653,43654,43655,43656,43657,43658", "answer": "43659"}
{"prompt": "44692", "answer": "44693"}
{"prompt": "40539,40540,40541,40542,40543,40544,40545", "answer": "40546"}
{"prompt": "40233,40234,40235", "answer": "40236"}
{"prompt": "17682,17683,17684,17685,17686", "answer": "17687"}
{"prompt": "2667,2668,2669,2670", "answer": "2671"}
{"prompt": "12426,12427,12428,12429,12430,12431,12432,12433,12434", "answer": "12435"}
{"prompt": "23708,23709,23710,23711,23712,23713,23714,23715,23716", "answer": "23717"}
{"prompt": "22371,22372,22373", "answer": "22374"}
{"prompt": "16801,16802,16803,16804,16805,16806", "answer": "16807"}
{"prompt": "23061,23062,23063,23064,23065", "answer": "23066"}
{"prompt": "44239,44240,44241,44242,44243,44244,44245,44246,44247,44248", "answer": "44249"}
{"prompt": "39219,39220,39221,39222,39223,39224,39225,39226,39227", "answer": "39228"}
{"prompt": "13116,13117,13118,13119,13120", "answer": "13121"}
{"prompt": "30422,30423,30424,30425,30426", "answer": "30427"}
{"prompt": "44950,44951,44952,44953,44954,44955", "answer": "44956"}
{"prompt": "34807,34808", "answer": "34809"}
{"prompt": "10522,10523,10524,10525,10526,10527", "answer": "10528"}
{"prompt": "40126,40127", "answer": "40128"}
{"prompt": "25766,25767", "answer": "25768"}
{"prompt": "40022,40023,40024", "answer": "40025"}
{"prompt": "36288,36289,36290,36291,36292,36293,36294,36295", "answer": "36296"}
{"prompt": "9961,9962,9963,9964", "answer": "9965"}
{"prompt": "38220,38221,38222,38223,38224,38225", "answer": "38226"}
{"prompt": "27348,27349,27350,27351,27352,27353,27354,27355,27356,27357", "answer": "27358"}
{"prompt": "25482,25483,25484,25485,25486,25487,25488,25489,25490,25491", "answer": "25492"}
{"prompt": "25222,25223,25224,25225,25226,25227,25228,25229", "answer": "25230"}
{"prompt": "20735,20736,20737", "answer": "20738"}
{"prompt": "44306,44307,44308,44309", "answer": "44310"}
{"prompt": "2886,2887,2888,2889,2890,2891,2892,2893", "answer": "2894"}
{"prompt": "41043,41044,41045,41046", "answer": "41047"}
{"prompt": "27022,27023,27024,27025,27026,27027,27028,27029,27030", "answer": "27031"}
{"prompt": "1769,1770,1771,1772,1773,1774,1775,1776", "answer": "1777"}
{"prompt": "5628", "answer": "5629"}
{"prompt": "5378,5379,5380,5381", "answer": "5382"}
{"prompt": "42156,42157,42158,42159,42160", "answer": "42161"}
{"prompt": "37580", "answer": "37581"}
{"prompt": "27894,27895,27896,27897,27898,27899,27900", "answer": "27901"}
{"prompt": "8810,8811,8812,8813,8814,8815,8816,8817,8818", "answer": "8819"}
{"prompt": "8287,8288,8289,8290,8291,8292,8293,8294,8295", "answer": "8296"}
{"prompt": "15473,15474,15475", "answer": "15476"}
{"prompt": "41703,41704,41705,41706,41707,41708,41709,41710,41711,41712", "answer": "41713"}
{"prompt": "44606,44607,44608,44609", "answer": "44610"}
{"prompt": "5828", "answer": "5829"}
{"prompt": "19464", "answer": "19465"}
{"prompt": "21167,21168,21169,21170,21171", "answer": "21172"}
{"prompt": "6716,6717,6718", "answer": "6719"}
{"prompt": "1161,1162,1163,1164,1165,1166,1167,1168", "answer": "1169"}
{"prompt": "15682,15683,15684,15685", "answer": "15686"}
{"prompt": "5693,5694,5695,5696,5697", "answer": "5698"}
{"prompt": "3911,3912,3913,3914,3915,3916,3917,3918,3919", "answer": "3920"}
{"prompt": "2742,2743,2744,2745,2746,2747,2748", "answer": "2749"}
{"prompt": "44915,44916,44917", "answer": "44918"}
{"prompt": "3725,3726,3727,3728,3729,3730,3731,3732,3733", "answer": "3734"}
{"prompt": "31297,31298,31299,31300,31301,31302,31303,31304", "answer": "31305"}
{"prompt": "16768,16769,16770,16771,16772,16773,16774,16775,16776,16777", "answer": "16778"}
{"prompt": "22743,22744,22745,22746,22747,22748,22749,22750,22751", "answer": "22752"}
{"prompt": "33203,33204,33205,33206,33207,33208,33209,33210,33211,33212", "answer": "33213"}
{"prompt": "34906,34907,34908,34909,34910", "answer": "34911"}
{"prompt": "41342,41343,41344,41345,41346,41347,41348", "answer": "41349"}
{"prompt": "6139,6140,6141,6142,6143,6144", "answer": "6145"}
{"prompt": "36120,36121,36122,36123,36124,36125,36126,36127", "answer": "36128"}
{"prompt": "16159,16160,16161,16162,16163,16164,16165,16166,16167,16168", "answer": "16169"}
{"prompt": "44483", "answer": "44484"}
{"prompt": "17075,17076", "answer": "17077"}
{"prompt": "41192,41193,41194,41195", "answer": "41196"}
{"prompt": "28224,28225,28226,28227,28228", "answer": "28229"}
{"prompt": "1526,1527,1528", "answer": "1529"}
{"prompt": "32109,32110,32111,32112,32113,32114", "answer": "32115"}
{"prompt": "23407,23408,23409,23410", "answer": "23411"}
{"prompt": "42376,42377,42378,42379,42380,42381,42382,42383", "answer": "42384"}
{"prompt": "34176,34177,34178", "answer": "34179"}
{"prompt": "618,619,620,621,622", "answer": "623"}
{"prompt": "32910,32911,32912,32913,32914,32915,32916,32917,32918", "answer": "32919"}
{"prompt": "35999,36000", "answer": "36001"}
{"prompt": "13809,13810,13811,13812,13813,13814,13815", "answer": "13816"}
{"prompt": "30798,30799", "answer": "30800"}
{"prompt": "19627,19628,19629,19630,19631", "answer": "19632"}
{"prompt": "14360,14361,14362,14363,14364,14365,14366", "answer": "14367"}
{"prompt": "43961,43962,43963,43964", "answer": "43965"}
{"prompt": "11436", "answer": "11437"}
{"prompt": "21933", "answer": "21934"}
{"prompt": "9041,9042,9043,9044,9045,9046,9047,9048,9049,9050", "answer": "9051"}
{"prompt": "17261,17262,17263,17264,17265,17266,17267,17268,17269,17270", "answer": "17271"}
{"prompt": "19812", "answer": "19813"}
{"prompt": "22207,22208,22209,22210,22211,22212,22213,22214,22215,22216", "answer": "22217"}
{"prompt": "25401,25402,25403,25404,25405,25406,25407,25408,25409,25410", "answer": "25411"}
{"prompt": "32991,32992,32993,32994,32995,32996,32997,32998,32999", "answer": "33000"}
{"prompt": "4549,4550,4551,4552,4553,4554,4555,4556", "answer": "4557"}
{"prompt": "37575", "answer": "37576"}
{"prompt": "38250,38251,38252,38253,38254,38255,38256,38257", "answer": "38258"}
{"prompt": "22385,22386,22387,22388,22389,22390,22391,22392,22393,22394", "answer": "22395"}
{"prompt": "2748,2749,2750,2751,2752,2753,2754,2755,2756,2757", "answer": "2758"}
{"prompt": "3627,3628,3629,3630,3631,3632,3633,3634", "answer": "3635"}
{"prompt": "15020,15021", "answer": "15022"}
{"prompt": "14668,14669,14670", "answer": "14671"}
{"prompt": "38917", "answer": "38918"}
{"prompt": "36698,36699,36700,36701,36702,36703", "answer": "36704"}
{"prompt": "42786,42787,42788,42789,42790,42791", "answer": "42792"}
{"prompt": "2840,2841,2842,2843,2844,2845,2846,2847", "answer": "2848"}
{"prompt": "14477,14478,14479,14480,14481,14482", "answer": "14483"}
{"prompt": "36800,36801,36802,36803,36804,36805,36806", "answer": "36807"}
{"prompt": "12731,12732,12733,12734,12735,12736,12737", "answer": "12738"}
{"prompt": "14025,14026,14027,14028,14029", "answer": "14030"}
{"prompt": "5083,5084,5085,5086,5087,5088", "answer": "5089"}
{"prompt": "34606,34607,34608", "answer": "34609"}
{"prompt": "12493", "answer": "12494"}
{"prompt": "23752,23753,23754,23755,23756,23757", "answer": "23758"}
{"prompt": "27831,27832", "answer": "27833"}
{"prompt": "39104,39105,39106,39107,39108,39109", "answer": "39110"}
{"prompt": "36748", "answer": "36749"}
{"prompt": "401,402,403", "answer": "404"}
{"prompt": "8216,8217,8218,8219,8220,8221", "answer": "8222"}
{"prompt": "17487,17488,17489,17490,17491,17492,17493,17494,17495", "answer": "17496"}
{"prompt": "26829,26830,26831,26832,26833", "answer": "26834"}
{"prompt": "42624,42625,42626,42627", "answer": "42628"}
{"prompt": "9650", "answer": "9651"}
{"prompt": "17378,17379,17380,17381,17382,17383,17384,17385,17386", "answer": "17387"}
{"prompt": "20251,20252,20253,20254,20255", "answer": "20256"}
{"prompt": "12345,12346,12347,12348,12349,12350", "answer": "12351"}
{"prompt": "43991", "answer": "43992"}
{"prompt": "43395,43396,43397,43398,43399,43400,43401,43402,43403,43404", "answer": "43405"}
{"prompt": "33890,33891,33892", "answer": "33893"}
{"prompt": "18263,18264,18265,18266,18267", "answer": "18268"}
{"prompt": "3984,3985,3986,3987,3988", "answer": "3989"}
{"prompt": "39746,39747,39748", "answer": "39749"}
{"prompt": "43944", "answer": "43945"}
{"prompt": "23187,23188,23189,23190,23191,23192,23193,23194,23195,23196", "answer": "23197"}
{"prompt": "28887,28888", "answer": "28889"}
{"prompt": "27066,27067,27068,27069,27070,27071,27072", "answer": "27073"}
{"prompt": "14567,14568,14569,14570,14571", "answer": "14572"}
{"prompt": "21826,21827,21828", "answer": "21829"}
{"prompt": "15554,15555,15556,15557,15558,15559,15560,15561,15562,15563", "answer": "15564"}
{"prompt": "16814,16815,16816,16817,16818,16819,16820,16821", "answer": "16822"}
{"prompt": "36703,36704,36705,36706,36707", "answer": "36708"}
{"prompt": "18287,18288,18289", "answer": "18290"}
{"prompt": "12222", "answer": "12223"}
{"prompt": "24116,24117,24118,24119,24120,24121", "answer": "24122"}
{"prompt": "35978,35979,35980,35981,35982", "answer": "35983"}
{"prompt": "26636", "answer": "26637"}
{"prompt": "2543,2544,2545,2546,2547,2548,2549", "answer": "2550"}
{"prompt": "23927,23928,23929,23930", "answer": "23931"}
{"prompt": "3922,3923,3924", "answer": "3925"}
{"prompt": "5684,5685,5686,5687,5688,5689,5690,5691,5692,5693", "answer": "5694"}
{"prompt": "25446,25447,25448,25449,25450,25451,25452,25453,25454", "answer": "25455"}
{"prompt": "41674,41675,41676,41677,41678,41679", "answer": "41680"}
{"prompt": "37682,37683,37684,37685,37686,37687,37688", "answer": "37689"}
{"prompt": "14833,14834,14835,14836", "answer": "14837"}
{"prompt": "14374,14375", "answer": "14376"}
{"prompt": "16043,16044", "answer": "16045"}
{"prompt": "29712,29713", "answer": "29714"}
{"prompt": "31181,31182", "answer": "31183"}
{"prompt": "44421,44422,44423,44424,44425,44426", "answer": "44427"}
{"prompt": "26604,26605,26606,26607,26608,26609", "answer": "26610"}
{"prompt": "11593,11594,11595,11596,11597,11598,11599,11600,11601", "answer": "11602"}
{"prompt": "14695,14696,14697,14698,14699,14700", "answer": "14701"}
{"prompt": "30187,30188,30189,30190,30191,30192,30193,30194,30195", "answer": "30196"}
{"prompt": "13694,13695,13696,13697,13698,13699,13700,13701,13702,13703", "answer": "13704"}
{"prompt": "16244", "answer": "16245"}
{"prompt": "17604,17605", "answer": "17606"}
{"prompt": "35939,35940,35941,35942,35943,35944,35945,35946,35947,35948", "answer": "35949"}
{"prompt": "23133,23134,23135,23136,23137,23138,23139", "answer": "23140"}
{"prompt": "24363,24364,24365,24366,24367", "answer": "24368"}
{"prompt": "13389,13390", "answer": "13391"}
{"prompt": "18933,18934", "answer": "18935"}
{"prompt": "36783,36784,36785", "answer": "36786"}
{"prompt": "23549,23550,23551,23552,23553,23554,23555,23556,23557,23558", "answer": "23559"}
{"prompt": "9922", "answer": "9923"}
{"prompt": "13572,13573,13574,13575", "answer": "13576"}
{"prompt": "2386,2387,2388,2389,2390,2391,2392,2393", "answer": "2394"}
{"prompt": "25351,25352,25353,25354,25355,25356,25357,25358", "answer": "25359"}
{"prompt": "45152,45153,45154,45155,45156", "answer": "45157"}
{"prompt": "6047,6048,6049,6050,6051,6052,6053", "answer": "6054"}
{"prompt": "31140,31141", "answer": "31142"}
{"prompt": "19597,19598,19599,19600,19601,19602,19603,19604", "answer": "19605"}
{"prompt": "43744,43745,43746,43747,43748,43749", "answer": "43750"}
{"prompt": "18442,18443,18444,18445,18446", "answer": "18447"}
{"prompt": "35450,35451,35452,35453", "answer": "35454"}
{"prompt": "8230,8231", "answer": "8232"}
{"prompt": "8399", "answer": "8400"}
{"prompt": "13781,13782,13783,13784,13785", "answer": "13786"}
{"prompt": "8549,8550,8551,8552,8553,8554", "answer": "8555"}
{"prompt": "7775,7776,7777,7778,7779,7780", "answer": "7781"}
{"prompt": "16434,16435,16436,16437,16438,16439", "answer": "16440"}
{"prompt": "30062,30063,30064,30065,30066,30067,30068", "answer": "30069"}
{"prompt": "7555,7556,7557,7558", "answer": "7559"}
{"prompt": "17461,17462,17463,17464,17465,17466,17467,17468,17469,17470", "answer": "17471"}
{"prompt": "33973,33974,33975,33976,33977,33978,33979,33980,33981,33982", "answer": "33983"}
{"prompt": "6542,6543,6544,6545,6546,6547,6548", "answer": "6549"}
{"prompt": "36188,36189", "answer": "36190"}
{"prompt": "34782,34783,34784,34785", "answer": "34786"}
{"prompt": "2232", "answer": "2233"}
{"prompt": "7481,7482,7483", "answer": "7484"}
{"prompt": "18333,18334,18335,18336,18337", "answer": "18338"}
{"prompt": "4182,4183,4184,4185,4186,4187,4188,4189", "answer": "4190"}
{"prompt": "26998,26999,27000", "answer": "27001"}
{"prompt": "23781,23782,23783,23784,23785,23786", "answer": "23787"}
{"prompt": "21545,21546,21547,21548", "answer": "21549"}
{"prompt": "39452,39453", "answer": "39454"}
{"prompt": "41393,41394", "answer": "41395"}
{"prompt": "8530,8531,8532,8533,8534,8535,8536,8537,8538,8539", "answer": "8540"}
{"prompt": "33237,33238", "answer": "33239"}
{"prompt": "34476,34477,34478,34479,34480,34481,34482,34483,34484,34485", "answer": "34486"}
{"prompt": "40262,40263,40264,40265,40266,40267,40268,40269,40270", "answer": "40271"}
{"prompt": "15099,15100,15101,15102,15103,15104,15105,15106,15107,15108", "answer": "15109"}
{"prompt": "8028,8029,8030,8031,8032,8033,8034,8035,8036", "answer": "8037"}
{"prompt": "19016,19017,19018", "answer": "19019"}
{"prompt": "41654,41655,41656,41657,41658,41659", "answer": "41660"}
{"prompt": "43105", "answer": "43106"}
{"prompt": "2894,2895,2896,2897,2898,2899,2900,2901,2902,2903", "answer": "2904"}
{"prompt": "31990,31991,31992,31993,31994,31995,31996,31997", "answer": "31998"}
{"prompt": "24435,24436,24437,24438,24439", "answer": "24440"}
{"prompt": "29754,29755,29756", "answer": "29757"}
{"prompt": "30445,30446,30447,30448,30449,30450,30451,30452,30453,30454", "answer": "30455"}
{"prompt": "38651,38652,38653,38654,38655,38656,38657", "answer": "38658"}
{"prompt": "3179,3180,3181,3182,3183,3184,3185,3186", "answer": "3187"}
{"prompt": "21835,21836,21837", "answer": "21838"}
{"prompt": "31305,31306,31307,31308,31309,31310,31311,31312,31313,31314", "answer": "31315"}
{"prompt": "25029,25030,25031,25032,25033,25034,25035", "answer": "25036"}
{"prompt": "2614,2615,2616,2617,2618,2619,2620,2621", "answer": "2622"}
{"prompt": "4117,4118,4119,4120,4121,4122,4123,4124,4125,4126", "answer": "4127"}
{"prompt": "30613,30614,30615,30616,30617,30618", "answer": "30619"}
{"prompt": "37431,37432,37433,37434,37435", "answer": "37436"}
{"prompt": "10055,10056,10057,10058,10059,10060,10061,10062,10063", "answer": "10064"}
{"prompt": "42910,42911,42912,42913", "answer": "42914"}
{"prompt": "33621,33622,33623,33624,33625,33626,33627", "answer": "33628"}
{"prompt": "36898,36899,36900", "answer": "36901"}
{"prompt": "17060,17061,17062,17063,17064", "answer": "17065"}
{"prompt": "8898,8899,8900,8901,8902,8903,8904", "answer": "8905"}
{"prompt": "32551,32552,32553,32554", "answer": "32555"}
{"prompt": "37615,37616,37617,37618,37619", "answer": "37620"}
{"prompt": "42359,42360,42361,42362,42363,42364,42365,42366,42367", "answer": "42368"}
{"prompt": "28339,28340,28341,28342,28343,28344,28345,28346", "answer": "28347"}
{"prompt": "27809,27810,27811,27812", "answer": "27813"}
{"prompt": "4650,4651,4652,4653,4654,4655,4656,4657", "answer": "4658"}
{"prompt": "27127,27128,27129,27130,27131", "answer": "27132"}
{"prompt": "42282,42283,42284,42285,42286,42287", "answer": "42288"}
{"prompt": "29794,29795,29796,29797,29798,29799,29800,29801,29802,29803", "answer": "29804"}
{"prompt": "4384,4385", "answer": "4386"}
{"prompt": "37659,37660,37661", "answer": "37662"}
{"prompt": "16909,16910,16911,16912,16913,16914,16915,16916,16917,16918", "answer": "16919"}
{"prompt": "27422,27423,27424,27425,27426,27427,27428,27429", "answer": "27430"}
{"prompt": "30684,30685", "answer": "30686"}
{"prompt": "10580,10581,10582,10583,10584,10585,10586", "answer": "10587"}
{"prompt": "14532,14533,14534,14535,14536,14537,14538,14539", "answer": "14540"}
{"prompt": "40621,40622,40623", "answer": "40624"}
{"prompt": "39622,39623,39624,39625,39626,39627,39628", "answer": "39629"}
{"prompt": "29847,29848,29849,29850,29851,29852,29853", "answer": "29854"}
{"prompt": "1236,1237,1238,1239,1240,1241,1242,1243,1244", "answer": "1245"}
{"prompt": "32064", "answer": "32065"}
{"prompt": "27431,27432,27433", "answer": "27434"}
{"prompt": "14573,14574,14575,14576,14577", "answer": "14578"}
{"prompt": "44943,44944,44945,44946,44947,44948,44949,44950", "answer": "44951"}
{"prompt": "110,111,112", "answer": "113"}
{"prompt": "14339,14340,14341", "answer": "14342"}
{"prompt": "36013,36014,36015,36016,36017", "answer": "36018"}
{"prompt": "8667,8668,8669,8670,8671,8672", "answer": "8673"}
{"prompt": "3820,3821,3822", "answer": "3823"}
{"prompt": "5328", "answer": "5329"}
{"prompt": "36612,36613,36614,36615,36616", "answer": "36617"}
{"prompt": "13924,13925,13926", "answer": "13927"}
{"prompt": "20155,20156,20157,20158,20159", "answer": "20160"}
{"prompt": "6306,6307,6308", "answer": "6309"}
{"prompt": "26074,26075,26076,26077", "answer": "26078"}
{"prompt": "31898,31899,31900,31901,31902", "answer": "31903"}
{"prompt": "2321,2322,2323,2324,2325,2326,2327,2328", "answer": "2329"}
{"prompt": "19203,19204,19205,19206,19207,19208,19209,19210,19211", "answer": "19212"}
{"prompt": "20902,20903,20904,20905,20906,20907,20908,20909,20910", "answer": "20911"}
{"prompt": "30342,30343,30344,30345,30346", "answer": "30347"}
{"prompt": "28549,28550", "answer": "28551"}
{"prompt": "5960,5961,5962,5963,5964", "answer": "5965"}
{"prompt": "25596", "answer": "25597"}
{"prompt": "45169,45170,45171", "answer": "45172"}
{"prompt": "37423,37424,37425,37426,37427,37428,37429,37430,37431", "answer": "37432"}
{"prompt": "32593,32594,32595,32596,32597,32598,32599,32600", "answer": "32601"}
{"prompt": "28291,28292,28293,28294,28295,28296,28297", "answer": "28298"}
{"prompt": "28030,28031,28032,28033,28034,28035,28036,28037", "answer": "28038"}
{"prompt": "12579,12580,12581", "answer": "12582"}
{"prompt": "7240", "answer": "7241"}
{"prompt": "35595,35596", "answer": "35597"}
{"prompt": "22663,22664,22665,22666", "answer": "22667"}
{"prompt": "36839", "answer": "36840"}
{"prompt": "25390,25391,25392,25393,25394,25395,25396,25397", "answer": "25398"}
{"prompt": "27991,27992,27993,27994,27995,27996,27997,27998,27999", "answer": "28000"}
{"prompt": "42902,42903,42904", "answer": "42905"}
{"prompt": "23861,23862,23863,23864", "answer": "23865"}
{"prompt": "1981,1982,1983,1984,1985,1986,1987", "answer": "1988"}
{"prompt": "25109,25110,25111,25112,25113,25114,25115,25116,25117", "answer": "25118"}
{"prompt": "42685,42686,42687,42688,42689,42690,42691", "answer": "42692"}
{"prompt": "36551,36552", "answer": "36553"}
{"prompt": "6506,6507", "answer": "6508"}
{"prompt": "9326,9327,9328,9329,9330,9331", "answer": "9332"}
{"prompt": "20992,20993,20994,20995,20996,20997,20998", "answer": "20999"}
{"prompt": "41195,41196,41197,41198,41199,41200,41201,41202,41203", "answer": "41204"}
{"prompt": "35959,35960,35961,35962,35963,35964", "answer": "35965"}
{"prompt": "33597", "answer": "33598"}
{"prompt": "11939,11940,11941,11942,11943,11944,11945,11946", "answer": "11947"}
{"prompt": "22284,22285,22286,22287", "answer": "22288"}
{"prompt": "7015", "answer": "7016"}
{"prompt": "18705,18706,18707,18708,18709,18710,18711", "answer": "18712"}
{"prompt": "36819,36820,36821", "answer": "36822"}
{"prompt": "28223", "answer": "28224"}
{"prompt": "5299,5300,5301,5302", "answer": "5303"}
{"prompt": "16304,16305,16306,16307,16308,16309,16310", "answer": "16311"}
{"prompt": "24480,24481,24482,24483,24484,24485,24486,24487", "answer": "24488"}
{"prompt": "16208,16209,16210,16211,16212,16213,16214", "answer": "16215"}
{"prompt": "8972,8973,8974,8975,8976", "answer": "8977"}
{"prompt": "2433,2434,2435,2436,2437,2438,2439,2440", "answer": "2441"}
{"prompt": "3024,3025,3026,3027,3028,3029", "answer": "3030"}
{"prompt": "19737,19738,19739,19740,19741,19742,19743,19744,19745", "answer": "19746"}
{"prompt": "44991,44992,44993,44994,44995,44996,44997,44998,44999,45000", "answer": "45001"}
{"prompt": "1352,1353,1354,1355,1356,1357", "answer": "1358"}
{"prompt": "23468,23469", "answer": "23470"}
{"prompt": "4096,4097,4098,4099,4100,4101,4102,4103,4104", "answer": "4105"}
{"prompt": "40587,40588,40589,40590,40591,40592,40593,40594,40595,40596", "answer": "40597"}
{"prompt": "34000,34001,34002,34003,34004,34005", "answer": "34006"}
{"prompt": "17403,17404,17405,17406,17407,17408,17409,17410,17411,17412", "answer": "17413"}
{"prompt": "25663,25664,25665,25666,25667", "answer": "25668"}
{"prompt": "34374,34375,34376", "answer": "34377"}
{"prompt": "35710,35711,35712,35713,35714,35715,35716,35717,35718,35719", "answer": "35720"}
{"prompt": "41872,41873,41874,41875,41876,41877,41878,41879,41880", "answer": "41881"}
{"prompt": "3153,3154,3155,3156,3157,3158,3159,3160,3161,3162", "answer": "3163"}
{"prompt": "37473,37474,37475,37476,37477,37478,37479,37480,37481,37482", "answer": "37483"}
{"prompt": "14792,14793,14794,14795,14796,14797,14798,14799,14800,14801", "answer": "14802"}
{"prompt": "36335,36336,36337,36338,36339,36340", "answer": "36341"}
{"prompt": "3978,3979,3980,3981,3982,3983,3984", "answer": "3985"}
{"prompt": "20220,20221,20222,20223,20224,20225", "answer": "20226"}
{"prompt": "10659,10660,10661,10662,10663,10664,10665,10666,10667,10668", "answer": "10669"}
{"prompt": "43790,43791,43792,43793,43794,43795,43796,43797", "answer": "43798"}
{"prompt": "31223,31224,31225", "answer": "31226"}
{"prompt": "43004,43005,43006,43007,43008,43009,43010,43011", "answer": "43012"}
{"prompt": "9551,9552,9553,9554,9555,9556,9557,9558,9559", "answer": "9560"}
{"prompt": "19482,19483,19484,19485,19486,19487,19488,19489,19490,19491", "answer": "19492"}
{"prompt": "44409,44410,44411,44412,44413", "answer": "44414"}
{"prompt": "38244", "answer": "38245"}
{"prompt": "2381,2382,2383,2384,2385,2386", "answer": "2387"}
{"prompt": "18127,18128,18129,18130,18131,18132,18133", "answer": "18134"}
{"prompt": "5866,5867", "answer": "5868"}
{"prompt": "27271,27272,27273,27274,27275", "answer": "27276"}
{"prompt": "32519,32520,32521,32522", "answer": "32523"}
{"prompt": "34096,34097", "answer": "34098"}
{"prompt": "8268,8269,8270,8271,8272,8273,8274,8275", "answer": "8276"}
{"prompt": "4800,4801,4802,4803,4804,4805,4806,4807,4808", "answer": "4809"}
{"prompt": "40911,40912,40913,40914,40915,40916,40917,40918,40919", "answer": "40920"}
{"prompt": "1497", "answer": "1498"}
{"prompt": "14818,14819,14820,14821,14822,14823", "answer": "14824"}
{"prompt": "43453,43454,43455,43456,43457,43458,43459,43460", "answer": "43461"}
{"prompt": "25300,25301,25302,25303,25304,25305,25306", "answer": "25307"}
{"prompt": "18110,18111,18112,18113,18114,18115,18116,18117,18118,18119", "answer": "18120"}
{"prompt": "7024,7025", "answer": "7026"}
{"prompt": "10416,10417,10418,10419,10420,10421,10422", "answer": "10423"}
{"prompt": "14192,14193,14194,14195,14196,14197,14198", "answer": "14199"}
{"prompt": "15459,15460,15461,15462,15463,15464", "answer": "15465"}
{"prompt": "15529,15530,15531,15532,15533,15534", "answer": "15535"}
{"prompt": "342", "answer": "343"}
{"prompt": "27767,27768,27769,27770,27771,27772,27773", "answer": "27774"}
{"prompt": "25685", "answer": "25686"}
{"prompt": "7646,7647,7648", "answer": "7649"}
{"prompt": "11604,11605,11606,11607,11608", "answer": "11609"}
{"prompt": "15776,15777,15778,15779,15780,15781", "answer": "15782"}
{"prompt": "27291,27292", "answer": "27293"}
{"prompt": "41408,41409,41410,41411,41412,41413,41414,41415,41416,41417", "answer": "41418"}
{"prompt": "28619,28620,28621,28622,28623,28624", "answer": "28625"}
{"prompt": "27586,27587,27588,27589,27590,27591,27592,27593,27594", "answer": "27595"}
{"prompt": "35994,35995,35996,35997,35998,35999", "answer": "36000"}
{"prompt": "15056,15057,15058,15059,15060,15061,15062,15063,15064", "answer": "15065"}
{"prompt": "13991,13992,13993", "answer": "13994"}
{"prompt": "24050,24051,24052,24053,24054,24055,24056,24057", "answer": "24058"}
{"prompt": "24041,24042,24043", "answer": "24044"}
{"prompt": "27465,27466,27467", "answer": "27468"}
{"prompt": "12375,12376,12377", "answer": "12378"}
{"prompt": "8927,8928,8929", "answer": "8930"}
{"prompt": "23563,23564,23565", "answer": "23566"}
{"prompt": "10898,10899,10900", "answer": "10901"}
{"prompt": "35463,35464,35465,35466,35467,35468,35469,35470,35471,35472", "answer": "35473"}
{"prompt": "7682,7683,7684,7685,7686", "answer": "7687"}
{"prompt": "40428,40429,40430,40431,40432,40433", "answer": "40434"}
{"prompt": "31548,31549,31550,31551", "answer": "31552"}
{"prompt": "31710,31711,31712", "answer": "31713"}
{"prompt": "7708,7709,7710", "answer": "7711"}
{"prompt": "33179,33180,33181,33182,33183", "answer": "33184"}
{"prompt": "33330,33331,33332,33333,33334,33335,33336", "answer": "33337"}
{"prompt": "34080", "answer": "34081"}
{"prompt": "12009,12010", "answer": "12011"}
{"prompt": "37995,37996,37997,37998,37999,38000,38001,38002", "answer": "38003"}
{"prompt": "25727", "answer": "25728"}
{"prompt": "16962,16963,16964,16965,16966,16967,16968,16969,16970", "answer": "16971"}
{"prompt": "3623", "answer": "3624"}
{"prompt": "7972,7973,7974,7975,7976,7977", "answer": "7978"}
{"prompt": "32397,32398,32399,32400,32401", "answer": "32402"}
{"prompt": "41366", "answer": "41367"}
{"prompt": "36167,36168,36169,36170", "answer": "36171"}
{"prompt": "42887,42888,42889,42890,42891,42892,42893,42894", "answer": "42895"}
{"prompt": "43798,43799", "answer": "43800"}
{"prompt": "40583,40584,40585,40586,40587", "answer": "40588"}
{"prompt": "1823,1824,1825,1826,1827", "answer": "1828"}
{"prompt": "20569,20570,20571", "answer": "20572"}
{"prompt": "29098", "answer": "29099"}
{"prompt": "14491,14492,14493,14494,14495,14496,14497,14498,14499", "answer": "14500"}
{"prompt": "25703", "answer": "25704"}
{"prompt": "1668,1669,1670,1671,1672,1673,1674", "answer": "1675"}
{"prompt": "38236,38237,38238", "answer": "38239"}
{"prompt": "1685,1686,1687,1688,1689,1690", "answer": "1691"}
{"prompt": "40686,40687,40688,40689,40690", "answer": "40691"}
{"prompt": "6421,6422,6423", "answer": "6424"}
{"prompt": "22599,22600,22601,22602,22603,22604,22605,22606,22607,22608", "answer": "22609"}
{"prompt": "3263,3264,3265,3266,3267", "answer": "3268"}
{"prompt": "6974,6975,6976,6977,6978,6979,6980,6981,6982,6983", "answer": "6984"}
{"prompt": "33982,33983,33984,33985,33986,33987,33988", "answer": "33989"}
{"prompt": "1929,1930,1931,1932,1933,1934,1935", "answer": "1936"}
{"prompt": "10746,10747,10748", "answer": "10749"}
{"prompt": "19474", "answer": "19475"}
{"prompt": "32462", "answer": "32463"}
{"prompt": "19457,19458,19459,19460,19461,19462,19463,19464", "answer": "19465"}
{"prompt": "17966,17967,17968,17969,17970,17971,17972,17973", "answer": "17974"}
{"prompt": "29320,29321", "answer": "29322"}
{"prompt": "42343,42344,42345", "answer": "42346"}
{"prompt": "18250,18251,18252,18253,18254,18255,18256,18257", "answer": "18258"}
{"prompt": "852,853,854,855,856,857,858,859,860", "answer": "861"}
{"prompt": "18210,18211,18212,18213,18214,18215", "answer": "18216"}
{"prompt": "2984,2985,2986,2987", "answer": "2988"}
{"prompt": "33031,33032,33033,33034,33035,33036,33037", "answer": "33038"}
{"prompt": "16175,16176,16177,16178,16179,16180,16181,16182", "answer": "16183"}
{"prompt": "39096,39097,39098,39099,39100,39101,39102,39103,39104", "answer": "39105"}
{"prompt": "15898,15899,15900", "answer": "15901"}
{"prompt": "30510,30511,30512", "answer": "30513"}
{"prompt": "43263,43264,43265,43266", "answer": "43267"}
{"prompt": "40048,40049,40050,40051,40052,40053,40054,40055", "answer": "40056"}
{"prompt": "42113,42114,42115,42116,42117", "answer": "42118"}
{"prompt": "12010,12011,12012", "answer": "12013"}
{"prompt": "43706,43707,43708", "answer": "43709"}
{"prompt": "7479,7480,7481", "answer": "7482"}
{"prompt": "44403,44404,44405,44406,44407,44408,44409", "answer": "44410"}
{"prompt": "19301,19302", "answer": "19303"}
{"prompt": "31406,31407,31408,31409,31410,31411", "answer": "31412"}
{"prompt": "24986", "answer": "24987"}
{"prompt": "35677,35678,35679,35680", "answer": "35681"}
{"prompt": "20677,20678,20679,20680,20681,20682,20683,20684,20685,20686", "answer": "20687"}
{"prompt": "35450", "answer": "35451"}
{"prompt": "2070,2071,2072", "answer": "2073"}
{"prompt": "41936,41937,41938,41939", "answer": "41940"}
{"prompt": "1480,1481,1482,1483,1484,1485,1486,1487,1488,1489", "answer": "1490"}
{"prompt": "15152,15153,15154,15155,15156,15157,15158,15159,15160,15161", "answer": "15162"}
{"prompt": "27483,27484,27485,27486,27487,27488,27489,27490", "answer": "27491"}
{"prompt": "32035,32036,32037,32038,32039,32040,32041,32042,32043,32044", "answer": "32045"}
{"prompt": "8896,8897,8898", "answer": "8899"}
{"prompt": "42250,42251,42252,42253,42254,42255,42256", "answer": "42257"}
{"prompt": "28283,28284,28285,28286,28287,28288,28289,28290,28291", "answer": "28292"}
{"prompt": "9156", "answer": "9157"}
{"prompt": "12654,12655,12656,12657,12658,12659,12660,12661,12662", "answer": "12663"}
{"prompt": "2336,2337,2338,2339", "answer": "2340"}
{"prompt": "23922,23923", "answer": "23924"}
{"prompt": "16648,16649,16650,16651,16652,16653,16654,16655", "answer": "16656"}
{"prompt": "14608,14609,14610,14611,14612,14613,14614", "answer": "14615"}
{"prompt": "40180,40181,40182,40183,40184,40185,40186,40187,40188,40189", "answer": "40190"}
{"prompt": "25077,25078,25079,25080,25081,25082,25083,25084", "answer": "25085"}
{"prompt": "5726,5727,5728,5729,5730,5731,5732,5733,5734,5735", "answer": "5736"}
{"prompt": "7181,7182,7183,7184,7185,7186,7187,7188,7189", "answer": "7190"}
{"prompt": "18483,18484,18485,18486,18487,18488", "answer": "18489"}
{"prompt": "29700,29701,29702", "answer": "29703"}
{"prompt": "6205,6206,6207", "answer": "6208"}
{"prompt": "19212,19213", "answer": "19214"}
{"prompt": "35016,35017,35018", "answer": "35019"}
{"prompt": "13086,13087,13088,13089", "answer": "13090"}
{"prompt": "31552", "answer": "31553"}
{"prompt": "23036,23037,23038,23039,23040,23041,23042,23043", "answer": "23044"}
{"prompt": "28441,28442,28443,28444,28445,28446,28447,28448,28449", "answer": "28450"}
{"prompt": "26985,26986,26987,26988,26989,26990,26991,26992", "answer": "26993"}
{"prompt": "38448,38449,38450,38451,38452,38453,38454,38455,38456", "answer": "38457"}
{"prompt": "1074,1075", "answer": "1076"}
{"prompt": "16561,16562,16563", "answer": "16564"}
{"prompt": "5526,5527,5528,5529,5530,5531,5532,5533,5534,5535", "answer": "5536"}
{"prompt": "24130,24131,24132,24133", "answer": "24134"}
{"prompt": "6573,6574,6575,6576,6577", "answer": "6578"}
{"prompt": "44917,44918,44919,44920", "answer": "44921"}
{"prompt": "27970,27971,27972,27973,27974,27975,27976,27977", "answer": "27978"}
{"prompt": "25753,25754", "answer": "25755"}
{"prompt": "35773,35774,35775,35776,35777,35778,35779", "answer": "35780"}
{"prompt": "32424,32425,32426,32427,32428,32429,32430,32431,32432,32433", "answer": "32434"}
{"prompt": "29221,29222,29223,29224,29225,29226,29227", "answer": "29228"}
{"prompt": "25688,25689,25690,25691,25692,25693,25694,25695", "answer": "25696"}
{"prompt": "42489,42490,42491,42492,42493,42494,42495,42496", "answer": "42497"}
{"prompt": "43451,43452,43453", "answer": "43454"}
{"prompt": "37402,37403", "answer": "37404"}
{"prompt": "22088,22089,22090,22091,22092,22093,22094,22095", "answer": "22096"}
{"prompt": "2509,2510,2511,2512,2513,2514,2515,2516,2517", "answer": "2518"}
{"prompt": "21668,21669,21670,21671,21672,21673,21674,21675,21676,21677", "answer": "21678"}
{"prompt": "36127,36128", "answer": "36129"}
{"prompt": "43997,43998,43999,44000,44001,44002,44003,44004,44005", "answer": "44006"}
{"prompt": "33160,33161,33162,33163,33164", "answer": "33165"}
{"prompt": "12249,12250,12251,12252,12253,12254,12255,12256", "answer": "12257"}
{"prompt": "145,146", "answer": "147"}
{"prompt": "428,429,430,431,432", "answer": "433"}
{"prompt": "19590,19591,19592,19593,19594,19595,19596,19597", "answer": "19598"}
{"prompt": "39,40,41,42", "answer": "43"}
{"prompt": "32609,32610,32611,32612,32613,32614,32615", "answer": "32616"}
{"prompt": "30587,30588,30589", "answer": "30590"}
{"prompt": "40459,40460,40461,40462,40463,40464,40465,40466,40467,40468", "answer": "40469"}
{"prompt": "38727,38728,38729,38730,38731,38732,38733", "answer": "38734"}
{"prompt": "23989,23990,23991,23992,23993,23994,23995,23996,23997", "answer": "23998"}
{"prompt": "715,716,717,718,719,720,721,722", "answer": "723"}
{"prompt": "39089,39090,39091,39092,39093,39094,39095,39096", "answer": "39097"}
{"prompt": "19365,19366,19367,19368,19369,19370,19371", "answer": "19372"}
{"prompt": "29276,29277,29278,29279,29280,29281", "answer": "29282"}
{"prompt": "37889,37890,37891,37892,37893", "answer": "37894"}
{"prompt": "12710,12711,12712,12713,12714,12715", "answer": "12716"}
{"prompt": "2950,2951,2952,2953,2954,2955,2956,2957,2958,2959", "answer": "2960"}
{"prompt": "13174,13175,13176,13177,13178,13179,13180", "answer": "13181"}
{"prompt": "8419,8420,8421,8422,8423", "answer": "8424"}
{"prompt": "7462,7463,7464", "answer": "7465"}
{"prompt": "40284,40285,40286,40287,40288,40289,40290", "answer": "40291"}
{"prompt": "42257,42258", "answer": "42259"}
{"prompt": "6834,6835,6836,6837,6838,6839", "answer": "6840"}
{"prompt": "22283,22284", "answer": "22285"}
{"prompt": "18572,18573,18574,18575,18576,18577,18578", "answer": "18579"}
{"prompt": "19976,19977,19978,19979,19980,19981,19982", "answer": "19983"}
{"prompt": "36592", "answer": "36593"}
{"prompt": "45128,45129,45130,45131,45132,45133,45134", "answer": "45135"}
{"prompt": "27439,27440,27441,27442,27443,27444,27445", "answer": "27446"}
{"prompt": "29380,29381,29382,29383,29384,29385,29386", "answer": "29387"}
{"prompt": "43569,43570,43571,43572,43573,43574,43575", "answer": "43576"}
{"prompt": "6780,6781,6782,6783,6784,6785,6786", "answer": "6787"}
{"prompt": "36791,36792,36793,36794,36795,36796,36797,36798,36799,36800", "answer": "36801"}
{"prompt": "39772,39773,39774", "answer": "39775"}
{"prompt": "28456,28457,28458,28459,28460,28461,28462,28463", "answer": "28464"}
{"prompt": "32886,32887,32888,32889,32890,32891,32892,32893,32894", "answer": "32895"}
{"prompt": "39012,39013,39014,39015,39016", "answer": "39017"}
{"prompt": "14571,14572,14573", "answer": "14574"}
{"prompt": "40500,40501", "answer": "40502"}
{"prompt": "38117,38118,38119", "answer": "38120"}
{"prompt": "41402,41403,41404,41405,41406,41407,41408", "answer": "41409"}
{"prompt": "12425,12426", "answer": "12427"}
{"prompt": "39205,39206,39207,39208,39209,39210", "answer": "39211"}
{"prompt": "29440,29441,29442", "answer": "29443"}
{"prompt": "34696,34697,34698,34699,34700,34701,34702,34703,34704", "answer": "34705"}
{"prompt": "25695,25696", "answer": "25697"}
{"prompt": "6639,6640,6641,6642,6643,6644,6645", "answer": "6646"}
{"prompt": "39236,39237,39238", "answer": "39239"}
{"prompt": "44432,44433,44434,44435,44436,44437,44438,44439,44440", "answer": "44441"}
{"prompt": "5964,5965,5966,5967,5968,5969,5970,5971", "answer": "5972"}
{"prompt": "23115", "answer": "23116"}
{"prompt": "19614,19615,19616,19617,19618,19619", "answer": "19620"}
{"prompt": "24013,24014,24015,24016,24017", "answer": "24018"}
{"prompt": "2562,2563,2564,2565,2566,2567,2568,2569", "answer": "2570"}
{"prompt": "4414,4415,4416,4417,4418", "answer": "4419"}
{"prompt": "22310,22311,22312,22313,22314,22315,22316,22317", "answer": "22318"}
{"prompt": "1846,1847,1848,1849,1850,1851,1852,1853,1854", "answer": "1855"}
{"prompt": "230,231", "answer": "232"}
{"prompt": "11799,11800,11801,11802,11803,11804", "answer": "11805"}
{"prompt": "5353,5354,5355,5356,5357", "answer": "5358"}
{"prompt": "23795,23796,23797,23798,23799", "answer": "23800"}
{"prompt": "18862,18863,18864,18865,18866,18867", "answer": "18868"}
{"prompt": "8636,8637,8638,8639,8640,8641,8642,8643", "answer": "8644"}
{"prompt": "12370,12371", "answer": "12372"}
{"prompt": "28383,28384,28385,28386,28387,28388,28389,28390,28391", "answer": "28392"}
{"prompt": "11608,11609,11610,11611,11612,11613,11614", "answer": "11615"}
{"prompt": "27586", "answer": "27587"}
{"prompt": "25748", "answer": "25749"}
{"prompt": "42367,42368,42369,42370,42371,42372,42373,42374,42375,42376", "answer": "42377"}
{"prompt": "4953,4954,4955", "answer": "4956"}
{"prompt": "16038,16039,16040,16041,16042", "answer": "16043"}
{"prompt": "39947,39948,39949,39950,39951,39952", "answer": "39953"}
{"prompt": "978,979,980,981,982,983,984", "answer": "985"}
{"prompt": "31831,31832,31833,31834,31835", "answer": "31836"}
{"prompt": "44738,44739,44740,44741,44742", "answer": "44743"}
{"prompt": "39152,39153,39154,39155,39156,39157,39158", "answer": "39159"}
{"prompt": "13296,13297,13298,13299,13300,13301,13302,13303,13304", "answer": "13305"}
{"prompt": "32462", "answer": "32463"}
{"prompt": "37054", "answer": "37055"}
{"prompt": "17718", "answer": "17719"}
{"prompt": "21400,21401", "answer": "21402"}
{"prompt": "2024,2025,2026,2027,2028,2029,2030", "answer": "2031"}
{"prompt": "16670,16671,16672,16673,16674,16675,16676,16677,16678,16679", "answer": "16680"}
{"prompt": "790,791,792,793", "answer": "794"}
{"prompt": "6348", "answer": "6349"}
{"prompt": "42982,42983,42984,42985,42986,42987,42988", "answer": "42989"}
{"prompt": "21391,21392,21393,21394,21395", "answer": "21396"}
{"prompt": "45159,45160,45161,45162,45163,45164,45165", "answer": "45166"}
{"prompt": "33774,33775,33776,33777,33778,33779,33780", "answer": "33781"}
{"prompt": "33800,33801,33802,33803,33804,33805,33806,33807", "answer": "33808"}
{"prompt": "36603", "answer": "36604"}
{"prompt": "10101,10102,10103,10104", "answer": "10105"}
{"prompt": "38311,38312,38313,38314,38315,38316,38317,38318", "answer": "38319"}
{"prompt": "8307,8308,8309,8310,8311,8312,8313", "answer": "8314"}
{"prompt": "13052,13053,13054,13055,13056,13057,13058,13059,13060,13061", "answer": "13062"}
{"prompt": "8456,8457,8458,8459,8460,8461,8462,8463", "answer": "8464"}
{"prompt": "3855,3856,3857,3858,3859,3860,3861,3862", "answer": "3863"}
{"prompt": "11756,11757,11758,11759,11760", "answer": "11761"}
{"prompt": "41506", "answer": "41507"}
{"prompt": "17680,17681,17682", "answer": "17683"}
{"prompt": "30397,30398,30399,30400,30401,30402,30403,30404,30405,30406", "answer": "30407"}
{"prompt": "3554,3555,3556", "answer": "3557"}
{"prompt": "26385,26386,26387,26388,26389,26390,26391,26392,26393,26394", "answer": "26395"}
{"prompt": "21413,21414,21415,21416,21417,21418,21419,21420", "answer": "21421"}
{"prompt": "44570,44571,44572,44573,44574,44575,44576,44577,44578,44579", "answer": "44580"}
{"prompt": "12067", "answer": "12068"}
{"prompt": "27152,27153,27154,27155,27156,27157,27158,27159,27160", "answer": "27161"}
{"prompt": "2809,2810,2811,2812,2813,2814", "answer": "2815"}
{"prompt": "30564,30565,30566,30567,30568,30569,30570,30571,30572,30573", "answer": "30574"}
{"prompt": "20025,20026,20027,20028,20029,20030,20031,20032", "answer": "20033"}
{"prompt": "12006,12007,12008,12009", "answer": "12010"}
{"prompt": "25297,25298,25299,25300", "answer": "25301"}
{"prompt": "13688,13689,13690,13691,13692,13693,13694", "answer": "13695"}
{"prompt": "43417,43418,43419,43420,43421,43422,43423,43424,43425,43426", "answer": "43427"}
{"prompt": "40348,40349", "answer": "40350"}
{"prompt": "9864,9865,9866,9867,9868,9869,9870,9871,9872,9873", "answer": "9874"}
{"prompt": "13655,13656,13657,13658,13659", "answer": "13660"}
{"prompt": "9770,9771,9772,9773,9774,9775,9776,9777,9778", "answer": "9779"}
{"prompt": "38966,38967,38968", "answer": "38969"}
{"prompt": "14977,14978,14979,14980,14981,14982,14983", "answer": "14984"}
{"prompt": "22078,22079,22080,22081,22082,22083,22084,22085,22086", "answer": "22087"}
{"prompt": "6875,6876,6877,6878,6879,6880,6881,6882", "answer": "6883"}
{"prompt": "41738,41739,41740,41741,41742,41743", "answer": "41744"}
{"prompt": "7145,7146", "answer": "7147"}
{"prompt": "15486", "answer": "15487"}
{"prompt": "31204,31205,31206,31207,31208,31209,31210,31211", "answer": "31212"}
{"prompt": "17936,17937,17938,17939,17940,17941,17942,17943", "answer": "17944"}
{"prompt": "38060", "answer": "38061"}
{"prompt": "38134,38135,38136,38137,38138", "answer": "38139"}
{"prompt": "11128,11129,11130,11131,11132,11133", "answer": "11134"}
{"prompt": "32748", "answer": "32749"}
{"prompt": "38378,38379", "answer": "38380"}
{"prompt": "20700,20701,20702,20703,20704,20705", "answer": "20706"}
{"prompt": "21881,21882,21883,21884", "answer": "21885"}
{"prompt": "8387,8388,8389,8390,8391,8392", "answer": "8393"}
{"prompt": "9120,9121,9122,9123,9124", "answer": "9125"}
{"prompt": "30276,30277,30278,30279,30280", "answer": "30281"}
{"prompt": "33152,33153,33154", "answer": "33155"}
{"prompt": "18364,18365,18366,18367,18368,18369,18370,18371,18372,18373", "answer": "18374"}
{"prompt": "33900,33901,33902,33903,33904,33905,33906,33907", "answer": "33908"}
{"prompt": "27745,27746", "answer": "27747"}
{"prompt": "5718,5719,5720,5721,5722,5723", "answer": "5724"}
{"prompt": "30836,30837,30838,30839,30840", "answer": "30841"}
{"prompt": "1450,1451,1452,1453,1454,1455", "answer": "1456"}
{"prompt": "16471,16472,16473", "answer": "16474"}
{"prompt": "24264,24265", "answer": "24266"}
{"prompt": "27415,27416,27417,27418,27419,27420,27421,27422", "answer": "27423"}
{"prompt": "30827,30828,30829,30830,30831", "answer": "30832"}
{"prompt": "11029,11030,11031,11032,11033,11034,11035,11036,11037,11038", "answer": "11039"}
{"prompt": "30864,30865,30866,30867,30868,30869,30870,30871", "answer": "30872"}
{"prompt": "14508,14509,14510", "answer": "14511"}
{"prompt": "4934,4935,4936,4937", "answer": "4938"}
{"prompt": "21618,21619,21620,21621,21622,21623,21624,21625,21626,21627", "answer": "21628"}
{"prompt": "42973,42974", "answer": "42975"}
{"prompt": "19731,19732,19733,19734,19735,19736,19737", "answer": "19738"}
{"prompt": "12725,12726,12727,12728,12729,12730,12731", "answer": "12732"}
{"prompt": "5422,5423", "answer": "5424"}
{"prompt": "31693,31694,31695,31696,31697,31698", "answer": "31699"}
{"prompt": "42037,42038,42039,42040", "answer": "42041"}
{"prompt": "45233,45234,45235", "answer": "45236"}
{"prompt": "3442,3443,3444,3445,3446", "answer": "3447"}
{"prompt": "43380,43381,43382,43383,43384,43385,43386", "answer": "43387"}
{"prompt": "2773,2774,2775", "answer": "2776"}
{"prompt": "42785,42786", "answer": "42787"}
{"prompt": "43680,43681,43682,43683,43684,43685,43686,43687,43688", "answer": "43689"}
{"prompt": "20568,20569", "answer": "20570"}
{"prompt": "31494", "answer": "31495"}
{"prompt": "38456,38457,38458,38459,38460,38461,38462,38463,38464,38465", "answer": "38466"}
{"prompt": "27552,27553,27554,27555,27556,27557,27558,27559,27560,27561", "answer": "27562"}
{"prompt": "7026,7027,7028,7029,7030,7031,7032,7033,7034,7035", "answer": "7036"}
{"prompt": "23687,23688,23689,23690,23691,23692,23693", "answer": "23694"}
{"prompt": "41772,41773,41774", "answer": "41775"}
{"prompt": "42110,42111", "answer": "42112"}
{"prompt": "6241,6242,6243,6244,6245,6246,6247,6248,6249,6250", "answer": "6251"}
{"prompt": "24846,24847,24848", "answer": "24849"}
{"prompt": "13563,13564,13565,13566,13567,13568,13569,13570,13571,13572", "answer": "13573"}
{"prompt": "40638,40639,40640,40641", "answer": "40642"}
{"prompt": "12607,12608,12609,12610,12611", "answer": "12612"}
{"prompt": "40581,40582,40583", "answer": "40584"}
{"prompt": "18031,18032", "answer": "18033"}
{"prompt": "9917,9918,9919", "answer": "9920"}
{"prompt": "32929,32930,32931,32932,32933,32934,32935,32936,32937,32938", "answer": "32939"}
{"prompt": "14405,14406,14407,14408,14409,14410,14411,14412", "answer": "14413"}
{"prompt": "40122,40123,40124,40125,40126", "answer": "40127"}
{"prompt": "18470,18471,18472,18473", "answer": "18474"}
{"prompt": "11726,11727,11728,11729,11730", "answer": "11731"}
{"prompt": "37716,37717,37718,37719,37720,37721,37722,37723,37724,37725", "answer": "37726"}
{"prompt": "26898,26899,26900,26901,26902,26903,26904,26905,26906", "answer": "26907"}
{"prompt": "3713,3714,3715,3716,3717,3718,3719,3720,3721,3722", "answer": "3723"}
{"prompt": "36594,36595,36596,36597,36598,36599,36600,36601", "answer": "36602"}
{"prompt": "11879,11880,11881,11882", "answer": "11883"}
{"prompt": "23979,23980,23981", "answer": "23982"}
{"prompt": "19947,19948,19949,19950", "answer": "19951"}
{"prompt": "37642,37643,37644,37645,37646,37647,37648", "answer": "37649"}
{"prompt": "32969,32970", "answer": "32971"}
{"prompt": "3254,3255,3256,3257,3258", "answer": "3259"}
{"prompt": "37453,37454,37455,37456", "answer": "37457"}
{"prompt": "43283,43284,43285,43286,43287", "answer": "43288"}
{"prompt": "31785,31786,31787", "answer": "31788"}
{"prompt": "15038", "answer": "15039"}
{"prompt": "41252,41253,41254,41255,41256,41257", "answer": "41258"}
{"prompt": "38657,38658,38659,38660,38661,38662,38663", "answer": "38664"}
{"prompt": "7788,7789,7790", "answer": "7791"}
{"prompt": "5932,5933,5934,5935,5936,5937", "answer": "5938"}
{"prompt": "30663,30664,30665,30666", "answer": "30667"}
{"prompt": "43688,43689,43690,43691,43692,43693", "answer": "43694"}
{"prompt": "23115,23116,23117", "answer": "23118"}
{"prompt": "1685", "answer": "1686"}
{"prompt": "16577,16578,16579,16580,16581,16582,16583,16584,16585,16586", "answer": "16587"}
{"prompt": "10376,10377,10378,10379,10380,10381", "answer": "10382"}
{"prompt": "30151,30152,30153", "answer": "30154"}
{"prompt": "13232,13233", "answer": "13234"}
{"prompt": "32131,32132", "answer": "32133"}
{"prompt": "13475,13476", "answer": "13477"}
{"prompt": "37176,37177,37178,37179,37180,37181", "answer": "37182"}
{"prompt": "37250,37251,37252,37253,37254", "answer": "37255"}
{"prompt": "39606,39607,39608", "answer": "39609"}
{"prompt": "15407,15408,15409", "answer": "15410"}
{"prompt": "24426,24427,24428", "answer": "24429"}
{"prompt": "44426,44427,44428,44429", "answer": "44430"}
{"prompt": "12321", "answer": "12322"}
{"prompt": "863,864,865,866,867,868,869,870,871,872", "answer": "873"}
{"prompt": "6694,6695,6696,6697,6698,6699,6700", "answer": "6701"}
{"prompt": "8036,8037,8038,8039,8040,8041,8042,8043,8044", "answer": "8045"}
{"prompt": "901,902,903,904,905,906,907,908", "answer": "909"}
{"prompt": "16057,16058,16059,16060,16061,16062", "answer": "16063"}
{"prompt": "14947,14948,14949,14950,14951,14952,14953,14954,14955,14956", "answer": "14957"}
{"prompt": "1314,1315,1316,1317,1318,1319,1320,1321,1322,1323", "answer": "1324"}
{"prompt": "19338,19339,19340,19341,19342,19343,19344", "answer": "19345"}
{"prompt": "22977,22978,22979,22980,22981,22982", "answer": "22983"}
{"prompt": "34793,34794,34795,34796,34797,34798", "answer": "34799"}
{"prompt": "31225,31226,31227,31228,31229,31230", "answer": "31231"}
{"prompt": "24731,24732,24733,24734,24735,24736", "answer": "24737"}
{"prompt": "14757,14758,14759,14760", "answer": "14761"}
{"prompt": "15739,15740,15741,15742,15743,15744,15745,15746,15747,15748", "answer": "15749"}
{"prompt": "13538,13539,13540,13541", "answer": "13542"}
{"prompt": "8855,8856,8857,8858,8859,8860,8861,8862", "answer": "8863"}
{"prompt": "4340", "answer": "4341"}
{"prompt": "3490,3491,3492,3493,3494", "answer": "3495"}
{"prompt": "3621,3622,3623", "answer": "3624"}
{"prompt": "27000,27001,27002,27003,27004,27005", "answer": "27006"}
{"prompt": "41616,41617,41618,41619,41620,41621,41622", "answer": "41623"}
{"prompt": "33164,33165,33166,33167", "answer": "33168"}
{"prompt": "19227,19228,19229,19230,19231", "answer": "19232"}
{"prompt": "37805,37806,37807,37808,37809,37810,37811", "answer": "37812"}
{"prompt": "18103", "answer": "18104"}
{"prompt": "28021,28022,28023,28024,28025,28026,28027,28028,28029,28030", "answer": "28031"}
{"prompt": "24040,24041", "answer": "24042"}
{"prompt": "16122,16123,16124", "answer": "16125"}
{"prompt": "25611,25612,25613,25614", "answer": "25615"}
{"prompt": "32555", "answer": "32556"}
{"prompt": "34928,34929,34930,34931,34932", "answer": "34933"}
{"prompt": "30287,30288,30289,30290,30291,30292,30293,30294,30295", "answer": "30296"}
{"prompt": "25867,25868,25869,25870,25871,25872,25873,25874,25875", "answer": "25876"}
{"prompt": "441,442,443,444,445,446,447", "answer": "448"}
{"prompt": "25420,25421", "answer": "25422"}
{"prompt": "13400,13401", "answer": "13402"}
{"prompt": "25244", "answer": "25245"}
{"prompt": "30726,30727,30728,30729", "answer": "30730"}
{"prompt": "37069,37070,37071,37072,37073,37074", "answer": "37075"}
{"prompt": "18854,18855,18856,18857,18858,18859,18860,18861,18862", "answer": "18863"}
{"prompt": "9365,9366,9367,9368,9369", "answer": "9370"}
{"prompt": "10339,10340,10341,10342,10343,10344,10345,10346,10347", "answer": "10348"}
{"prompt": "40793,40794,40795,40796,40797", "answer": "40798"}
{"prompt": "44514,44515,44516,44517,44518,44519,44520,44521,44522", "answer": "44523"}
{"prompt": "33616,33617,33618,33619,33620,33621", "answer": "33622"}
{"prompt": "42062,42063,42064,42065,42066,42067,42068,42069", "answer": "42070"}
{"prompt": "22698,22699,22700,22701", "answer": "22702"}
{"prompt": "18373,18374,18375,18376", "answer": "18377"}
{"prompt": "8956,8957", "answer": "8958"}
{"prompt": "21305,21306,21307,21308", "answer": "21309"}
{"prompt": "3239,3240,3241,3242,3243,3244,3245,3246", "answer": "3247"}
{"prompt": "41880,41881,41882,41883,41884,41885,41886,41887,41888,41889", "answer": "41890"}
{"prompt": "40325,40326,40327,40328,40329,40330,40331,40332,40333", "answer": "40334"}
{"prompt": "8341,8342", "answer": "8343"}
{"prompt": "39859", "answer": "39860"}
{"prompt": "35782,35783,35784,35785,35786,35787", "answer": "35788"}
{"prompt": "6237,6238,6239,6240,6241", "answer": "6242"}
{"prompt": "15892,15893,15894,15895,15896", "answer": "15897"}
{"prompt": "32672,32673,32674,32675,32676,32677,32678,32679,32680", "answer": "32681"}
{"prompt": "4163,4164,4165,4166,4167,4168", "answer": "4169"}
{"prompt": "9501,9502,9503,9504,9505,9506,9507,9508,9509", "answer": "9510"}
{"prompt": "14354,14355,14356,14357,14358,14359,14360", "answer": "14361"}
{"prompt": "36630,36631", "answer": "36632"}
{"prompt": "10218,10219,10220,10221,10222", "answer": "10223"}
{"prompt": "12776,12777,12778", "answer": "12779"}
{"prompt": "37119,37120,37121,37122,37123", "answer": "37124"}
{"prompt": "5693", "answer": "5694"}
{"prompt": "16876,16877,16878,16879,16880,16881,16882", "answer": "16883"}
{"prompt": "20063,20064,20065,20066,20067,20068,20069,20070", "answer": "20071"}
{"prompt": "39839,39840", "answer": "39841"}
{"prompt": "11202,11203,11204,11205", "answer": "11206"}
{"prompt": "23068,23069,23070,23071,23072,23073,23074,23075,23076,23077", "answer": "23078"}
{"prompt": "41916,41917,41918,41919,41920,41921", "answer": "41922"}
{"prompt": "17474,17475,17476,17477,17478,17479", "answer": "17480"}
{"prompt": "3785,3786,3787,3788,3789,3790,3791,3792,3793,3794", "answer": "3795"}
{"prompt": "19387,19388,19389,19390,19391,19392,19393,19394,19395,19396", "answer": "19397"}
{"prompt": "42231,42232,42233", "answer": "42234"}
{"prompt": "19267", "answer": "19268"}
{"prompt": "28484,28485", "answer": "28486"}
{"prompt": "356,357,358,359,360", "answer": "361"}
{"prompt": "22511,22512,22513", "answer": "22514"}
{"prompt": "10336,10337", "answer": "10338"}
{"prompt": "5289,5290,5291,5292,5293,5294,5295,5296", "answer": "5297"}
{"prompt": "35479,35480,35481,35482,35483,35484", "answer": "35485"}
{"prompt": "33495,33496,33497,33498", "answer": "33499"}
{"prompt": "21332,21333,21334", "answer": "21335"}
{"prompt": "40983,40984,40985,40986,40987,40988,40989", "answer": "40990"}
{"prompt": "25035,25036", "answer": "25037"}
{"prompt": "23034", "answer": "23035"}
{"prompt": "32566,32567,32568", "answer": "32569"}
{"prompt": "21260", "answer": "21261"}
{"prompt": "2537,2538,2539,2540,2541,2542,2543", "answer": "2544"}
{"prompt": "28824,28825,28826,28827,28828", "answer": "28829"}
{"prompt": "35392,35393,35394,35395,35396,35397", "answer": "35398"}
{"prompt": "7198,7199,7200", "answer": "7201"}
{"prompt": "36839,36840,36841,36842,36843,36844,36845,36846,36847", "answer": "36848"}
{"prompt": "15647,15648", "answer": "15649"}
{"prompt": "38124,38125", "answer": "38126"}
{"prompt": "44363,44364,44365,44366,44367,44368,44369,44370,44371,44372", "answer": "44373"}
{"prompt": "9000,9001,9002,9003,9004,9005,9006,9007,9008", "answer": "9009"}
{"prompt": "5906,5907,5908,5909,5910,5911,5912,5913,5914,5915", "answer": "5916"}
{"prompt": "17864,17865,17866,17867,17868", "answer": "17869"}
{"prompt": "42802,42803,42804,42805,42806,42807", "answer": "42808"}
{"prompt": "33823,33824,33825,33826,33827,33828,33829", "answer": "33830"}
{"prompt": "25058,25059,25060,25061,25062,25063,25064,25065", "answer": "25066"}
{"prompt": "23167,23168,23169,23170,23171,23172,23173,23174,23175", "answer": "23176"}
{"prompt": "2402,2403,2404,2405,2406,2407,2408,2409,2410", "answer": "2411"}
{"prompt": "45214,45215,45216,45217,45218,45219", "answer": "45220"}
{"prompt": "11675,11676,11677,11678", "answer": "11679"}
{"prompt": "37695,37696,37697,37698,37699", "answer": "37700"}
{"prompt": "28975,28976,28977,28978,28979,28980,28981", "answer": "28982"}
{"prompt": "2725,2726,2727,2728,2729,2730,2731,2732,2733,2734", "answer": "2735"}
{"prompt": "30531,30532,30533,30534,30535,30536,30537,30538,30539,30540", "answer": "30541"}
{"prompt": "23864,23865,23866,23867,23868,23869,23870", "answer": "23871"}
{"prompt": "5064,5065", "answer": "5066"}
{"prompt": "12067,12068,12069,12070,12071,12072,12073,12074,12075", "answer": "12076"}
{"prompt": "35235,35236,35237,35238,35239", "answer": "35240"}
{"prompt": "42226,42227,42228,42229,42230,42231", "answer": "42232"}
{"prompt": "44525,44526,44527,44528", "answer": "44529"}
{"prompt": "24506,24507,24508,24509,24510,24511,24512,24513,24514", "answer": "24515"}
{"prompt": "14629,14630,14631,14632,14633,14634,14635,14636,14637,14638", "answer": "14639"}
{"prompt": "11117,11118", "answer": "11119"}
{"prompt": "15030,15031", "answer": "15032"}
{"prompt": "25754,25755,25756,25757", "answer": "25758"}
{"prompt": "35074,35075", "answer": "35076"}
{"prompt": "23357,23358,23359,23360", "answer": "23361"}
{"prompt": "37633,37634,37635,37636,37637,37638,37639,37640,37641,37642", "answer": "37643"}
{"prompt": "41889,41890,41891", "answer": "41892"}
{"prompt": "5633,5634,5635,5636", "answer": "5637"}
{"prompt": "23966,23967,23968,23969,23970,23971,23972", "answer": "23973"}
{"prompt": "31219,31220,31221,31222,31223", "answer": "31224"}
{"prompt": "21933", "answer": "21934"}
{"prompt": "27176,27177,27178,27179,27180,27181,27182,27183,27184", "answer": "27185"}
{"prompt": "14093,14094,14095,14096,14097,14098", "answer": "14099"}
{"prompt": "32410,32411,32412,32413", "answer": "32414"}
{"prompt": "41203,41204,41205,41206,41207", "answer": "41208"}
{"prompt": "31843,31844,31845,31846,31847,31848,31849,31850", "answer": "31851"}
{"prompt": "27656", "answer": "27657"}
{"prompt": "13609,13610,13611,13612,13613", "answer": "13614"}
{"prompt": "19745,19746,19747,19748,19749,19750,19751,19752,19753", "answer": "19754"}
{"prompt": "1658,1659,1660,1661,1662,1663,1664,1665,1666", "answer": "1667"}
{"prompt": "35165,35166", "answer": "35167"}
{"prompt": "19642,19643,19644,19645,19646,19647,19648,19649,19650", "answer": "19651"}
{"prompt": "20915,20916,20917,20918,20919,20920,20921,20922,20923", "answer": "20924"}
{"prompt": "41609,41610,41611,41612,41613,41614,41615,41616", "answer": "41617"}
{"prompt": "43712,43713,43714,43715", "answer": "43716"}
{"prompt": "38810,38811,38812,38813,38814,38815,38816,38817,38818", "answer": "38819"}
{"prompt": "22394,22395,22396,22397,22398,22399,22400,22401,22402,22403", "answer": "22404"}
{"prompt": "28228,28229,28230,28231,28232,28233", "answer": "28234"}
{"prompt": "38899,38900,38901,38902,38903,38904,38905,38906,38907,38908", "answer": "38909"}
{"prompt": "35486", "answer": "35487"}
{"prompt": "28202,28203,28204,28205,28206,28207,28208,28209", "answer": "28210"}
{"prompt": "18957,18958,18959,18960,18961,18962,18963,18964,18965,18966", "answer": "18967"}
{"prompt": "14907,14908,14909,14910", "answer": "14911"}
{"prompt": "27676,27677,27678,27679,27680", "answer": "27681"}
{"prompt": "18750,18751,18752,18753", "answer": "18754"}
{"prompt": "3001,3002,3003,3004,3005", "answer": "3006"}
{"prompt": "24115,24116", "answer": "24117"}
{"prompt": "44372,44373,44374,44375,44376,44377,44378,44379", "answer": "44380"}
{"prompt": "37216,37217", "answer": "37218"}
{"prompt": "11507,11508,11509,11510,11511", "answer": "11512"}
{"prompt": "30779,30780,30781,30782,30783,30784,30785", "answer": "30786"}
{"prompt": "21436,21437,21438,21439,21440", "answer": "21441"}
{"prompt": "11081,11082,11083,11084,11085,11086,11087", "answer": "11088"}
{"prompt": "44217,44218,44219,44220,44221,44222,44223,44224", "answer": "44225"}
{"prompt": "22319,22320,22321,22322", "answer": "22323"}
{"prompt": "24854,24855", "answer": "24856"}
{"prompt": "16971,16972,16973,16974,16975,16976", "answer": "16977"}
{"prompt": "36400", "answer": "36401"}
{"prompt": "23618,23619,23620,23621,23622,23623,23624,23625", "answer": "23626"}
{"prompt": "4702,4703", "answer": "4704"}
{"prompt": "36053,36054,36055,36056,36057", "answer": "36058"}
{"prompt": "44536,44537", "answer": "44538"}
{"prompt": "15904,15905,15906,15907,15908,15909,15910,15911,15912,15913", "answer": "15914"}
{"prompt": "13729,13730,13731,13732,13733,13734,13735,13736", "answer": "13737"}
{"prompt": "42791", "answer": "42792"}
{"prompt": "24711,24712,24713,24714,24715,24716,24717,24718,24719,24720", "answer": "24721"}
{"prompt": "43451", "answer": "43452"}
{"prompt": "24707,24708,24709,24710,24711", "answer": "24712"}
{"prompt": "30552", "answer": "30553"}
{"prompt": "16944,16945", "answer": "16946"}
{"prompt": "38244,38245,38246,38247", "answer": "38248"}
{"prompt": "18083,18084,18085,18086,18087,18088,18089,18090", "answer": "18091"}
{"prompt": "33009,33010,33011,33012,33013,33014,33015,33016,33017", "answer": "33018"}
{"prompt": "25209,25210,25211", "answer": "25212"}
{"prompt": "6889,6890,6891,6892,6893,6894,6895,6896,6897,6898", "answer": "6899"}
{"prompt": "12618,12619,12620,12621,12622,12623", "answer": "12624"}
{"prompt": "12623,12624,12625,12626,12627", "answer": "12628"}
{"prompt": "29220", "answer": "29221"}
{"prompt": "38797,38798,38799,38800,38801,38802,38803,38804,38805,38806", "answer": "38807"}
{"prompt": "4352,4353,4354", "answer": "4355"}
{"prompt": "27922,27923,27924", "answer": "27925"}
{"prompt": "36249,36250,36251,36252,36253,36254,36255,36256,36257,36258", "answer": "36259"}
{"prompt": "9822,9823,9824,9825,9826,9827,9828,9829,9830,9831", "answer": "9832"}
{"prompt": "16837,16838,16839,16840,16841", "answer": "16842"}
{"prompt": "34932,34933,34934,34935,34936,34937,34938", "answer": "34939"}
{"prompt": "16808,16809", "answer": "16810"}
{"prompt": "15202,15203,15204,15205,15206,15207,15208,15209,15210,15211", "answer": "15212"}
{"prompt": "35876", "answer": "35877"}
{"prompt": "37235,37236,37237,37238,37239,37240", "answer": "37241"}
{"prompt": "12870,12871,12872,12873,12874,12875,12876,12877", "answer": "12878"}
{"prompt": "17958,17959,17960,17961", "answer": "17962"}
{"prompt": "40402,40403,40404", "answer": "40405"}
{"prompt": "21230,21231,21232", "answer": "21233"}
{"prompt": "44357,44358,44359,44360", "answer": "44361"}
{"prompt": "12089,12090,12091,12092,12093,12094,12095,12096,12097", "answer": "12098"}
{"prompt": "43595,43596,43597,43598,43599,43600,43601,43602", "answer": "43603"}
{"prompt": "5996,5997,5998,5999,6000,6001,6002,6003,6004", "answer": "6005"}
{"prompt": "8830,8831,8832,8833,8834,8835,8836,8837,8838,8839", "answer": "8840"}
{"prompt": "31651,31652,31653,31654,31655,31656,31657", "answer": "31658"}
{"prompt": "5308,5309,5310,5311,5312,5313,5314,5315,5316", "answer": "5317"}
{"prompt": "491,492,493", "answer": "494"}
{"prompt": "23679,23680,23681,23682,23683,23684,23685,23686,23687", "answer": "23688"}
{"prompt": "7369,7370,7371,7372,7373,7374,7375,7376,7377", "answer": "7378"}
{"prompt": "36100,36101,36102", "answer": "36103"}
{"prompt": "14499,14500,14501,14502,14503,14504,14505,14506,14507,14508", "answer": "14509"}
{"prompt": "21972,21973,21974,21975,21976,21977,21978,21979,21980,21981", "answer": "21982"}
{"prompt": "21499,21500,21501", "answer": "21502"}
{"prompt": "5388,5389,5390,5391,5392,5393,5394,5395,5396,5397", "answer": "5398"}
{"prompt": "14106,14107,14108,14109,14110,14111,14112,14113", "answer": "14114"}
{"prompt": "15757", "answer": "15758"}
{"prompt": "12286,12287", "answer": "12288"}
{"prompt": "34618,34619,34620,34621,34622,34623", "answer": "34624"}
{"prompt": "9994", "answer": "9995"}
{"prompt": "21404,21405,21406,21407,21408,21409,21410,21411,21412,21413", "answer": "21414"}
{"prompt": "19167,19168,19169,19170,19171,19172,19173,19174", "answer": "19175"}
{"prompt": "41174,41175,41176", "answer": "41177"}
{"prompt": "17143,17144", "answer": "17145"}
{"prompt": "43079,43080,43081,43082,43083,43084,43085,43086,43087", "answer": "43088"}
{"prompt": "36281,36282,36283,36284", "answer": "36285"}
{"prompt": "26839,26840,26841,26842", "answer": "26843"}
{"prompt": "9317,9318,9319,9320,9321,9322,9323,9324,9325,9326", "answer": "9327"}
{"prompt": "8399,8400,8401,8402,8403,8404", "answer": "8405"}
{"prompt": "23201,23202,23203,23204,23205,23206", "answer": "23207"}
{"prompt": "3869,3870,3871,3872,3873", "answer": "3874"}
{"prompt": "10574,10575,10576,10577,10578,10579,10580", "answer": "10581"}
{"prompt": "15133,15134,15135,15136,15137,15138,15139,15140,15141", "answer": "15142"}
{"prompt": "3483,3484,3485,3486,3487,3488,3489,3490", "answer": "3491"}
{"prompt": "2978,2979,2980,2981,2982,2983,2984", "answer": "2985"}
{"prompt": "34615,34616", "answer": "34617"}
{"prompt": "36482,36483,36484,36485,36486,36487,36488,36489", "answer": "36490"}
{"prompt": "25654,25655,25656,25657,25658,25659,25660,25661,25662,25663", "answer": "25664"}
{"prompt": "41749,41750,41751,41752,41753,41754,41755,41756", "answer": "41757"}
{"prompt": "8149,8150", "answer": "8151"}
{"prompt": "4678,4679,4680", "answer": "4681"}
{"prompt": "33890", "answer": "33891"}
{"prompt": "21197,21198,21199", "answer": "21200"}
{"prompt": "18300,18301,18302,18303,18304,18305,18306,18307,18308,18309", "answer": "18310"}
{"prompt": "17753,17754,17755,17756,17757", "answer": "17758"}
{"prompt": "3546", "answer": "3547"}
{"prompt": "13736,13737,13738,13739,13740,13741,13742,13743,13744,13745", "answer": "13746"}
{"prompt": "20006,20007,20008,20009,20010,20011,20012,20013,20014,20015", "answer": "20016"}
{"prompt": "27236,27237,27238,27239,27240,27241,27242,27243,27244", "answer": "27245"}
{"prompt": "4769,4770,4771,4772,4773,4774", "answer": "4775"}
{"prompt": "45068,45069,45070,45071", "answer": "45072"}
{"prompt": "45320,45321,45322,45323,45324,45325", "answer": "45326"}
{"prompt": "17694,17695,17696,17697,17698,17699,17700,17701,17702,17703", "answer": "17704"}
{"prompt": "29340,29341,29342,29343,29344,29345,29346,29347", "answer": "29348"}
{"prompt": "36572,36573,36574,36575,36576,36577,36578,36579,36580", "answer": "36581"}
{"prompt": "4991,4992,4993,4994,4995,4996,4997,4998,4999", "answer": "5000"}
{"prompt": "34293,34294", "answer": "34295"}
{"prompt": "19891,19892,19893,19894,19895,19896,19897,19898,19899", "answer": "19900"}
{"prompt": "22294,22295,22296,22297,22298,22299,22300,22301,22302,22303", "answer": "22304"}
{"prompt": "17218,17219,17220,17221,17222,17223", "answer": "17224"}
{"prompt": "28321,28322,28323,28324,28325,28326,28327,28328,28329,28330", "answer": "28331"}
{"prompt": "22822,22823,22824", "answer": "22825"}
{"prompt": "2372,2373,2374,2375,2376,2377,2378,2379,2380,2381", "answer": "2382"}
{"prompt": "15675,15676,15677", "answer": "15678"}
{"prompt": "42457,42458,42459,42460,42461,42462", "answer": "42463"}
{"prompt": "44808,44809,44810,44811,44812,44813,44814,44815", "answer": "44816"}
{"prompt": "30630,30631,30632", "answer": "30633"}
{"prompt": "33646,33647,33648,33649,33650", "answer": "33651"}
{"prompt": "27145,27146,27147,27148,27149,27150,27151,27152", "answer": "27153"}
{"prompt": "5840,5841,5842,5843,5844,5845,5846,5847", "answer": "5848"}
{"prompt": "6306", "answer": "6307"}
{"prompt": "35301,35302,35303,35304,35305,35306,35307,35308", "answer": "35309"}
{"prompt": "14183,14184,14185,14186,14187,14188,14189,14190,14191,14192", "answer": "14193"}
{"prompt": "19982,19983,19984,19985,19986,19987,19988,19989,19990,19991", "answer": "19992"}
{"prompt": "1636,1637,1638,1639,1640,1641,1642,1643,1644", "answer": "1645"}
{"prompt": "31795", "answer": "31796"}
{"prompt": "5357,5358,5359,5360,5361,5362,5363,5364,5365,5366", "answer": "5367"}
{"prompt": "1202", "answer": "1203"}
{"prompt": "30845,30846,30847,30848,30849", "answer": "30850"}
{"prompt": "28616,28617,28618,28619", "answer": "28620"}
{"prompt": "12417,12418,12419,12420,12421,12422,12423", "answer": "12424"}
{"prompt": "31088,31089,31090,31091,31092", "answer": "31093"}
{"prompt": "26968,26969,26970,26971,26972,26973,26974,26975,26976", "answer": "26977"}
{"prompt": "34680,34681,34682,34683,34684,34685,34686,34687", "answer": "34688"}
{"prompt": "9931,9932", "answer": "9933"}
{"prompt": "27044", "answer": "27045"}
{"prompt": "15128,15129,15130,15131", "answer": "15132"}
{"prompt": "38984,38985,38986,38987,38988,38989,38990,38991", "answer": "38992"}
{"prompt": "32327,32328,32329", "answer": "32330"}
{"prompt": "18477,18478,18479,18480,18481,18482,18483", "answer": "18484"}
{"prompt": "34178,34179,34180", "answer": "34181"}
{"prompt": "6020,6021,6022,6023", "answer": "6024"}
{"prompt": "4028", "answer": "4029"}
{"prompt": "13718,13719", "answer": "13720"}
{"prompt": "42775,42776", "answer": "42777"}
{"prompt": "39319,39320,39321,39322,39323,39324,39325", "answer": "39326"}
{"prompt": "22136,22137", "answer": "22138"}
{"prompt": "6473,6474,6475,6476,6477,6478,6479", "answer": "6480"}
{"prompt": "6386,6387,6388,6389,6390,6391", "answer": "6392"}
{"prompt": "15651,15652,15653,15654,15655,15656,15657,15658,15659", "answer": "15660"}
{"prompt": "38980,38981", "answer": "38982"}
{"prompt": "15493,15494,15495,15496,15497,15498,15499,15500", "answer": "15501"}
{"prompt": "29029", "answer": "29030"}
{"prompt": "24918,24919", "answer": "24920"}
{"prompt": "7794,7795,7796,7797,7798,7799,7800,7801", "answer": "7802"}
{"prompt": "2189,2190", "answer": "2191"}
{"prompt": "29124,29125,29126,29127", "answer": "29128"}
{"prompt": "17435,17436,17437,17438", "answer": "17439"}
{"prompt": "5210,5211", "answer": "5212"}
{"prompt": "27378,27379,27380,27381,27382,27383,27384,27385,27386", "answer": "27387"}
{"prompt": "43371,43372,43373", "answer": "43374"}
{"prompt": "4762,4763,4764,4765,4766,4767,4768", "answer": "4769"}
{"prompt": "29077,29078,29079,29080,29081,29082,29083,29084", "answer": "29085"}
{"prompt": "20985", "answer": "20986"}
{"prompt": "6567,6568,6569", "answer": "6570"}
{"prompt": "25174,25175", "answer": "25176"}
{"prompt": "5226,5227,5228", "answer": "5229"}
{"prompt": "1601,1602,1603", "answer": "1604"}
{"prompt": "28538", "answer": "28539"}
{"prompt": "42714,42715,42716,42717,42718", "answer": "42719"}
{"prompt": "557,558", "answer": "559"}
{"prompt": "29679,29680,29681,29682,29683,29684", "answer": "29685"}
{"prompt": "40415,40416,40417,40418,40419,40420", "answer": "40421"}
{"prompt": "3062", "answer": "3063"}
{"prompt": "33048,33049,33050,33051", "answer": "33052"}
{"prompt": "11253,11254,11255,11256,11257,11258,11259,11260,11261,11262", "answer": "11263"}
{"prompt": "16132,16133,16134,16135,16136,16137,16138,16139", "answer": "16140"}
{"prompt": "39298,39299,39300,39301", "answer": "39302"}
{"prompt": "11614,11615,11616,11617,11618,11619,11620,11621,11622,11623", "answer": "11624"}
{"prompt": "13525,13526,13527,13528,13529,13530,13531", "answer": "13532"}
{"prompt": "22608,22609", "answer": "22610"}
{"prompt": "35429,35430,35431,35432,35433,35434", "answer": "35435"}
{"prompt": "15013,15014,15015,15016,15017,15018,15019,15020", "answer": "15021"}
{"prompt": "42034", "answer": "42035"}
{"prompt": "14305,14306,14307,14308,14309", "answer": "14310"}
{"prompt": "238,239", "answer": "240"}
{"prompt": "26204,26205,26206,26207", "answer": "26208"}
{"prompt": "16959,16960,16961", "answer": "16962"}
{"prompt": "40641,40642,40643,40644,40645,40646,40647,40648,40649", "answer": "40650"}
{"prompt": "31143,31144,31145,31146,31147,31148,31149,31150,31151", "answer": "31152"}
{"prompt": "22962,22963,22964,22965,22966,22967,22968", "answer": "22969"}
{"prompt": "17757,17758,17759,17760,17761", "answer": "17762"}
{"prompt": "38416,38417,38418,38419,38420,38421,38422,38423,38424", "answer": "38425"}
{"prompt": "32356,32357,32358,32359,32360,32361,32362,32363,32364", "answer": "32365"}
{"prompt": "27296", "answer": "27297"}
{"prompt": "7826", "answer": "7827"}
{"prompt": "41556,41557,41558,41559,41560", "answer": "41561"}
{"prompt": "15504,15505,15506,15507,15508", "answer": "15509"}
{"prompt": "38747,38748,38749,38750", "answer": "38751"}
{"prompt": "43150,43151,43152,43153,43154,43155,43156,43157,43158,43159", "answer": "43160"}
{"prompt": "18151,18152,18153,18154,18155", "answer": "18156"}
{"prompt": "28320,28321", "answer": "28322"}
{"prompt": "7790,7791,7792,7793,7794", "answer": "7795"}
{"prompt": "6041,6042,6043,6044,6045,6046,6047", "answer": "6048"}
{"prompt": "42083,42084,42085,42086,42087,42088,42089", "answer": "42090"}
{"prompt": "19149,19150,19151,19152,19153,19154,19155,19156,19157", "answer": "19158"}
{"prompt": "21449,21450", "answer": "21451"}
{"prompt": "29603,29604,29605,29606,29607,29608,29609", "answer": "29610"}
{"prompt": "6494,6495", "answer": "6496"}
{"prompt": "44328", "answer": "44329"}
{"prompt": "4639,4640,4641,4642,4643,4644,4645", "answer": "4646"}
{"prompt": "21919,21920,21921,21922,21923,21924,21925,21926", "answer": "21927"}
{"prompt": "14316,14317,14318", "answer": "14319"}
{"prompt": "41395,41396,41397,41398,41399,41400,41401,41402", "answer": "41403"}
{"prompt": "27784,27785,27786,27787,27788,27789,27790,27791", "answer": "27792"}
{"prompt": "34223,34224,34225,34226,34227,34228,34229,34230,34231", "answer": "34232"}
{"prompt": "24759,24760,24761,24762,24763,24764,24765", "answer": "24766"}
{"prompt": "16608,16609,16610,16611,16612,16613,16614", "answer": "16615"}
{"prompt": "30075,30076,30077,30078,30079,30080,30081,30082,30083,30084", "answer": "30085"}
{"prompt": "42080,42081,42082,42083", "answer": "42084"}
{"prompt": "29098,29099,29100,29101,29102,29103,29104,29105,29106,29107", "answer": "29108"}
{"prompt": "16514,16515,16516,16517", "answer": "16518"}
{"prompt": "37334,37335,37336,37337,37338", "answer": "37339"}
{"prompt": "23175,23176,23177,23178,23179", "answer": "23180"}
{"prompt": "4564,4565,4566,4567,4568,4569,4570,4571", "answer": "4572"}
{"prompt": "27455,27456,27457,27458", "answer": "27459"}
{"prompt": "37699,37700,37701,37702,37703,37704,37705,37706", "answer": "37707"}
{"prompt": "42260,42261,42262", "answer": "42263"}
{"prompt": "13345,13346,13347,13348,13349,13350,13351", "answer": "13352"}
{"prompt": "8080,8081,8082,8083,8084,8085", "answer": "8086"}
{"prompt": "8647,8648,8649", "answer": "8650"}
{"prompt": "29045,29046,29047,29048,29049,29050", "answer": "29051"}
{"prompt": "15827,15828,15829", "answer": "15830"}
{"prompt": "6054,6055,6056,6057,6058,6059", "answer": "6060"}
{"prompt": "41366,41367,41368,41369", "answer": "41370"}
{"prompt": "7503", "answer": "7504"}
{"prompt": "40560,40561,40562,40563,40564,40565,40566,40567,40568,40569", "answer": "40570"}
{"prompt": "8541,8542,8543,8544,8545,8546,8547,8548,8549", "answer": "8550"}
{"prompt": "35758,35759,35760,35761,35762,35763,35764,35765,35766", "answer": "35767"}
{"prompt": "12259,12260,12261,12262,12263,12264,12265,12266", "answer": "12267"}
{"prompt": "2504,2505,2506,2507,2508,2509", "answer": "2510"}
{"prompt": "13069,13070,13071", "answer": "13072"}
{"prompt": "20015,20016,20017,20018,20019,20020,20021,20022,20023", "answer": "20024"}
{"prompt": "4736,4737", "answer": "4738"}
{"prompt": "44079", "answer": "44080"}
{"prompt": "22373,22374,22375,22376,22377,22378", "answer": "22379"}
{"prompt": "19753,19754", "answer": "19755"}
{"prompt": "921,922,923,924,925,926,927,928,929,930", "answer": "931"}
{"prompt": "34362,34363,34364,34365", "answer": "34366"}
{"prompt": "6718,6719,6720,6721,6722,6723,6724,6725,6726,6727", "answer": "6728"}
{"prompt": "30258,30259,30260,30261,30262,30263,30264,30265", "answer": "30266"}
{"prompt": "42568,42569,42570,42571,42572,42573,42574,42575,42576,42577", "answer": "42578"}
{"prompt": "5501,5502,5503,5504,5505,5506,5507,5508,5509,5510", "answer": "5511"}
{"prompt": "45136,45137,45138,45139,45140,45141,45142,45143,45144,45145", "answer": "45146"}
{"prompt": "38809,38810", "answer": "38811"}
{"prompt": "21396,21397,21398,21399,21400", "answer": "21401"}
{"prompt": "35245,35246,35247,35248,35249,35250,35251,35252", "answer": "35253"}
{"prompt": "39118,39119,39120,39121,39122,39123,39124,39125,39126", "answer": "39127"}
{"prompt": "26862", "answer": "26863"}
{"prompt": "16985,16986,16987,16988,16989,16990,16991,16992,16993,16994", "answer": "16995"}
{"prompt": "37490,37491", "answer": "37492"}
{"prompt": "28338,28339", "answer": "28340"}
{"prompt": "37811,37812,37813,37814,37815,37816", "answer": "37817"}
{"prompt": "8266,8267,8268", "answer": "8269"}
{"prompt": "9650", "answer": "9651"}
{"prompt": "23107,23108,23109,23110,23111,23112", "answer": "23113"}
{"prompt": "15923,15924", "answer": "15925"}
{"prompt": "28763,28764,28765,28766,28767,28768,28769", "answer": "28770"}
{"prompt": "41985,41986,41987,41988,41989,41990", "answer": "41991"}
{"prompt": "277,278,279,280", "answer": "281"}
{"prompt": "43924,43925,43926,43927,43928", "answer": "43929"}
{"prompt": "14638,14639,14640,14641", "answer": "14642"}
{"prompt": "43296,43297,43298,43299,43300,43301,43302,43303", "answer": "43304"}
{"prompt": "40851,40852,40853,40854,40855,40856", "answer": "40857"}
{"prompt": "22860,22861,22862,22863,22864,22865,22866,22867,22868,22869", "answer": "22870"}
{"prompt": "15038", "answer": "15039"}
{"prompt": "40224,40225", "answer": "40226"}
{"prompt": "16070,16071,16072", "answer": "16073"}
{"prompt": "45243,45244", "answer": "45245"}
{"prompt": "31712,31713,31714,31715,31716,31717", "answer": "31718"}
{"prompt": "41458,41459,41460,41461", "answer": "41462"}
{"prompt": "31980,31981,31982,31983,31984", "answer": "31985"}
{"prompt": "6727,6728,6729,6730,6731,6732,6733,6734", "answer": "6735"}
{"prompt": "22766,22767,22768,22769,22770,22771", "answer": "22772"}
{"prompt": "12364,12365,12366,12367,12368,12369,12370", "answer": "12371"}
{"prompt": "5636,5637,5638", "answer": "5639"}
{"prompt": "16785,16786,16787", "answer": "16788"}
{"prompt": "17270", "answer": "17271"}
{"prompt": "35218,35219,35220", "answer": "35221"}
{"prompt": "16042,16043", "answer": "16044"}
{"prompt": "23930,23931,23932,23933,23934,23935,23936,23937,23938", "answer": "23939"}
{"prompt": "7089,7090,7091,7092,7093,7094,7095,7096,7097,7098", "answer": "7099"}
{"prompt": "34060,34061,34062,34063,34064", "answer": "34065"}
{"prompt": "17378", "answer": "17379"}
{"prompt": "21300,21301", "answer": "21302"}
{"prompt": "3205,3206,3207,3208,3209,3210,3211,3212,3213,3214", "answer": "3215"}
{"prompt": "43974,43975,43976,43977,43978,43979", "answer": "43980"}
{"prompt": "24468,24469,24470", "answer": "24471"}
{"prompt": "19697,19698,19699,19700,19701,19702,19703,19704", "answer": "19705"}
{"prompt": "30544,30545,30546,30547,30548", "answer": "30549"}
{"prompt": "20727,20728,20729,20730,20731,20732,20733,20734,20735", "answer": "20736"}
{"prompt": "3378,3379,3380,3381,3382,3383", "answer": "3384"}
{"prompt": "20998,20999", "answer": "21000"}
{"prompt": "2757,2758,2759,2760,2761,2762,2763,2764,2765,2766", "answer": "2767"}
{"prompt": "39262,39263,39264,39265,39266,39267,39268,39269,39270,39271", "answer": "39272"}
{"prompt": "12497,12498,12499,12500,12501,12502,12503,12504", "answer": "12505"}
{"prompt": "21330,21331,21332", "answer": "21333"}
{"prompt": "30762,30763,30764,30765,30766,30767,30768", "answer": "30769"}
{"prompt": "18276,18277,18278,18279,18280", "answer": "18281"}
{"prompt": "43769,43770,43771", "answer": "43772"}
{"prompt": "26696", "answer": "26697"}
{"prompt": "18736,18737,18738,18739,18740,18741,18742", "answer": "18743"}
{"prompt": "1120,1121,1122,1123,1124,1125,1126", "answer": "1127"}
{"prompt": "28359,28360,28361,28362,28363,28364,28365", "answer": "28366"}
{"prompt": "21016,21017", "answer": "21018"}
{"prompt": "32433,32434,32435,32436", "answer": "32437"}
{"prompt": "23328,23329,23330,23331,23332,23333,23334,23335", "answer": "23336"}
{"prompt": "18996,18997", "answer": "18998"}
{"prompt": "2143,2144,2145,2146,2147,2148", "answer": "2149"}
{"prompt": "19563,19564,19565,19566,19567,19568,19569,19570,19571", "answer": "19572"}
{"prompt": "41375,41376", "answer": "41377"}
{"prompt": "18056,18057,18058,18059", "answer": "18060"}
{"prompt": "38262,38263,38264,38265,38266,38267,38268", "answer": "38269"}
{"prompt": "15924,15925,15926,15927", "answer": "15928"}
{"prompt": "33359", "answer": "33360"}
{"prompt": "40958,40959,40960,40961,40962,40963", "answer": "40964"}
{"prompt": "5211,5212,5213,5214,5215", "answer": "5216"}
{"prompt": "38991,38992,38993,38994,38995,38996,38997", "answer": "38998"}
{"prompt": "30899,30900,30901", "answer": "30902"}
{"prompt": "9492,9493,9494,9495,9496,9497,9498,9499,9500,9501", "answer": "9502"}
{"prompt": "9650", "answer": "9651"}
{"prompt": "7408,7409,7410,7411", "answer": "7412"}
{"prompt": "12464,12465,12466,12467,12468,12469,12470,12471,12472,12473", "answer": "12474"}
{"prompt": "36494,36495,36496,36497,36498,36499,36500", "answer": "36501"}
{"prompt": "17099,17100,17101,17102,17103,17104,17105,17106", "answer": "17107"}
{"prompt": "33912,33913,33914,33915,33916,33917,33918", "answer": "33919"}
{"prompt": "36159,36160,36161,36162,36163,36164,36165", "answer": "36166"}
{"prompt": "12035,12036,12037,12038,12039,12040,12041,12042,12043,12044", "answer": "12045"}
{"prompt": "6815,6816,6817,6818,6819,6820,6821,6822,6823", "answer": "6824"}
{"prompt": "7980,7981,7982,7983,7984,7985,7986,7987,7988,7989", "answer": "7990"}
{"prompt": "16575,16576,16577", "answer": "16578"}
{"prompt": "38873,38874", "answer": "38875"}
{"prompt": "31767", "answer": "31768"}
{"prompt": "2458,2459,2460,2461,2462,2463,2464,2465,2466", "answer": "2467"}
{"prompt": "38024,38025,38026,38027,38028,38029,38030,38031,38032,38033", "answer": "38034"}
{"prompt": "40505,40506,40507,40508,40509,40510", "answer": "40511"}
{"prompt": "10935,10936,10937,10938,10939,10940,10941,10942", "answer": "10943"}
{"prompt": "19665,19666", "answer": "19667"}
{"prompt": "39875,39876,39877,39878,39879", "answer": "39880"}
{"prompt": "30304,30305,30306,30307,30308,30309,30310,30311,30312,30313", "answer": "30314"}
{"prompt": "30039,30040,30041", "answer": "30042"}
{"prompt": "21249,21250,21251,21252,21253,21254,21255,21256,21257", "answer": "21258"}
{"prompt": "12277,12278,12279,12280,12281,12282,12283,12284,12285,12286", "answer": "12287"}
{"prompt": "9112,9113,9114,9115,9116,9117,9118,9119,9120", "answer": "9121"}
{"prompt": "16314,16315,16316", "answer": "16317"}
{"prompt": "3220,3221,3222,3223,3224,3225", "answer": "3226"}
{"prompt": "20873,20874,20875,20876,20877,20878,20879", "answer": "20880"}
{"prompt": "42709,42710,42711,42712,42713,42714", "answer": "42715"}
{"prompt": "41231,41232,41233,41234,41235,41236,41237,41238,41239", "answer": "41240"}
{"prompt": "11205,11206,11207,11208", "answer": "11209"}
{"prompt": "41808,41809,41810,41811,41812,41813", "answer": "41814"}
{"prompt": "5589,5590,5591,5592,5593,5594", "answer": "5595"}
{"prompt": "32497,32498,32499,32500,32501,32502,32503,32504", "answer": "32505"}
{"prompt": "15464,15465", "answer": "15466"}
{"prompt": "12164,12165,12166,12167,12168", "answer": "12169"}
{"prompt": "34993,34994", "answer": "34995"}
{"prompt": "4987,4988,4989,4990,4991", "answer": "4992"}
{"prompt": "44640,44641,44642,44643,44644,44645,44646,44647", "answer": "44648"}
{"prompt": "4087", "answer": "4088"}
{"prompt": "28779,28780,28781,28782,28783,28784,28785,28786,28787,28788", "answer": "28789"}
{"prompt": "16310,16311,16312,16313,16314", "answer": "16315"}
{"prompt": "13889,13890,13891", "answer": "13892"}
{"prompt": "43220,43221,43222,43223,43224,43225,43226,43227", "answer": "43228"}
{"prompt": "31811,31812,31813,31814,31815,31816,31817", "answer": "31818"}
{"prompt": "12818,12819,12820,12821,12822", "answer": "12823"}
{"prompt": "27954,27955,27956,27957", "answer": "27958"}
{"prompt": "26416,26417,26418,26419,26420,26421,26422", "answer": "26423"}
{"prompt": "2100,2101,2102,2103,2104,2105,2106,2107,2108", "answer": "2109"}
{"prompt": "14121,14122,14123,14124", "answer": "14125"}
{"prompt": "21761,21762,21763,21764,21765,21766,21767,21768", "answer": "21769"}
{"prompt": "33052", "answer": "33053"}
{"prompt": "10497,10498,10499", "answer": "10500"}
{"prompt": "9282,9283,9284,9285,9286", "answer": "9287"}
{"prompt": "18075,18076,18077,18078,18079,18080,18081,18082,18083", "answer": "18084"}
{"prompt": "25474,25475,25476,25477,25478,25479,25480", "answer": "25481"}
{"prompt": "1632", "answer": "1633"}
{"prompt": "31673,31674", "answer": "31675"}
{"prompt": "22031,22032,22033,22034,22035,22036,22037,22038,22039", "answer": "22040"}
{"prompt": "17817,17818,17819,17820,17821,17822,17823,17824", "answer": "17825"}
{"prompt": "40532,40533,40534,40535,40536,40537,40538,40539", "answer": "40540"}
{"prompt": "5924,5925,5926,5927,5928,5929,5930,5931,5932", "answer": "5933"}
{"prompt": "24645,24646,24647,24648,24649", "answer": "24650"}
{"prompt": "38821,38822,38823,38824,38825,38826,38827,38828", "answer": "38829"}
{"prompt": "3924,3925,3926,3927,3928", "answer": "3929"}
{"prompt": "10288,10289,10290,10291,10292,10293,10294,10295,10296,10297", "answer": "10298"}
{"prompt": "16372,16373,16374,16375", "answer": "16376"}
{"prompt": "18684,18685,18686", "answer": "18687"}
{"prompt": "23004,23005,23006,23007,23008,23009,23010,23011,23012,23013", "answer": "23014"}
{"prompt": "23880,23881,23882,23883,23884,23885,23886", "answer": "23887"}
{"prompt": "39306", "answer": "39307"}
{"prompt": "20796,20797,20798,20799", "answer": "20800"}
{"prompt": "20718,20719,20720,20721,20722,20723,20724,20725,20726", "answer": "20727"}
{"prompt": "44292,44293,44294,44295,44296,44297,44298,44299,44300,44301", "answer": "44302"}
{"prompt": "29588,29589,29590,29591,29592,29593,29594,29595,29596,29597", "answer": "29598"}
{"prompt": "32986,32987,32988", "answer": "32989"}
{"prompt": "29227,29228", "answer": "29229"}
{"prompt": "41546,41547", "answer": "41548"}
{"prompt": "14047,14048,14049,14050,14051,14052,14053,14054", "answer": "14055"}
{"prompt": "36634,36635,36636,36637", "answer": "36638"}
{"prompt": "9525,9526,9527,9528,9529", "answer": "9530"}
{"prompt": "30685", "answer": "30686"}
{"prompt": "7517,7518,7519,7520,7521,7522,7523,7524", "answer": "7525"}
{"prompt": "37310,37311,37312,37313,37314,37315,37316,37317", "answer": "37318"}
{"prompt": "28113,28114,28115", "answer": "28116"}
{"prompt": "16953,16954,16955,16956,16957,16958,16959", "answer": "16960"}
{"prompt": "5203,5204,5205,5206,5207,5208", "answer": "5209"}
{"prompt": "13273,13274,13275,13276,13277,13278,13279", "answer": "13280"}
{"prompt": "25013,25014,25015,25016,25017,25018,25019,25020", "answer": "25021"}
{"prompt": "33907,33908", "answer": "33909"}
{"prompt": "15146,15147,15148,15149,15150,15151,15152", "answer": "15153"}
{"prompt": "40991,40992", "answer": "40993"}
{"prompt": "15594,15595,15596,15597", "answer": "15598"}
{"prompt": "14745,14746,14747,14748,14749,14750,14751,14752", "answer": "14753"}
{"prompt": "20938,20939,20940,20941,20942,20943,20944,20945", "answer": "20946"}
{"prompt": "39367,39368,39369,39370,39371", "answer": "39372"}
{"prompt": "37756,37757,37758,37759,37760,37761,37762,37763", "answer": "37764"}
{"prompt": "37092,37093,37094,37095,37096", "answer": "37097"}
{"prompt": "25385,25386,25387,25388,25389,25390", "answer": "25391"}
{"prompt": "13280,13281", "answer": "13282"}
{"prompt": "37136,37137,37138,37139,37140,37141,37142,37143,37144", "answer": "37145"}
{"prompt": "11474,11475,11476,11477,11478", "answer": "11479"}
{"prompt": "5381,5382,5383,5384,5385,5386,5387,5388", "answer": "5389"}
{"prompt": "13935,13936,13937,13938,13939,13940,13941,13942,13943", "answer": "13944"}
{"prompt": "36662,36663,36664,36665,36666,36667", "answer": "36668"}
{"prompt": "17509,17510,17511,17512,17513,17514", "answer": "17515"}
{"prompt": "28669,28670,28671,28672,28673,28674", "answer": "28675"}
{"prompt": "39879,39880,39881,39882,39883,39884", "answer": "39885"}
{"prompt": "31468,31469,31470,31471,31472", "answer": "31473"}
{"prompt": "35381", "answer": "35382"}
{"prompt": "42180,42181,42182,42183", "answer": "42184"}
{"prompt": "37123,37124,37125,37126,37127,37128,37129", "answer": "37130"}
{"prompt": "19149", "answer": "19150"}
{"prompt": "12211,12212,12213,12214", "answer": "12215"}
{"prompt": "5800,5801", "answer": "5802"}
{"prompt": "22706,22707,22708,22709,22710,22711,22712", "answer": "22713"}
{"prompt": "34292,34293", "answer": "34294"}
{"prompt": "6360,6361,6362,6363,6364,6365,6366", "answer": "6367"}
{"prompt": "33391,33392,33393,33394,33395", "answer": "33396"}
{"prompt": "7139,7140", "answer": "7141"}
{"prompt": "28834,28835", "answer": "28836"}
{"prompt": "12131,12132,12133,12134,12135,12136,12137,12138,12139", "answer": "12140"}
{"prompt": "5716", "answer": "5717"}
{"prompt": "21190", "answer": "21191"}
{"prompt": "38052,38053,38054", "answer": "38055"}
{"prompt": "22684,22685,22686,22687,22688,22689,22690,22691,22692", "answer": "22693"}
{"prompt": "30613", "answer": "30614"}
{"prompt": "42211,42212,42213,42214,42215,42216,42217,42218", "answer": "42219"}
{"prompt": "27834,27835,27836,27837,27838,27839,27840,27841", "answer": "27842"}
{"prompt": "30619,30620,30621", "answer": "30622"}
{"prompt": "42009,42010,42011,42012,42013,42014", "answer": "42015"}
{"prompt": "44528,44529,44530,44531,44532,44533,44534,44535,44536", "answer": "44537"}
{"prompt": "18647,18648,18649,18650,18651,18652", "answer": "18653"}
{"prompt": "11511,11512,11513", "answer": "11514"}
{"prompt": "44677,44678,44679,44680,44681,44682,44683", "answer": "44684"}
{"prompt": "34883,34884,34885,34886,34887,34888,34889", "answer": "34890"}
{"prompt": "3988,3989,3990,3991,3992,3993,3994,3995,3996", "answer": "3997"}
{"prompt": "7200,7201,7202,7203,7204,7205", "answer": "7206"}
{"prompt": "30108,30109,30110,30111,30112,30113,30114,30115,30116", "answer": "30117"}
{"prompt": "19957,19958,19959,19960", "answer": "19961"}
{"prompt": "27220,27221,27222", "answer": "27223"}
{"prompt": "16500,16501,16502,16503,16504", "answer": "16505"}
{"prompt": "26011,26012,26013,26014,26015", "answer": "26016"}
{"prompt": "11404,11405,11406,11407,11408,11409,11410,11411,11412,11413", "answer": "11414"}
{"prompt": "36473,36474,36475,36476,36477", "answer": "36478"}
{"prompt": "2339,2340", "answer": "2341"}
{"prompt": "27318,27319,27320,27321,27322,27323,27324,27325,27326,27327", "answer": "27328"}
{"prompt": "6053,6054", "answer": "6055"}
{"prompt": "18426,18427,18428", "answer": "18429"}
{"prompt": "30454,30455,30456,30457,30458", "answer": "30459"}
{"prompt": "18911,18912,18913,18914", "answer": "18915"}
{"prompt": "11989", "answer": "11990"}
{"prompt": "218,219,220,221,222,223,224,225,226,227", "answer": "228"}
{"prompt": "41430,41431,41432,41433,41434,41435,41436,41437", "answer": "41438"}
{"prompt": "6746,6747", "answer": "6748"}
{"prompt": "23841,23842,23843,23844,23845,23846", "answer": "23847"}
{"prompt": "24701,24702,24703,24704,24705,24706,24707", "answer": "24708"}
{"prompt": "44728,44729,44730,44731,44732,44733,44734,44735,44736", "answer": "44737"}
{"prompt": "11574,11575,11576,11577,11578,11579", "answer": "11580"}
{"prompt": "18686,18687,18688,18689,18690,18691,18692,18693", "answer": "18694"}
{"prompt": "20847,20848,20849,20850,20851,20852,20853,20854,20855,20856", "answer": "20857"}
{"prompt": "35478,35479", "answer": "35480"}
{"prompt": "31361,31362", "answer": "31363"}
{"prompt": "9264,9265", "answer": "9266"}
{"prompt": "45303,45304,45305,45306,45307", "answer": "45308"}
{"prompt": "29693,29694,29695,29696,29697,29698,29699,29700", "answer": "29701"}
{"prompt": "11229,11230", "answer": "11231"}
{"prompt": "10626", "answer": "10627"}
{"prompt": "19070,19071", "answer": "19072"}
{"prompt": "29631,29632,29633,29634", "answer": "29635"}
{"prompt": "18822,18823,18824,18825,18826", "answer": "18827"}
{"prompt": "37113,37114,37115,37116,37117,37118,37119", "answer": "37120"}
{"prompt": "6548,6549,6550,6551,6552,6553,6554,6555,6556,6557", "answer": "6558"}
{"prompt": "27254,27255,27256,27257,27258,27259", "answer": "27260"}
{"prompt": "18297,18298,18299,18300", "answer": "18301"}
{"prompt": "36489,36490,36491,36492,36493,36494", "answer": "36495"}
{"prompt": "24967,24968,24969,24970,24971,24972,24973,24974", "answer": "24975"}
{"prompt": "25954,25955,25956,25957,25958,25959,25960", "answer": "25961"}
{"prompt": "9369,9370,9371,9372,9373,9374,9375,9376", "answer": "9377"}
{"prompt": "8,9,10,11", "answer": "12"}
{"prompt": "16940,16941,16942,16943,16944", "answer": "16945"}
{"prompt": "22895,22896", "answer": "22897"}
{"prompt": "39128,39129,39130,39131,39132,39133", "answer": "39134"}
{"prompt": "21874,21875,21876,21877,21878,21879,21880,21881", "answer": "21882"}
{"prompt": "40245,40246,40247,40248,40249,40250,40251,40252,40253,40254", "answer": "40255"}
{"prompt": "16473,16474,16475,16476,16477,16478,16479,16480,16481,16482", "answer": "16483"}
{"prompt": "4104,4105,4106,4107,4108,4109,4110,4111", "answer": "4112"}
{"prompt": "44123,44124,44125,44126,44127,44128", "answer": "44129"}
{"prompt": "40306", "answer": "40307"}
{"prompt": "316,317,318,319,320,321,322", "answer": "323"}
{"prompt": "26663,26664,26665,26666,26667,26668,26669,26670,26671,26672", "answer": "26673"}
{"prompt": "11236,11237,11238,11239,11240,11241,11242,11243,11244,11245", "answer": "11246"}
{"prompt": "30222,30223,30224,30225,30226,30227", "answer": "30228"}
{"prompt": "43123,43124,43125,43126,43127,43128,43129,43130,43131,43132", "answer": "43133"}
{"prompt": "7995,7996,7997", "answer": "7998"}
{"prompt": "40942,40943,40944,40945,40946,40947,40948,40949,40950", "answer": "40951"}
{"prompt": "20118,20119,20120,20121,20122,20123", "answer": "20124"}
{"prompt": "26776,26777,26778,26779,26780", "answer": "26781"}
{"prompt": "7352,7353,7354", "answer": "7355"}
{"prompt": "17686,17687,17688,17689,17690,17691,17692", "answer": "17693"}
{"prompt": "3024", "answer": "3025"}
{"prompt": "32758,32759,32760", "answer": "32761"}
{"prompt": "25790,25791,25792,25793,25794,25795,25796,25797,25798", "answer": "25799"}
{"prompt": "17772,17773", "answer": "17774"}
{"prompt": "7311,7312,7313,7314,7315,7316,7317", "answer": "7318"}
{"prompt": "40690,40691,40692", "answer": "40693"}
{"prompt": "24458,24459,24460", "answer": "24461"}
{"prompt": "30489,30490,30491,30492,30493,30494,30495,30496,30497,30498", "answer": "30499"}
{"prompt": "1782,1783,1784,1785,1786,1787,1788,1789", "answer": "1790"}
{"prompt": "19907,19908,19909,19910,19911,19912", "answer": "19913"}
{"prompt": "25090,25091,25092,25093,25094", "answer": "25095"}
{"prompt": "17212,17213,17214,17215,17216,17217,17218", "answer": "17219"}
{"prompt": "37373,37374,37375,37376,37377,37378,37379,37380,37381", "answer": "37382"}
{"prompt": "21565,21566,21567,21568,21569,21570", "answer": "21571"}
{"prompt": "21743,21744,21745,21746", "answer": "21747"}
{"prompt": "9064,9065", "answer": "9066"}
{"prompt": "8445,8446,8447", "answer": "8448"}
{"prompt": "41591,41592,41593,41594,41595,41596,41597,41598,41599,41600", "answer": "41601"}
{"prompt": "30368,30369,30370,30371,30372,30373,30374,30375", "answer": "30376"}
{"prompt": "35318,35319,35320,35321,35322,35323,35324,35325,35326", "answer": "35327"}
{"prompt": "29042,29043,29044,29045", "answer": "29046"}
{"prompt": "38309,38310,38311", "answer": "38312"}
{"prompt": "2274,2275,2276,2277", "answer": "2278"}
{"prompt": "7044,7045,7046,7047,7048,7049,7050,7051,7052", "answer": "7053"}
{"prompt": "34144,34145,34146,34147,34148", "answer": "34149"}
{"prompt": "31924,31925,31926,31927", "answer": "31928"}
{"prompt": "42221,42222,42223,42224,42225,42226", "answer": "42227"}
{"prompt": "9947,9948,9949,9950,9951,9952,9953", "answer": "9954"}
{"prompt": "37224,37225,37226,37227,37228,37229,37230,37231", "answer": "37232"}
{"prompt": "1435,1436,1437,1438,1439", "answer": "1440"}
{"prompt": "6569,6570,6571,6572,6573", "answer": "6574"}
{"prompt": "16935,16936,16937,16938,16939,16940", "answer": "16941"}
{"prompt": "45270,45271,45272,45273", "answer": "45274"}
{"prompt": "43308,43309,43310,43311,43312,43313,43314,43315,43316", "answer": "43317"}
{"prompt": "6765,6766,6767,6768,6769,6770,6771", "answer": "6772"}
{"prompt": "9529,9530", "answer": "9531"}
{"prompt": "24598,24599,24600,24601,24602,24603,24604,24605", "answer": "24606"}
{"prompt": "40129", "answer": "40130"}
{"prompt": "19344,19345,19346,19347,19348,19349,19350,19351", "answer": "19352"}
{"prompt": "36988,36989,36990,36991,36992,36993,36994,36995", "answer": "36996"}
{"prompt": "16602,16603", "answer": "16604"}
{"prompt": "1957,1958,1959,1960,1961,1962,1963,1964,1965", "answer": "1966"}
{"prompt": "2870,2871,2872,2873,2874,2875,2876,2877,2878,2879", "answer": "2880"}
{"prompt": "31719,31720,31721,31722,31723", "answer": "31724"}
{"prompt": "32944,32945,32946,32947", "answer": "32948"}
{"prompt": "32964,32965,32966,32967,32968", "answer": "32969"}
{"prompt": "10195,10196,10197,10198,10199,10200,10201", "answer": "10202"}
{"prompt": "34398,34399,34400,34401", "answer": "34402"}
{"prompt": "18826,18827,18828,18829,18830", "answer": "18831"}
{"prompt": "12343", "answer": "12344"}
{"prompt": "3623,3624,3625,3626,3627", "answer": "3628"}
{"prompt": "38122,38123,38124", "answer": "38125"}
{"prompt": "38647,38648,38649,38650,38651", "answer": "38652"}
{"prompt": "39325,39326,39327", "answer": "39328"}
{"prompt": "30931,30932,30933,30934,30935,30936,30937,30938", "answer": "30939"}
{"prompt": "28721,28722,28723,28724,28725,28726,28727,28728,28729", "answer": "28730"}
{"prompt": "8466,8467,8468,8469", "answer": "8470"}
{"prompt": "26939,26940,26941,26942", "answer": "26943"}
{"prompt": "407,408,409", "answer": "410"}
{"prompt": "37937,37938,37939,37940,37941,37942,37943", "answer": "37944"}
{"prompt": "31824,31825,31826", "answer": "31827"}
{"prompt": "17038,17039,17040,17041,17042,17043,17044", "answer": "17045"}
{"prompt": "18534,18535,18536,18537,18538,18539,18540,18541,18542,18543", "answer": "18544"}
{"prompt": "34426,34427", "answer": "34428"}
{"prompt": "7329,7330,7331,7332,7333", "answer": "7334"}
{"prompt": "4406,4407,4408,4409,4410,4411,4412,4413,4414", "answer": "4415"}
{"prompt": "26640,26641,26642", "answer": "26643"}
{"prompt": "33232,33233,33234", "answer": "33235"}
{"prompt": "32084,32085,32086,32087,32088,32089,32090,32091", "answer": "32092"}
{"prompt": "8324,8325,8326,8327,8328,8329,8330,8331,8332", "answer": "8333"}
{"prompt": "7693,7694,7695,7696,7697,7698,7699,7700", "answer": "7701"}
{"prompt": "32956,32957,32958,32959,32960,32961,32962", "answer": "32963"}
{"prompt": "25604,25605,25606,25607,25608,25609,25610,25611", "answer": "25612"}
{"prompt": "12802,12803,12804,12805,12806,12807,12808", "answer": "12809"}
{"prompt": "24916,24917,24918", "answer": "24919"}
{"prompt": "27861,27862,27863,27864,27865,27866,27867,27868,27869", "answer": "27870"}
{"prompt": "14299,14300,14301,14302,14303,14304,14305", "answer": "14306"}
{"prompt": "17961,17962,17963,17964,17965,17966", "answer": "17967"}
{"prompt": "44815,44816,44817,44818", "answer": "44819"}
{"prompt": "17906,17907,17908,17909", "answer": "17910"}
{"prompt": "31342,31343", "answer": "31344"}
{"prompt": "43329,43330,43331,43332,43333,43334,43335", "answer": "43336"}
{"prompt": "24217,24218,24219,24220,24221,24222,24223,24224", "answer": "24225"}
{"prompt": "18027,18028,18029,18030,18031", "answer": "18032"}
{"prompt": "14217,14218,14219,14220,14221,14222,14223,14224,14225,14226", "answer": "14227"}
{"prompt": "34710,34711,34712,34713,34714,34715,34716,34717", "answer": "34718"}
{"prompt": "43096,43097,43098,43099,43100,43101,43102,43103,43104,43105", "answer": "43106"}
{"prompt": "42904,42905,42906,42907,42908,42909,42910", "answer": "42911"}
{"prompt": "18623,18624,18625,18626,18627,18628,18629,18630", "answer": "18631"}
{"prompt": "43116,43117,43118", "answer": "43119"}
{"prompt": "5746", "answer": "5747"}
{"prompt": "37900,37901,37902,37903,37904,37905,37906", "answer": "37907"}
{"prompt": "12878,12879,12880", "answer": "12881"}
{"prompt": "6321,6322,6323,6324,6325,6326", "answer": "6327"}
{"prompt": "39959,39960,39961,39962,39963,39964,39965,39966", "answer": "39967"}
{"prompt": "17729,17730,17731,17732", "answer": "17733"}
{"prompt": "15211", "answer": "15212"}
{"prompt": "19164,19165,19166,19167", "answer": "19168"}
{"prompt": "18887,18888,18889,18890,18891,18892", "answer": "18893"}
{"prompt": "13666,13667,13668,13669,13670,13671,13672,13673,13674", "answer": "13675"}
{"prompt": "31184,31185,31186,31187,31188,31189,31190,31191,31192,31193", "answer": "31194"}
{"prompt": "403,404,405,406,407", "answer": "408"}
{"prompt": "21683,21684,21685,21686,21687,21688,21689,21690,21691,21692", "answer": "21693"}
{"prompt": "41246,41247,41248,41249,41250,41251,41252", "answer": "41253"}
{"prompt": "26321", "answer": "26322"}
{"prompt": "21645,21646,21647,21648,21649", "answer": "21650"}
{"prompt": "7867,7868", "answer": "7869"}
{"prompt": "35367,35368,35369,35370,35371,35372", "answer": "35373"}
{"prompt": "32456,32457,32458,32459,32460,32461,32462", "answer": "32463"}
{"prompt": "25849,25850,25851,25852,25853,25854,25855,25856", "answer": "25857"}
{"prompt": "9584,9585", "answer": "9586"}
{"prompt": "33214,33215,33216,33217,33218,33219,33220,33221,33222", "answer": "33223"}
{"prompt": "10967,10968,10969,10970,10971,10972,10973,10974,10975", "answer": "10976"}
{"prompt": "22609,22610,22611,22612,22613,22614,22615", "answer": "22616"}
{"prompt": "28550,28551,28552,28553,28554", "answer": "28555"}
{"prompt": "4788,4789,4790,4791,4792,4793", "answer": "4794"}
{"prompt": "5715,5716", "answer": "5717"}
{"prompt": "44613,44614,44615,44616,44617,44618,44619,44620", "answer": "44621"}
{"prompt": "32689,32690,32691,32692", "answer": "32693"}
{"prompt": "17655,17656,17657,17658,17659,17660,17661,17662,17663,17664", "answer": "17665"}
{"prompt": "38708,38709,38710", "answer": "38711"}
{"prompt": "23634,23635,23636,23637,23638", "answer": "23639"}
{"prompt": "21064,21065,21066,21067,21068,21069,21070", "answer": "21071"}
{"prompt": "35206,35207,35208,35209,35210,35211,35212,35213,35214", "answer": "35215"}
{"prompt": "39144,39145,39146", "answer": "39147"}
{"prompt": "29663,29664,29665,29666,29667,29668,29669,29670,29671,29672", "answer": "29673"}
{"prompt": "41252", "answer": "41253"}
{"prompt": "20945,20946,20947,20948,20949", "answer": "20950"}
{"prompt": "13943,13944,13945,13946,13947,13948,13949,13950,13951", "answer": "13952"}
{"prompt": "25600", "answer": "25601"}
{"prompt": "33055,33056,33057,33058,33059,33060,33061,33062,33063", "answer": "33064"}
{"prompt": "25118,25119,25120,25121,25122", "answer": "25123"}
{"prompt": "19302,19303,19304,19305,19306,19307", "answer": "19308"}
{"prompt": "5487,5488,5489,5490,5491,5492,5493,5494,5495", "answer": "5496"}
{"prompt": "35075,35076,35077,35078,35079,35080,35081,35082,35083", "answer": "35084"}
{"prompt": "38211,38212,38213,38214,38215,38216,38217,38218,38219,38220", "answer": "38221"}
{"prompt": "30360,30361,30362,30363,30364,30365,30366,30367,30368", "answer": "30369"}
{"prompt": "10329,10330,10331,10332,10333,10334,10335,10336", "answer": "10337"}
{"prompt": "27712,27713,27714,27715,27716,27717,27718,27719,27720", "answer": "27721"}
{"prompt": "40422,40423,40424,40425,40426,40427,40428", "answer": "40429"}
{"prompt": "16742,16743,16744,16745,16746,16747,16748,16749,16750,16751", "answer": "16752"}
{"prompt": "12371,12372,12373,12374,12375", "answer": "12376"}
{"prompt": "16544", "answer": "16545"}
{"prompt": "11071,11072,11073,11074,11075,11076,11077", "answer": "11078"}
{"prompt": "12808,12809,12810,12811,12812", "answer": "12813"}
{"prompt": "9690,9691,9692,9693,9694,9695,9696,9697,9698", "answer": "9699"}
{"prompt": "26829", "answer": "26830"}
{"prompt": "18258,18259,18260,18261,18262,18263", "answer": "18264"}
{"prompt": "17007,17008,17009", "answer": "17010"}
{"prompt": "30915,30916,30917,30918,30919,30920,30921", "answer": "30922"}
{"prompt": "23957,23958,23959,23960,23961,23962,23963,23964", "answer": "23965"}
{"prompt": "12350,12351,12352,12353", "answer": "12354"}
{"prompt": "25614,25615", "answer": "25616"}
{"prompt": "36400,36401,36402,36403", "answer": "36404"}
{"prompt": "7810,7811,7812,7813,7814,7815,7816,7817", "answer": "7818"}
{"prompt": "41165,41166,41167,41168,41169,41170,41171,41172,41173,41174", "answer": "41175"}
{"prompt": "31959,31960,31961,31962,31963,31964,31965,31966,31967", "answer": "31968"}
{"prompt": "33406,33407,33408,33409,33410,33411,33412,33413,33414,33415", "answer": "33416"}
{"prompt": "37456,37457,37458,37459,37460,37461,37462,37463,37464,37465", "answer": "37466"}
{"prompt": "33522,33523,33524,33525", "answer": "33526"}
{"prompt": "15431,15432,15433,15434", "answer": "15435"}
{"prompt": "13777,13778", "answer": "13779"}
{"prompt": "6267,6268,6269,6270,6271,6272,6273,6274,6275,6276", "answer": "6277"}
{"prompt": "41049,41050,41051,41052,41053,41054,41055,41056", "answer": "41057"}
{"prompt": "31342", "answer": "31343"}
{"prompt": "33044,33045,33046,33047,33048", "answer": "33049"}
{"prompt": "39979,39980,39981,39982,39983,39984,39985,39986,39987,39988", "answer": "39989"}
{"prompt": "35658,35659,35660,35661", "answer": "35662"}
{"prompt": "4615,4616,4617,4618", "answer": "4619"}
{"prompt": "15962,15963,15964,15965,15966,15967,15968,15969", "answer": "15970"}
{"prompt": "16371,16372", "answer": "16373"}
{"prompt": "24265,24266,24267", "answer": "24268"}
{"prompt": "40444,40445,40446,40447", "answer": "40448"}
{"prompt": "37648,37649", "answer": "37650"}
{"prompt": "41967,41968,41969,41970,41971,41972,41973,41974,41975,41976", "answer": "41977"}
{"prompt": "13634,13635,13636,13637,13638,13639", "answer": "13640"}
{"prompt": "26171,26172,26173,26174,26175", "answer": "26176"}
{"prompt": "14936,14937", "answer": "14938"}
{"prompt": "10997,10998,10999,11000,11001,11002,11003,11004,11005", "answer": "11006"}
{"prompt": "33194,33195,33196,33197,33198,33199,33200,33201", "answer": "33202"}
{"prompt": "17863,17864", "answer": "17865"}
{"prompt": "39514,39515,39516,39517,39518,39519,39520,39521,39522,39523", "answer": "39524"}
{"prompt": "843,844,845,846,847,848,849,850,851,852", "answer": "853"}
{"prompt": "41309,41310,41311,41312", "answer": "41313"}
{"prompt": "24159,24160,24161", "answer": "24162"}
{"prompt": "32257,32258,32259,32260,32261,32262,32263,32264,32265,32266", "answer": "32267"}
{"prompt": "41440,41441,41442,41443,41444,41445", "answer": "41446"}
{"prompt": "19913,19914,19915", "answer": "19916"}
{"prompt": "32895,32896,32897,32898,32899,32900,32901,32902", "answer": "32903"}
{"prompt": "29191,29192,29193,29194,29195,29196", "answer": "29197"}
{"prompt": "2536,2537", "answer": "2538"}
{"prompt": "39109,39110,39111,39112,39113,39114,39115,39116", "answer": "39117"}
{"prompt": "37518,37519,37520,37521,37522,37523", "answer": "37524"}
{"prompt": "19245", "answer": "19246"}
{"prompt": "34254,34255,34256,34257,34258,34259,34260,34261,34262", "answer": "34263"}
{"prompt": "25459,25460,25461,25462,25463,25464,25465,25466", "answer": "25467"}
{"prompt": "26229,26230,26231,26232,26233,26234,26235,26236,26237,26238", "answer": "26239"}
{"prompt": "2522,2523,2524,2525", "answer": "2526"}
{"prompt": "17144", "answer": "17145"}
{"prompt": "9096,9097,9098,9099,9100,9101,9102,9103,9104,9105", "answer": "9106"}
{"prompt": "5881,5882", "answer": "5883"}
{"prompt": "36847,36848,36849,36850,36851,36852,36853", "answer": "36854"}
{"prompt": "22459,22460,22461", "answer": "22462"}
{"prompt": "4087,4088,4089", "answer": "4090"}
{"prompt": "23938,23939,23940,23941,23942,23943,23944", "answer": "23945"}
{"prompt": "38589,38590,38591,38592,38593,38594", "answer": "38595"}
{"prompt": "29227", "answer": "29228"}
{"prompt": "6557", "answer": "6558"}
{"prompt": "8976,8977,8978", "answer": "8979"}
{"prompt": "16513,16514", "answer": "16515"}
{"prompt": "22422,22423,22424,22425", "answer": "22426"}
{"prompt": "9105,9106,9107,9108,9109,9110,9111,9112", "answer": "9113"}
{"prompt": "17035,17036,17037,17038", "answer": "17039"}
{"prompt": "36258,36259,36260,36261,36262,36263,36264", "answer": "36265"}
{"prompt": "36996,36997,36998,36999,37000,37001,37002,37003", "answer": "37004"}
{"prompt": "7716,7717", "answer": "7718"}
{"prompt": "37005,37006,37007,37008,37009,37010", "answer": "37011"}
{"prompt": "40494,40495,40496,40497,40498,40499,40500", "answer": "40501"}
{"prompt": "41263,41264,41265,41266,41267,41268,41269", "answer": "41270"}
{"prompt": "4910,4911,4912,4913,4914,4915,4916,4917,4918,4919", "answer": "4920"}
{"prompt": "12097,12098,12099,12100,12101", "answer": "12102"}
{"prompt": "34646,34647,34648,34649", "answer": "34650"}
{"prompt": "17518,17519,17520,17521,17522,17523,17524,17525,17526", "answer": "17527"}
{"prompt": "31392,31393,31394,31395", "answer": "31396"}
{"prompt": "8894,8895,8896", "answer": "8897"}
{"prompt": "27999", "answer": "28000"}
{"prompt": "16994,16995,16996,16997,16998,16999,17000,17001", "answer": "17002"}
{"prompt": "30037,30038,30039", "answer": "30040"}
{"prompt": "7173,7174,7175,7176,7177,7178,7179,7180,7181", "answer": "7182"}
{"prompt": "18975", "answer": "18976"}
{"prompt": "20492,20493,20494,20495,20496", "answer": "20497"}
{"prompt": "14616,14617,14618,14619", "answer": "14620"}
{"prompt": "24413,24414,24415,24416,24417", "answer": "24418"}
{"prompt": "22350,22351,22352,22353,22354,22355,22356,22357,22358,22359", "answer": "22360"}
{"prompt": "815,816,817,818,819,820,821,822,823", "answer": "824"}
{"prompt": "13917,13918,13919,13920,13921,13922,13923,13924", "answer": "13925"}
{"prompt": "3341,3342,3343,3344,3345,3346,3347,3348", "answer": "3349"}
{"prompt": "17501,17502,17503,17504,17505,17506,17507,17508,17509", "answer": "17510"}
{"prompt": "23315,23316,23317,23318,23319,23320,23321,23322,23323,23324", "answer": "23325"}
{"prompt": "21125,21126,21127,21128,21129,21130,21131,21132,21133,21134", "answer": "21135"}
{"prompt": "38850,38851,38852,38853,38854", "answer": "38855"}
{"prompt": "29413,29414,29415,29416,29417,29418,29419,29420", "answer": "29421"}
{"prompt": "44212,44213,44214,44215,44216,44217", "answer": "44218"}
{"prompt": "12183,12184", "answer": "12185"}
{"prompt": "823,824,825,826,827,828,829,830", "answer": "831"}
{"prompt": "15292,15293,15294,15295,15296", "answer": "15297"}
{"prompt": "42328,42329,42330,42331", "answer": "42332"}
{"prompt": "22279", "answer": "22280"}
{"prompt": "43337,43338", "answer": "43339"}
{"prompt": "18694,18695,18696", "answer": "18697"}
{"prompt": "35277,35278,35279,35280,35281,35282,35283,35284,35285", "answer": "35286"}
{"prompt": "43087,43088,43089,43090,43091", "answer": "43092"}
{"prompt": "44158,44159", "answer": "44160"}
{"prompt": "8322,8323,8324", "answer": "8325"}
{"prompt": "23053,23054,23055,23056,23057,23058,23059,23060,23061", "answer": "23062"}
{"prompt": "30417,30418,30419,30420,30421,30422", "answer": "30423"}
{"prompt": "23737,23738,23739,23740,23741,23742,23743,23744,23745", "answer": "23746"}
{"prompt": "7008,7009,7010,7011,7012,7013,7014,7015", "answer": "7016"}
{"prompt": "37045,37046", "answer": "37047"}
{"prompt": "15627,15628,15629,15630,15631,15632", "answer": "15633"}
{"prompt": "29050,29051,29052,29053", "answer": "29054"}
{"prompt": "24382,24383,24384,24385,24386,24387,24388,24389", "answer": "24390"}
{"prompt": "43132,43133,43134,43135,43136,43137,43138,43139,43140,43141", "answer": "43142"}
{"prompt": "42151,42152,42153", "answer": "42154"}
{"prompt": "37562,37563,37564,37565,37566", "answer": "37567"}
{"prompt": "6384,6385,6386", "answer": "6387"}
{"prompt": "24475,24476,24477,24478,24479,24480", "answer": "24481"}
{"prompt": "17205,17206,17207", "answer": "17208"}
{"prompt": "12511,12512,12513,12514", "answer": "12515"}
{"prompt": "19725,19726,19727,19728,19729,19730,19731", "answer": "19732"}
{"prompt": "44742,44743,44744,44745,44746,44747,44748", "answer": "44749"}
{"prompt": "38710,38711,38712,38713,38714,38715,38716,38717,38718,38719", "answer": "38720"}
{"prompt": "15003,15004,15005,15006,15007,15008,15009,15010,15011", "answer": "15012"}
{"prompt": "6577,6578,6579,6580,6581,6582", "answer": "6583"}
{"prompt": "29937,29938,29939,29940,29941,29942,29943,29944,29945,29946", "answer": "29947"}
{"prompt": "16712,16713,16714", "answer": "16715"}
{"prompt": "45037,45038", "answer": "45039"}
{"prompt": "35381,35382,35383,35384,35385,35386,35387,35388,35389,35390", "answer": "35391"}
{"prompt": "18381,18382,18383,18384", "answer": "18385"}
{"prompt": "42167,42168,42169,42170,42171,42172,42173,42174,42175", "answer": "42176"}
{"prompt": "8352,8353,8354,8355,8356", "answer": "8357"}
{"prompt": "30575,30576,30577,30578,30579,30580,30581,30582", "answer": "30583"}
{"prompt": "33682,33683,33684,33685,33686,33687,33688,33689", "answer": "33690"}
{"prompt": "19860,19861,19862,19863,19864,19865", "answer": "19866"}
{"prompt": "18659", "answer": "18660"}
{"prompt": "11932,11933,11934,11935,11936,11937,11938,11939", "answer": "11940"}
{"prompt": "37601,37602,37603,37604,37605,37606,37607,37608,37609,37610", "answer": "37611"}
{"prompt": "23592,23593,23594,23595,23596,23597,23598,23599", "answer": "23600"}
{"prompt": "24816,24817,24818,24819,24820", "answer": "24821"}
{"prompt": "3884,3885", "answer": "3886"}
{"prompt": "32052", "answer": "32053"}
{"prompt": "13632,13633,13634", "answer": "13635"}
{"prompt": "11997", "answer": "11998"}
{"prompt": "10435,10436,10437,10438,10439", "answer": "10440"}
{"prompt": "26145,26146,26147", "answer": "26148"}
{"prompt": "44053,44054,44055,44056,44057,44058,44059", "answer": "44060"}
{"prompt": "8094,8095", "answer": "8096"}
{"prompt": "41144,41145,41146,41147,41148,41149,41150,41151,41152,41153", "answer": "41154"}
{"prompt": "31748,31749,31750,31751,31752,31753,31754,31755", "answer": "31756"}
{"prompt": "20412,20413,20414,20415,20416,20417,20418,20419,20420,20421", "answer": "20422"}
{"prompt": "15031,15032,15033,15034,15035", "answer": "15036"}
{"prompt": "34889,34890", "answer": "34891"}
{"prompt": "6606,6607,6608,6609,6610,6611,6612,6613,6614", "answer": "6615"}
{"prompt": "41132,41133,41134,41135", "answer": "41136"}
{"prompt": "21178,21179,21180,21181,21182,21183,21184", "answer": "21185"}
{"prompt": "4074", "answer": "4075"}
{"prompt": "37746,37747,37748,37749", "answer": "37750"}
{"prompt": "37512,37513,37514,37515,37516,37517,37518", "answer": "37519"}
{"prompt": "14825,14826,14827,14828", "answer": "14829"}
{"prompt": "3560", "answer": "3561"}
{"prompt": "36603,36604,36605,36606,36607,36608,36609", "answer": "36610"}
{"prompt": "38507,38508,38509,38510,38511,38512", "answer": "38513"}
{"prompt": "14243,14244,14245,14246,14247,14248,14249,14250,14251,14252", "answer": "14253"}
{"prompt": "27970", "answer": "27971"}
{"prompt": "41715,41716,41717,41718,41719,41720,41721,41722,41723,41724", "answer": "41725"}
{"prompt": "39523,39524,39525,39526", "answer": "39527"}
{"prompt": "30639,30640,30641,30642,30643,30644,30645", "answer": "30646"}
{"prompt": "18232,18233,18234,18235,18236,18237,18238,18239,18240,18241", "answer": "18242"}
{"prompt": "34649,34650,34651,34652,34653,34654,34655", "answer": "34656"}
{"prompt": "10626,10627,10628,10629,10630", "answer": "10631"}
{"prompt": "29722,29723", "answer": "29724"}
{"prompt": "29819,29820,29821,29822", "answer": "29823"}
{"prompt": "16054,16055,16056", "answer": "16057"}
{"prompt": "45277,45278,45279,45280,45281,45282,45283", "answer": "45284"}
{"prompt": "39394,39395,39396,39397,39398,39399,39400,39401,39402,39403", "answer": "39404"}
{"prompt": "23259,23260,23261,23262,23263,23264,23265,23266,23267", "answer": "23268"}
{"prompt": "6175,6176,6177,6178,6179", "answer": "6180"}
{"prompt": "21707,21708,21709,21710,21711,21712,21713,21714,21715", "answer": "21716"}
{"prompt": "23285,23286,23287,23288,23289", "answer": "23290"}
{"prompt": "5746,5747,5748", "answer": "5749"}
{"prompt": "1044,1045,1046,1047,1048", "answer": "1049"}
{"prompt": "32878,32879,32880,32881,32882,32883,32884,32885,32886", "answer": "32887"}
{"prompt": "25141,25142,25143,25144", "answer": "25145"}
{"prompt": "43664,43665,43666,43667,43668,43669,43670,43671,43672", "answer": "43673"}
{"prompt": "11832,11833,11834,11835", "answer": "11836"}
{"prompt": "10951,10952,10953,10954,10955,10956,10957,10958", "answer": "10959"}
{"prompt": "11382,11383,11384,11385,11386,11387,11388", "answer": "11389"}
{"prompt": "13883,13884,13885,13886,13887", "answer": "13888"}
{"prompt": "19607,19608,19609,19610,19611,19612,19613,19614", "answer": "19615"}
{"prompt": "39335,39336,39337,39338,39339,39340,39341,39342,39343", "answer": "39344"}
{"prompt": "3005,3006,3007,3008,3009,3010,3011,3012,3013,3014", "answer": "3015"}
{"prompt": "12922,12923,12924,12925,12926,12927", "answer": "12928"}
{"prompt": "20856,20857,20858,20859,20860,20861,20862,20863,20864,20865", "answer": "20866"}
{"prompt": "41210", "answer": "41211"}
{"prompt": "23540,23541,23542,23543", "answer": "23544"}
{"prompt": "2860,2861,2862,2863", "answer": "2864"}
{"prompt": "21199,21200,21201,21202,21203,21204,21205,21206,21207", "answer": "21208"}
{"prompt": "24675,24676,24677,24678,24679,24680,24681,24682,24683", "answer": "24684"}
{"prompt": "34178", "answer": "34179"}
{"prompt": "36019,36020,36021,36022,36023", "answer": "36024"}
{"prompt": "42153,42154,42155,42156", "answer": "42157"}
{"prompt": "14641,14642,14643,14644,14645,14646,14647,14648,14649", "answer": "14650"}
{"prompt": "25094,25095,25096,25097,25098,25099", "answer": "25100"}
{"prompt": "41480,41481,41482,41483,41484,41485,41486,41487", "answer": "41488"}
{"prompt": "19717,19718,19719,19720,19721,19722,19723,19724", "answer": "19725"}
{"prompt": "34111,34112,34113,34114,34115,34116,34117,34118,34119,34120", "answer": "34121"}
{"prompt": "34210,34211,34212,34213,34214,34215", "answer": "34216"}
{"prompt": "39050,39051,39052", "answer": "39053"}
{"prompt": "29776,29777,29778,29779,29780,29781,29782,29783,29784", "answer": "29785"}
{"prompt": "31026,31027,31028,31029,31030", "answer": "31031"}
{"prompt": "12972,12973,12974,12975,12976,12977", "answer": "12978"}
{"prompt": "11998", "answer": "11999"}
{"prompt": "37964,37965", "answer": "37966"}
{"prompt": "12829,12830", "answer": "12831"}
{"prompt": "420,421,422,423,424,425,426,427,428", "answer": "429"}
{"prompt": "35586,35587,35588,35589,35590,35591,35592,35593,35594,35595", "answer": "35596"}
{"prompt": "17680", "answer": "17681"}
{"prompt": "14615,14616", "answer": "14617"}
{"prompt": "33384,33385,33386,33387,33388,33389,33390,33391", "answer": "33392"}
{"prompt": "12317,12318,12319,12320,12321", "answer": "12322"}
{"prompt": "22120,22121,22122", "answer": "22123"}
{"prompt": "35719,35720", "answer": "35721"}
{"prompt": "15699,15700,15701,15702,15703,15704", "answer": "15705"}
{"prompt": "37540,37541", "answer": "37542"}
{"prompt": "26873,26874,26875,26876,26877,26878", "answer": "26879"}
{"prompt": "42141", "answer": "42142"}
{"prompt": "10773,10774,10775,10776,10777,10778", "answer": "10779"}
{"prompt": "22757,22758,22759,22760,22761,22762,22763,22764,22765,22766", "answer": "22767"}
{"prompt": "2277,2278,2279,2280,2281,2282,2283", "answer": "2284"}
{"prompt": "8205,8206,8207,8208,8209", "answer": "8210"}
{"prompt": "26067,26068,26069,26070,26071", "answer": "26072"}
{"prompt": "33848,33849,33850,33851,33852", "answer": "33853"}
{"prompt": "41342", "answer": "41343"}
{"prompt": "42823,42824,42825,42826,42827", "answer": "42828"}
{"prompt": "3560,3561,3562,3563,3564,3565,3566,3567,3568", "answer": "3569"}
{"prompt": "11953,11954,11955", "answer": "11956"}
{"prompt": "43917,43918", "answer": "43919"}
{"prompt": "40783,40784,40785", "answer": "40786"}
{"prompt": "17147,17148,17149", "answer": "17150"}
{"prompt": "9996,9997,9998,9999,10000,10001,10002,10003,10004", "answer": "10005"}
{"prompt": "25974,25975,25976,25977", "answer": "25978"}
{"prompt": "4829,4830,4831,4832,4833,4834,4835", "answer": "4836"}
{"prompt": "37300,37301,37302", "answer": "37303"}
{"prompt": "15478,15479,15480,15481,15482,15483,15484,15485,15486", "answer": "15487"}
{"prompt": "41504,41505", "answer": "41506"}
{"prompt": "7717,7718,7719,7720", "answer": "7721"}
{"prompt": "37412,37413,37414,37415", "answer": "37416"}
{"prompt": "36592,36593,36594", "answer": "36595"}
{"prompt": "10235,10236,10237,10238,10239", "answer": "10240"}
{"prompt": "26498,26499,26500,26501,26502,26503,26504,26505,26506", "answer": "26507"}
{"prompt": "25251,25252,25253,25254,25255,25256,25257,25258,25259", "answer": "25260"}
{"prompt": "6711", "answer": "6712"}
{"prompt": "34535,34536", "answer": "34537"}
{"prompt": "22486,22487,22488,22489,22490,22491,22492,22493,22494", "answer": "22495"}
{"prompt": "1618,1619,1620,1621,1622,1623,1624", "answer": "1625"}
{"prompt": "25036,25037,25038,25039", "answer": "25040"}
{"prompt": "27829,27830,27831", "answer": "27832"}
{"prompt": "10381,10382,10383,10384,10385", "answer": "10386"}
{"prompt": "6870,6871,6872", "answer": "6873"}
{"prompt": "25672,25673,25674,25675", "answer": "25676"}
{"prompt": "10317", "answer": "10318"}
{"prompt": "36225,36226", "answer": "36227"}
{"prompt": "30390,30391,30392,30393,30394,30395,30396,30397", "answer": "30398"}
{"prompt": "42697,42698,42699,42700,42701,42702", "answer": "42703"}
{"prompt": "40115,40116,40117,40118,40119,40120,40121,40122", "answer": "40123"}
{"prompt": "32401", "answer": "32402"}
{"prompt": "1725,1726,1727", "answer": "1728"}
{"prompt": "9064", "answer": "9065"}
{"prompt": "19975,19976", "answer": "19977"}
{"prompt": "19064,19065,19066,19067,19068,19069,19070", "answer": "19071"}
{"prompt": "35684,35685,35686,35687,35688", "answer": "35689"}
{"prompt": "11348,11349,11350,11351,11352,11353,11354,11355,11356,11357", "answer": "11358"}
{"prompt": "34162,34163,34164,34165,34166,34167,34168,34169,34170,34171", "answer": "34172"}
{"prompt": "21184,21185,21186,21187,21188,21189,21190", "answer": "21191"}
{"prompt": "7130,7131,7132", "answer": "7133"}
{"prompt": "4304", "answer": "4305"}
{"prompt": "30906,30907,30908,30909,30910,30911,30912,30913,30914", "answer": "30915"}
{"prompt": "2870", "answer": "2871"}
{"prompt": "24380,24381", "answer": "24382"}
{"prompt": "9572,9573,9574,9575,9576,9577,9578,9579,9580,9581", "answer": "9582"}
{"prompt": "39133,39134,39135,39136,39137,39138", "answer": "39139"}
{"prompt": "797,798,799,800,801,802,803", "answer": "804"}
{"prompt": "42144,42145,42146,42147", "answer": "42148"}
{"prompt": "44255,44256,44257,44258,44259,44260,44261", "answer": "44262"}
{"prompt": "29825,29826,29827,29828,29829,29830", "answer": "29831"}
{"prompt": "23757", "answer": "23758"}
{"prompt": "27034,27035,27036,27037,27038", "answer": "27039"}
{"prompt": "2864", "answer": "2865"}
{"prompt": "19009,19010,19011,19012,19013,19014,19015,19016", "answer": "19017"}
{"prompt": "14373,14374", "answer": "14375"}
{"prompt": "3704,3705,3706,3707,3708,3709,3710,3711,3712,3713", "answer": "3714"}
{"prompt": "35484,35485,35486", "answer": "35487"}
{"prompt": "22675,22676,22677,22678,22679,22680,22681,22682,22683", "answer": "22684"}
{"prompt": "5443,5444,5445,5446,5447", "answer": "5448"}
{"prompt": "1360,1361,1362,1363,1364", "answer": "1365"}
{"prompt": "39215", "answer": "39216"}
{"prompt": "32266", "answer": "32267"}
{"prompt": "29853,29854,29855,29856,29857,29858", "answer": "29859"}
{"prompt": "1446,1447", "answer": "1448"}
{"prompt": "17018,17019,17020,17021,17022,17023,17024", "answer": "17025"}
{"prompt": "21115,21116,21117,21118,21119,21120,21121,21122,21123,21124", "answer": "21125"}
{"prompt": "19362", "answer": "19363"}
{"prompt": "39698,39699,39700,39701,39702", "answer": "39703"}
{"prompt": "40443,40444", "answer": "40445"}
{"prompt": "29318,29319,29320", "answer": "29321"}
{"prompt": "17001,17002,17003,17004,17005,17006,17007", "answer": "17008"}
{"prompt": "12927,12928,12929,12930,12931,12932,12933", "answer": "12934"}
{"prompt": "10314,10315,10316,10317", "answer": "10318"}
{"prompt": "33117,33118,33119,33120,33121,33122,33123,33124,33125", "answer": "33126"}
{"prompt": "29357,29358,29359,29360", "answer": "29361"}
{"prompt": "39581,39582,39583,39584,39585,39586,39587,39588,39589,39590", "answer": "39591"}
{"prompt": "5372,5373,5374,5375,5376,5377", "answer": "5378"}
{"prompt": "4688,4689,4690,4691,4692,4693,4694,4695,4696,4697", "answer": "4698"}
{"prompt": "3477,3478,3479,3480", "answer": "3481"}
{"prompt": "39420,39421,39422,39423,39424,39425,39426,39427,39428", "answer": "39429"}
{"prompt": "3048,3049", "answer": "3050"}
{"prompt": "39343,39344,39345,39346,39347", "answer": "39348"}
{"prompt": "9249,9250,9251,9252,9253,9254", "answer": "9255"}
{"prompt": "14836,14837,14838,14839,14840,14841,14842,14843,14844", "answer": "14845"}
{"prompt": "19673,19674,19675,19676,19677,19678,19679,19680", "answer": "19681"}
{"prompt": "29321,29322,29323,29324,29325,29326,29327,29328", "answer": "29329"}
{"prompt": "41046,41047,41048,41049", "answer": "41050"}
{"prompt": "26268", "answer": "26269"}
{"prompt": "37092", "answer": "37093"}
{"prompt": "30849,30850,30851,30852,30853,30854,30855,30856,30857,30858", "answer": "30859"}
{"prompt": "23721,23722,23723,23724,23725,23726,23727", "answer": "23728"}
{"prompt": "11160,11161,11162,11163", "answer": "11164"}
{"prompt": "12168,12169,12170,12171,12172,12173", "answer": "12174"}
{"prompt": "16603,16604,16605,16606,16607,16608", "answer": "16609"}
{"prompt": "617,618", "answer": "619"}
{"prompt": "15587,15588,15589,15590,15591,15592,15593,15594", "answer": "15595"}
{"prompt": "13402,13403,13404", "answer": "13405"}
{"prompt": "11016", "answer": "11017"}
{"prompt": "32707", "answer": "32708"}
{"prompt": "41817,41818,41819,41820,41821,41822,41823,41824,41825,41826", "answer": "41827"}
{"prompt": "32821,32822,32823,32824,32825,32826", "answer": "32827"}
{"prompt": "838,839,840,841,842,843", "answer": "844"}
{"prompt": "11105,11106,11107,11108,11109,11110,11111", "answer": "11112"}
{"prompt": "30346,30347,30348,30349,30350,30351,30352,30353,30354,30355", "answer": "30356"}
{"prompt": "12627,12628", "answer": "12629"}
{"prompt": "26509,26510,26511,26512,26513,26514,26515,26516", "answer": "26517"}
{"prompt": "9391,9392,9393,9394,9395,9396,9397,9398", "answer": "9399"}
{"prompt": "13887,13888,13889", "answer": "13890"}
{"prompt": "39215,39216,39217,39218,39219", "answer": "39220"}
{"prompt": "22261,22262,22263,22264,22265,22266,22267,22268,22269,22270", "answer": "22271"}
{"prompt": "1756,1757,1758,1759,1760", "answer": "1761"}
{"prompt": "13788,13789,13790,13791,13792,13793", "answer": "13794"}
{"prompt": "35988,35989,35990,35991,35992,35993,35994", "answer": "35995"}
{"prompt": "18169,18170,18171,18172,18173,18174,18175,18176,18177", "answer": "18178"}
{"prompt": "29153,29154,29155,29156,29157", "answer": "29158"}
{"prompt": "1416,1417,1418,1419,1420,1421,1422,1423,1424", "answer": "1425"}
{"prompt": "40344,40345,40346,40347,40348", "answer": "40349"}
{"prompt": "30498", "answer": "30499"}
{"prompt": "1702,1703,1704,1705,1706,1707,1708,1709,1710", "answer": "1711"}
{"prompt": "38300,38301,38302,38303,38304,38305,38306", "answer": "38307"}
{"prompt": "36892,36893,36894,36895,36896,36897,36898", "answer": "36899"}
{"prompt": "22896,22897,22898,22899", "answer": "22900"}
{"prompt": "31617,31618", "answer": "31619"}
{"prompt": "7354,7355,7356,7357,7358,7359,7360,7361,7362", "answer": "7363"}
{"prompt": "42091,42092,42093,42094,42095,42096", "answer": "42097"}
{"prompt": "21913,21914,21915,21916,21917,21918,21919", "answer": "21920"}
{"prompt": "43235,43236,43237,43238,43239,43240,43241,43242,43243", "answer": "43244"}
{"prompt": "231", "answer": "232"}
{"prompt": "28903,28904,28905,28906,28907,28908,28909,28910", "answer": "28911"}
{"prompt": "40290,40291,40292,40293,40294,40295,40296,40297,40298,40299", "answer": "40300"}
{"prompt": "35097,35098,35099,35100", "answer": "35101"}
{"prompt": "14434,14435,14436,14437,14438,14439", "answer": "14440"}
{"prompt": "45265,45266,45267,45268", "answer": "45269"}
{"prompt": "42331,42332,42333,42334,42335,42336,42337,42338,42339", "answer": "42340"}
{"prompt": "44955,44956,44957,44958,44959,44960,44961", "answer": "44962"}
{"prompt": "4111,4112,4113,4114,4115", "answer": "4116"}
{"prompt": "44590,44591,44592,44593,44594,44595,44596,44597,44598,44599", "answer": "44600"}
{"prompt": "41422,41423,41424,41425,41426", "answer": "41427"}
{"prompt": "32250,32251,32252,32253,32254,32255", "answer": "32256"}
{"prompt": "33003,33004,33005,33006,33007,33008,33009", "answer": "33010"}
{"prompt": "14017,14018,14019,14020,14021,14022,14023,14024,14025", "answer": "14026"}
{"prompt": "36530,36531,36532,36533,36534,36535,36536", "answer": "36537"}
{"prompt": "16740,16741,16742", "answer": "16743"}
{"prompt": "22441,22442,22443,22444,22445,22446,22447", "answer": "22448"}
{"prompt": "4276,4277,4278,4279,4280,4281", "answer": "4282"}
{"prompt": "23645,23646,23647", "answer": "23648"}
{"prompt": "9642,9643,9644,9645,9646,9647,9648,9649,9650", "answer": "9651"}
{"prompt": "37833,37834,37835,37836,37837,37838,37839", "answer": "37840"}
{"prompt": "35051,35052,35053,35054,35055", "answer": "35056"}
{"prompt": "1900,1901,1902,1903,1904,1905", "answer": "1906"}
{"prompt": "15765,15766,15767,15768", "answer": "15769"}
{"prompt": "15044,15045,15046,15047,15048,15049,15050,15051,15052", "answer": "15053"}
{"prompt": "39127,39128", "answer": "39129"}
{"prompt": "24411,24412", "answer": "24413"}
{"prompt": "18044,18045,18046,18047,18048,18049,18050,18051,18052,18053", "answer": "18054"}
{"prompt": "381,382,383,384,385,386,387,388", "answer": "389"}
{"prompt": "40692", "answer": "40693"}
{"prompt": "25587,25588,25589,25590,25591,25592,25593,25594,25595", "answer": "25596"}
{"prompt": "33183", "answer": "33184"}
{"prompt": "27005,27006,27007,27008,27009,27010", "answer": "27011"}
{"prompt": "21322,21323,21324,21325,21326,21327,21328,21329,21330", "answer": "21331"}
{"prompt": "4793,4794,4795,4796,4797,4798,4799,4800", "answer": "4801"}
{"prompt": "11981,11982,11983,11984,11985,11986,11987,11988,11989", "answer": "11990"}
{"prompt": "5943,5944,5945,5946,5947,5948,5949,5950,5951,5952", "answer": "5953"}
{"prompt": "409,410,411,412", "answer": "413"}
{"prompt": "15162,15163,15164,15165,15166", "answer": "15167"}
{"prompt": "24470", "answer": "24471"}
{"prompt": "3722,3723,3724,3725", "answer": "3726"}
{"prompt": "45226,45227,45228,45229,45230,45231,45232,45233", "answer": "45234"}
{"prompt": "12965,12966,12967,12968,12969,12970,12971,12972", "answer": "12973"}
{"prompt": "2988,2989,2990,2991,2992,2993,2994,2995,2996,2997", "answer": "2998"}
{"prompt": "17232,17233,17234,17235,17236", "answer": "17237"}
{"prompt": "3910,3911", "answer": "3912"}
{"prompt": "19182", "answer": "19183"}
{"prompt": "34469,34470", "answer": "34471"}
{"prompt": "28122", "answer": "28123"}
{"prompt": "6065,6066,6067,6068,6069,6070", "answer": "6071"}
{"prompt": "6645", "answer": "6646"}
{"prompt": "15738,15739", "answer": "15740"}
{"prompt": "38968,38969,38970,38971,38972,38973", "answer": "38974"}
{"prompt": "1226,1227,1228,1229,1230,1231,1232,1233,1234", "answer": "1235"}
{"prompt": "40486,40487,40488,40489,40490,40491,40492,40493,40494", "answer": "40495"}
{"prompt": "25159,25160,25161", "answer": "25162"}
{"prompt": "14556", "answer": "14557"}
{"prompt": "42718,42719,42720,42721,42722,42723,42724", "answer": "42725"}
{"prompt": "10677", "answer": "10678"}
{"prompt": "5594,5595,5596,5597,5598,5599,5600", "answer": "5601"}
{"prompt": "44474,44475,44476", "answer": "44477"}
{"prompt": "33920,33921,33922,33923,33924,33925,33926,33927", "answer": "33928"}
{"prompt": "24412,24413", "answer": "24414"}
{"prompt": "31314,31315,31316,31317,31318,31319,31320,31321,31322", "answer": "31323"}
{"prompt": "12701,12702,12703,12704,12705,12706,12707,12708,12709,12710", "answer": "12711"}
{"prompt": "3417,3418,3419,3420,3421,3422,3423,3424,3425", "answer": "3426"}
{"prompt": "28311,28312,28313,28314,28315,28316,28317,28318,28319,28320", "answer": "28321"}
{"prompt": "11297,11298,11299,11300,11301,11302,11303,11304,11305", "answer": "11306"}
{"prompt": "7844,7845,7846,7847,7848,7849,7850,7851,7852,7853", "answer": "7854"}
{"prompt": "1579", "answer": "1580"}
{"prompt": "6970,6971,6972,6973,6974", "answer": "6975"}
{"prompt": "18586,18587,18588,18589,18590", "answer": "18591"}
{"prompt": "34893,34894,34895,34896,34897,34898,34899", "answer": "34900"}
{"prompt": "29924,29925,29926,29927,29928", "answer": "29929"}
{"prompt": "24092,24093,24094,24095,24096,24097,24098,24099,24100", "answer": "24101"}
{"prompt": "2814,2815,2816,2817,2818,2819", "answer": "2820"}
{"prompt": "30465,30466,30467,30468,30469,30470,30471,30472,30473,30474", "answer": "30475"}
{"prompt": "22255,22256,22257,22258,22259,22260,22261", "answer": "22262"}
{"prompt": "22718,22719,22720", "answer": "22721"}
{"prompt": "38,39", "answer": "40"}
{"prompt": "18637,18638,18639", "answer": "18640"}
{"prompt": "12721", "answer": "12722"}
{"prompt": "31861,31862,31863,31864,31865,31866,31867,31868,31869,31870", "answer": "31871"}
{"prompt": "13876,13877,13878,13879,13880,13881,13882,13883", "answer": "13884"}
{"prompt": "8722,8723", "answer": "8724"}
{"prompt": "30680,30681,30682,30683,30684", "answer": "30685"}
{"prompt": "27791", "answer": "27792"}
{"prompt": "8221,8222,8223,8224,8225,8226", "answer": "8227"}
{"prompt": "962,963,964,965", "answer": "966"}
{"prompt": "21784,21785", "answer": "21786"}
{"prompt": "24992,24993,24994", "answer": "24995"}
{"prompt": "31096,31097,31098", "answer": "31099"}
{"prompt": "31479,31480,31481,31482,31483,31484,31485,31486,31487", "answer": "31488"}
{"prompt": "2590,2591,2592,2593,2594,2595,2596,2597,2598,2599", "answer": "2600"}
{"prompt": "19792,19793,19794,19795", "answer": "19796"}
{"prompt": "14760,14761,14762", "answer": "14763"}
{"prompt": "36375,36376,36377,36378,36379,36380,36381,36382", "answer": "36383"}
{"prompt": "15832,15833,15834,15835,15836,15837,15838,15839", "answer": "15840"}
{"prompt": "38160,38161,38162", "answer": "38163"}
{"prompt": "40649,40650,40651,40652,40653,40654,40655", "answer": "40656"}
{"prompt": "29564,29565,29566", "answer": "29567"}
{"prompt": "14992,14993,14994,14995,14996,14997,14998", "answer": "14999"}
{"prompt": "4955,4956,4957,4958", "answer": "4959"}
{"prompt": "11955,11956,11957,11958,11959,11960", "answer": "11961"}
{"prompt": "38484,38485,38486,38487,38488,38489,38490,38491,38492", "answer": "38493"}
{"prompt": "38937,38938,38939", "answer": "38940"}
{"prompt": "3528,3529,3530,3531,3532", "answer": "3533"}
{"prompt": "9010,9011,9012,9013,9014,9015,9016,9017,9018,9019", "answer": "9020"}
{"prompt": "28463,28464,28465", "answer": "28466"}
{"prompt": "41693", "answer": "41694"}
{"prompt": "44793,44794,44795,44796,44797,44798,44799,44800", "answer": "44801"}
{"prompt": "24942", "answer": "24943"}
{"prompt": "32947,32948,32949,32950,32951,32952,32953,32954", "answer": "32955"}
{"prompt": "7883,7884,7885,7886,7887,7888,7889", "answer": "7890"}
{"prompt": "26067", "answer": "26068"}
{"prompt": "14768,14769,14770,14771,14772,14773,14774,14775,14776,14777", "answer": "14778"}
{"prompt": "25598,25599,25600", "answer": "25601"}
{"prompt": "20404,20405,20406,20407,20408,20409,20410,20411", "answer": "20412"}
{"prompt": "28087,28088,28089,28090,28091", "answer": "28092"}
{"prompt": "3659,3660,3661", "answer": "3662"}
{"prompt": "12890,12891,12892,12893,12894,12895", "answer": "12896"}
{"prompt": "5882,5883", "answer": "5884"}
{"prompt": "17739,17740,17741,17742,17743", "answer": "17744"}
{"prompt": "151,152,153,154,155,156", "answer": "157"}
{"prompt": "28238,28239,28240,28241,28242,28243,28244", "answer": "28245"}
{"prompt": "20614,20615,20616,20617,20618,20619,20620,20621,20622,20623", "answer": "20624"}
{"prompt": "25522,25523,25524,25525,25526,25527,25528", "answer": "25529"}
{"prompt": "40828,40829,40830,40831,40832,40833", "answer": "40834"}
{"prompt": "37920,37921,37922", "answer": "37923"}
{"prompt": "3300,3301,3302,3303", "answer": "3304"}
{"prompt": "33733,33734,33735,33736,33737", "answer": "33738"}
{"prompt": "7569,7570,7571,7572", "answer": "7573"}
{"prompt": "8751,8752,8753,8754,8755,8756,8757,8758,8759,8760", "answer": "8761"}
{"prompt": "6839,6840,6841,6842,6843,6844", "answer": "6845"}
{"prompt": "2906,2907,2908,2909,2910,2911,2912,2913", "answer": "2914"}
{"prompt": "11520,11521,11522,11523,11524,11525,11526,11527,11528", "answer": "11529"}
{"prompt": "11278,11279,11280,11281", "answer": "11282"}
{"prompt": "6372,6373,6374,6375,6376,6377,6378,6379", "answer": "6380"}
{"prompt": "35453,35454,35455,35456", "answer": "35457"}
{"prompt": "27824,27825,27826,27827,27828,27829", "answer": "27830"}
{"prompt": "37973,37974", "answer": "37975"}
{"prompt": "13,14", "answer": "15"}
{"prompt": "17091,17092,17093,17094,17095,17096,17097,17098,17099", "answer": "17100"}
{"prompt": "6114,6115,6116,6117,6118,6119,6120,6121,6122,6123", "answer": "6124"}
{"prompt": "14832,14833", "answer": "14834"}
{"prompt": "17026", "answer": "17027"}
{"prompt": "12962,12963,12964,12965", "answer": "12966"}
{"prompt": "5254,5255,5256,5257,5258,5259,5260,5261,5262", "answer": "5263"}
{"prompt": "36822,36823,36824,36825,36826,36827", "answer": "36828"}
{"prompt": "37267,37268,37269,37270,37271,37272,37273,37274,37275", "answer": "37276"}
{"prompt": "1875,1876,1877,1878,1879", "answer": "1880"}
{"prompt": "12473,12474,12475,12476,12477,12478,12479,12480,12481,12482", "answer": "12483"}
{"prompt": "34105,34106,34107,34108", "answer": "34109"}
{"prompt": "4835,4836", "answer": "4837"}
{"prompt": "5187,5188,5189,5190,5191,5192,5193,5194", "answer": "5195"}
{"prompt": "21076,21077,21078,21079,21080,21081,21082,21083", "answer": "21084"}
{"prompt": "30057,30058,30059", "answer": "30060"}
{"prompt": "19380,19381,19382,19383,19384,19385,19386,19387", "answer": "19388"}
{"prompt": "27458,27459,27460,27461", "answer": "27462"}
{"prompt": "38108,38109,38110,38111,38112", "answer": "38113"}
{"prompt": "11252,11253", "answer": "11254"}
{"prompt": "41836,41837,41838", "answer": "41839"}
{"prompt": "36079,36080,36081,36082,36083,36084,36085", "answer": "36086"}
{"prompt": "6081,6082,6083,6084,6085,6086,6087,6088", "answer": "6089"}
{"prompt": "1009,1010", "answer": "1011"}
{"prompt": "44461,44462,44463,44464,44465,44466,44467,44468,44469", "answer": "44470"}
{"prompt": "31106,31107,31108,31109,31110,31111,31112,31113", "answer": "31114"}
{"prompt": "21420,21421,21422,21423,21424,21425", "answer": "21426"}
{"prompt": "10107,10108,10109,10110,10111", "answer": "10112"}
{"prompt": "15885,15886,15887,15888,15889,15890,15891,15892", "answer": "15893"}
{"prompt": "36110,36111,36112,36113,36114,36115,36116,36117,36118", "answer": "36119"}
{"prompt": "3955,3956,3957,3958,3959", "answer": "3960"}
{"prompt": "30954,30955,30956,30957", "answer": "30958"}
{"prompt": "8694,8695,8696,8697,8698", "answer": "8699"}
{"prompt": "1427,1428,1429,1430,1431,1432,1433,1434,1435", "answer": "1436"}
{"prompt": "11245,11246,11247,11248", "answer": "11249"}
{"prompt": "15035,15036,15037,15038", "answer": "15039"}
{"prompt": "36425,36426,36427,36428,36429,36430", "answer": "36431"}
{"prompt": "17919", "answer": "17920"}
{"prompt": "37444,37445,37446,37447,37448,37449,37450,37451,37452,37453", "answer": "37454"}
{"prompt": "22328,22329,22330,22331,22332,22333,22334,22335,22336,22337", "answer": "22338"}
{"prompt": "14031,14032,14033,14034,14035,14036,14037,14038", "answer": "14039"}
{"prompt": "30729,30730,30731,30732,30733,30734,30735", "answer": "30736"}
{"prompt": "44178,44179,44180,44181,44182", "answer": "44183"}
{"prompt": "9055,9056,9057,9058,9059,9060,9061,9062,9063,9064", "answer": "9065"}
{"prompt": "29393,29394,29395,29396,29397,29398", "answer": "29399"}
{"prompt": "29084,29085", "answer": "29086"}
{"prompt": "16171,16172,16173,16174,16175", "answer": "16176"}
{"prompt": "25875,25876,25877,25878,25879,25880,25881", "answer": "25882"}
{"prompt": "31731,31732,31733", "answer": "31734"}
{"prompt": "44005,44006", "answer": "44007"}
{"prompt": "16945,16946", "answer": "16947"}
{"prompt": "32418,32419,32420,32421,32422,32423,32424", "answer": "32425"}
{"prompt": "16333,16334,16335,16336,16337", "answer": "16338"}
{"prompt": "38339,38340,38341,38342,38343,38344,38345,38346,38347,38348", "answer": "38349"}
{"prompt": "6882,6883,6884,6885,6886,6887,6888,6889", "answer": "6890"}
{"prompt": "20315,20316,20317,20318,20319,20320,20321,20322,20323,20324", "answer": "20325"}
{"prompt": "17305,17306,17307,17308,17309,17310,17311,17312,17313", "answer": "17314"}
{"prompt": "45077,45078,45079", "answer": "45080"}
{"prompt": "11478,11479,11480,11481,11482,11483,11484", "answer": "11485"}
{"prompt": "13448,13449,13450,13451,13452,13453,13454,13455", "answer": "13456"}
{"prompt": "30772,30773,30774,30775,30776,30777,30778,30779", "answer": "30780"}
{"prompt": "3663,3664,3665,3666,3667,3668,3669,3670,3671,3672", "answer": "3673"}
{"prompt": "24197,24198", "answer": "24199"}
{"prompt": "12606,12607", "answer": "12608"}
{"prompt": "40420,40421,40422", "answer": "40423"}
{"prompt": "28541,28542,28543,28544,28545", "answer": "28546"}
{"prompt": "34171,34172,34173,34174,34175,34176", "answer": "34177"}
{"prompt": "5860,5861,5862,5863,5864,5865,5866", "answer": "5867"}
{"prompt": "253,254,255,256,257,258,259,260", "answer": "261"}
{"prompt": "13480", "answer": "13481"}
{"prompt": "23469,23470,23471,23472,23473,23474,23475,23476,23477", "answer": "23478"}
{"prompt": "3839,3840,3841,3842,3843,3844,3845,3846", "answer": "3847"}
{"prompt": "39227,39228,39229,39230,39231,39232,39233,39234,39235,39236", "answer": "39237"}
{"prompt": "29038,29039,29040,29041,29042", "answer": "29043"}
{"prompt": "1189,1190,1191,1192,1193,1194,1195,1196,1197", "answer": "1198"}
{"prompt": "21859,21860,21861,21862,21863,21864,21865,21866", "answer": "21867"}
{"prompt": "24589,24590,24591,24592,24593", "answer": "24594"}
{"prompt": "29891,29892,29893", "answer": "29894"}
{"prompt": "29025,29026,29027,29028,29029", "answer": "29030"}
{"prompt": "14003,14004,14005,14006", "answer": "14007"}
{"prompt": "40206,40207,40208,40209", "answer": "40210"}
{"prompt": "27886,27887,27888,27889,27890,27891,27892,27893,27894", "answer": "27895"}
{"prompt": "17319,17320,17321,17322,17323,17324,17325,17326,17327", "answer": "17328"}
{"prompt": "29093,29094,29095,29096,29097", "answer": "29098"}
{"prompt": "17648,17649,17650,17651,17652,17653,17654,17655", "answer": "17656"}
{"prompt": "39007,39008,39009,39010,39011,39012", "answer": "39013"}
{"prompt": "23533,23534,23535,23536,23537", "answer": "23538"}
{"prompt": "35055,35056,35057,35058,35059,35060,35061,35062,35063,35064", "answer": "35065"}
{"prompt": "19174,19175,19176,19177,19178,19179", "answer": "19180"}
{"prompt": "4252,4253,4254,4255,4256,4257,4258,4259", "answer": "4260"}
{"prompt": "1102,1103,1104,1105,1106,1107,1108,1109", "answer": "1110"}
{"prompt": "9727,9728,9729,9730,9731,9732,9733,9734,9735,9736", "answer": "9737"}
{"prompt": "17348,17349,17350,17351,17352,17353,17354,17355,17356,17357", "answer": "17358"}
{"prompt": "39938", "answer": "39939"}
{"prompt": "9619,9620,9621,9622,9623,9624,9625,9626,9627,9628", "answer": "9629"}
{"prompt": "33295,33296,33297,33298,33299,33300", "answer": "33301"}
{"prompt": "19025,19026,19027,19028,19029,19030,19031", "answer": "19032"}
{"prompt": "3327,3328,3329,3330,3331,3332,3333,3334", "answer": "3335"}
{"prompt": "10094,10095,10096,10097,10098,10099,10100,10101", "answer": "10102"}
{"prompt": "20479,20480,20481,20482,20483,20484", "answer": "20485"}
{"prompt": "18711,18712,18713,18714,18715,18716,18717", "answer": "18718"}
{"prompt": "45060,45061,45062,45063,45064,45065,45066,45067,45068", "answer": "45069"}
{"prompt": "43206,43207,43208,43209,43210,43211", "answer": "43212"}
{"prompt": "34436,34437", "answer": "34438"}
{"prompt": "10813,10814,10815,10816,10817,10818,10819,10820,10821,10822", "answer": "10823"}
{"prompt": "25418,25419,25420", "answer": "25421"}
{"prompt": "41122,41123,41124", "answer": "41125"}
{"prompt": "12990,12991,12992,12993,12994", "answer": "12995"}
{"prompt": "38694,38695,38696,38697,38698,38699,38700,38701", "answer": "38702"}
{"prompt": "26189,26190,26191,26192,26193,26194,26195", "answer": "26196"}
{"prompt": "34994,34995", "answer": "34996"}
{"prompt": "21106,21107", "answer": "21108"}
{"prompt": "31113,31114,31115,31116", "answer": "31117"}
{"prompt": "5742,5743,5744,5745,5746", "answer": "5747"}
{"prompt": "38733,38734,38735,38736,38737,38738,38739,38740", "answer": "38741"}
{"prompt": "36470,36471,36472,36473", "answer": "36474"}
{"prompt": "1289,1290,1291,1292,1293,1294,1295,1296,1297,1298", "answer": "1299"}
{"prompt": "6326", "answer": "6327"}
{"prompt": "25600,25601,25602,25603", "answer": "25604"}
{"prompt": "30651,30652,30653,30654", "answer": "30655"}
{"prompt": "16716", "answer": "16717"}
{"prompt": "19351,19352,19353,19354,19355,19356,19357", "answer": "19358"}
{"prompt": "23953,23954,23955", "answer": "23956"}
{"prompt": "37280,37281,37282,37283,37284,37285,37286", "answer": "37287"}
{"prompt": "13644,13645,13646,13647", "answer": "13648"}
{"prompt": "21458,21459,21460,21461,21462,21463,21464,21465", "answer": "21466"}
{"prompt": "13340,13341,13342,13343,13344,13345", "answer": "13346"}
{"prompt": "18192,18193,18194,18195,18196,18197,18198,18199,18200,18201", "answer": "18202"}
{"prompt": "3398,3399,3400,3401,3402,3403,3404,3405,3406", "answer": "3407"}
{"prompt": "42533,42534,42535,42536,42537,42538,42539,42540", "answer": "42541"}
{"prompt": "44843,44844,44845,44846,44847,44848,44849", "answer": "44850"}
{"prompt": "34215,34216,34217", "answer": "34218"}
{"prompt": "9657,9658,9659,9660,9661,9662,9663,9664", "answer": "9665"}
{"prompt": "38153", "answer": "38154"}
{"prompt": "6560,6561,6562,6563,6564", "answer": "6565"}
{"prompt": "31378,31379,31380,31381,31382,31383,31384,31385,31386", "answer": "31387"}
{"prompt": "10239,10240,10241,10242,10243,10244,10245,10246", "answer": "10247"}
{"prompt": "6983,6984,6985,6986,6987,6988", "answer": "6989"}
{"prompt": "28815,28816,28817,28818,28819", "answer": "28820"}
{"prompt": "15473", "answer": "15474"}
{"prompt": "11835,11836,11837", "answer": "11838"}
{"prompt": "20989,20990,20991,20992", "answer": "20993"}
{"prompt": "5215,5216,5217,5218,5219,5220", "answer": "5221"}
{"prompt": "10439,10440,10441,10442,10443,10444,10445,10446,10447,10448", "answer": "10449"}
{"prompt": "43181,43182,43183,43184,43185,43186,43187,43188,43189", "answer": "43190"}
{"prompt": "41573,41574,41575,41576,41577,41578,41579,41580,41581,41582", "answer": "41583"}
{"prompt": "38492,38493,38494,38495,38496,38497,38498", "answer": "38499"}
{"prompt": "34704", "answer": "34705"}
{"prompt": "1859,1860", "answer": "1861"}
{"prompt": "11633,11634,11635,11636", "answer": "11637"}
{"prompt": "4919,4920,4921,4922,4923,4924,4925", "answer": "4926"}
{"prompt": "27526,27527,27528,27529,27530,27531,27532", "answer": "27533"}
{"prompt": "43610,43611,43612,43613,43614,43615,43616,43617,43618,43619", "answer": "43620"}
{"prompt": "34459,34460,34461,34462", "answer": "34463"}
{"prompt": "37789,37790,37791,37792,37793,37794,37795,37796,37797,37798", "answer": "37799"}
{"prompt": "11534,11535,11536,11537,11538,11539,11540", "answer": "11541"}
{"prompt": "9171,9172,9173,9174,9175,9176,9177,9178", "answer": "9179"}
{"prompt": "27010,27011,27012,27013,27014,27015", "answer": "27016"}
{"prompt": "2943,2944,2945", "answer": "2946"}
{"prompt": "17076,17077,17078,17079,17080,17081,17082", "answer": "17083"}
{"prompt": "14098,14099,14100,14101,14102,14103,14104,14105,14106", "answer": "14107"}
{"prompt": "23799,23800,23801", "answer": "23802"}
{"prompt": "8086,8087,8088,8089,8090,8091", "answer": "8092"}
{"prompt": "345", "answer": "346"}
{"prompt": "31197,31198,31199,31200,31201,31202,31203,31204", "answer": "31205"}
{"prompt": "29992,29993,29994", "answer": "29995"}
{"prompt": "23372,23373,23374,23375,23376,23377,23378,23379", "answer": "23380"}
{"prompt": "21947,21948,21949,21950,21951", "answer": "21952"}
{"prompt": "11915,11916,11917,11918,11919,11920,11921,11922,11923", "answer": "11924"}
{"prompt": "38864,38865,38866,38867,38868,38869,38870,38871,38872,38873", "answer": "38874"}
{"prompt": "3147,3148,3149,3150,3151,3152,3153", "answer": "3154"}
{"prompt": "27211,27212,27213,27214,27215,27216,27217,27218,27219,27220", "answer": "27221"}
{"prompt": "6756,6757,6758,6759,6760,6761,6762,6763,6764,6765", "answer": "6766"}
{"prompt": "3316,3317,3318,3319,3320,3321,3322,3323,3324", "answer": "3325"}
{"prompt": "4297,4298,4299,4300,4301,4302,4303,4304", "answer": "4305"}
{"prompt": "3225,3226,3227,3228,3229,3230,3231,3232", "answer": "3233"}
{"prompt": "17161,17162", "answer": "17163"}
{"prompt": "21026,21027,21028,21029,21030,21031", "answer": "21032"}
{"prompt": "38002,38003,38004,38005,38006,38007,38008,38009,38010,38011", "answer": "38012"}
{"prompt": "25965,25966,25967,25968,25969,25970,25971,25972,25973,25974", "answer": "25975"}
{"prompt": "21089,21090,21091,21092,21093,21094,21095", "answer": "21096"}
{"prompt": "17274,17275,17276,17277,17278,17279", "answer": "17280"}
{"prompt": "37317", "answer": "37318"}
{"prompt": "4349,4350,4351,4352", "answer": "4353"}
{"prompt": "13141,13142", "answer": "13143"}
{"prompt": "20831", "answer": "20832"}
{"prompt": "10278,10279", "answer": "10280"}
{"prompt": "42926,42927,42928,42929", "answer": "42930"}
{"prompt": "39429", "answer": "39430"}
{"prompt": "23693,23694,23695,23696,23697,23698,23699,23700", "answer": "23701"}
{"prompt": "6409,6410,6411,6412,6413,6414,6415,6416,6417,6418", "answer": "6419"}
{"prompt": "15313,15314,15315,15316,15317,15318,15319,15320", "answer": "15321"}
{"prompt": "18774", "answer": "18775"}
{"prompt": "25667", "answer": "25668"}
{"prompt": "7393,7394,7395,7396", "answer": "7397"}
{"prompt": "37988,37989,37990,37991,37992,37993,37994", "answer": "37995"}
{"prompt": "37956,37957,37958,37959,37960,37961,37962,37963,37964", "answer": "37965"}
{"prompt": "1580,1581,1582,1583,1584,1585,1586", "answer": "1587"}
{"prompt": "27952,27953,27954", "answer": "27955"}
{"prompt": "6391,6392,6393,6394,6395", "answer": "6396"}
{"prompt": "33275,33276,33277,33278,33279,33280,33281,33282,33283", "answer": "33284"}
{"prompt": "43211,43212,43213,43214,43215,43216,43217,43218,43219,43220", "answer": "43221"}
{"prompt": "42894,42895,42896,42897,42898,42899,42900,42901,42902", "answer": "42903"}
{"prompt": "45000,45001,45002,45003,45004,45005,45006,45007", "answer": "45008"}
{"prompt": "34401,34402", "answer": "34403"}
{"prompt": "7166,7167,7168,7169,7170,7171,7172,7173", "answer": "7174"}
{"prompt": "2313,2314,2315,2316,2317,2318,2319,2320,2321", "answer": "2322"}
{"prompt": "2194,2195,2196,2197,2198,2199,2200,2201,2202", "answer": "2203"}
{"prompt": "24986,24987,24988,24989,24990,24991", "answer": "24992"}
{"prompt": "35411,35412,35413,35414,35415,35416", "answer": "35417"}
{"prompt": "28918,28919,28920", "answer": "28921"}
{"prompt": "29405,29406,29407,29408,29409,29410,29411,29412", "answer": "29413"}
{"prompt": "24824,24825,24826,24827,24828,24829,24830,24831,24832", "answer": "24833"}
{"prompt": "489,490,491", "answer": "492"}
{"prompt": "30735,30736,30737,30738,30739,30740,30741", "answer": "30742"}
{"prompt": "13770,13771,13772", "answer": "13773"}
{"prompt": "29834,29835,29836,29837,29838,29839,29840,29841,29842,29843", "answer": "29844"}
{"prompt": "43935", "answer": "43936"}
{"prompt": "29433,29434,29435,29436,29437,29438,29439,29440", "answer": "29441"}
{"prompt": "26462,26463,26464,26465,26466", "answer": "26467"}
{"prompt": "39995,39996,39997,39998,39999,40000", "answer": "40001"}
{"prompt": "25055", "answer": "25056"}
{"prompt": "12449,12450", "answer": "12451"}
{"prompt": "586,587,588", "answer": "589"}
{"prompt": "27502,27503,27504,27505", "answer": "27506"}
{"prompt": "42509,42510,42511,42512,42513,42514,42515", "answer": "42516"}
{"prompt": "38689,38690,38691,38692,38693", "answer": "38694"}
{"prompt": "7226,7227,7228,7229,7230,7231", "answer": "7232"}
{"prompt": "42611,42612,42613,42614,42615,42616,42617,42618,42619", "answer": "42620"}
{"prompt": "20191,20192,20193,20194,20195,20196,20197,20198,20199,20200", "answer": "20201"}
{"prompt": "3574,3575,3576,3577,3578,3579,3580,3581", "answer": "3582"}
{"prompt": "11791,11792", "answer": "11793"}
{"prompt": "34088,34089,34090,34091,34092,34093,34094,34095,34096", "answer": "34097"}
{"prompt": "26516,26517,26518,26519,26520,26521,26522", "answer": "26523"}
{"prompt": "38521,38522,38523,38524,38525", "answer": "38526"}
{"prompt": "16506,16507,16508,16509,16510,16511,16512,16513", "answer": "16514"}
{"prompt": "40545,40546,40547,40548", "answer": "40549"}
{"prompt": "4402,4403,4404,4405,4406", "answer": "4407"}
{"prompt": "30525,30526,30527,30528,30529", "answer": "30530"}
{"prompt": "3000,3001", "answer": "3002"}
{"prompt": "39301,39302,39303,39304,39305", "answer": "39306"}
{"prompt": "6557,6558,6559,6560", "answer": "6561"}
{"prompt": "44621,44622,44623,44624,44625,44626", "answer": "44627"}
{"prompt": "26313,26314,26315,26316,26317,26318,26319,26320,26321", "answer": "26322"}
{"prompt": "5674,5675,5676,5677", "answer": "5678"}
{"prompt": "40433,40434,40435,40436,40437", "answer": "40438"}
{"prompt": "22837,22838,22839,22840,22841,22842,22843,22844,22845", "answer": "22846"}
{"prompt": "1016,1017,1018,1019", "answer": "1020"}
{"prompt": "31088", "answer": "31089"}
{"prompt": "1357,1358,1359,1360", "answer": "1361"}
{"prompt": "3822,3823,3824,3825,3826,3827,3828,3829,3830", "answer": "3831"}
{"prompt": "29893,29894,29895,29896,29897", "answer": "29898"}
{"prompt": "38796,38797", "answer": "38798"}
{"prompt": "39614,39615,39616,39617,39618,39619,39620", "answer": "39621"}
{"prompt": "32853", "answer": "32854"}
{"prompt": "28585,28586,28587,28588,28589,28590", "answer": "28591"}
{"prompt": "6432,6433", "answer": "6434"}
{"prompt": "18202,18203,18204,18205,18206,18207,18208,18209,18210", "answer": "18211"}
{"prompt": "16882,16883,16884,16885,16886,16887", "answer": "16888"}
{"prompt": "23566,23567", "answer": "23568"}
{"prompt": "22615,22616,22617", "answer": "22618"}
{"prompt": "17459,17460,17461", "answer": "17462"}
{"prompt": "43846,43847,43848,43849,43850", "answer": "43851"}
{"prompt": "1075", "answer": "1076"}
{"prompt": "21232,21233,21234,21235,21236", "answer": "21237"}
{"prompt": "37649,37650,37651,37652,37653,37654,37655", "answer": "37656"}
{"prompt": "38240", "answer": "38241"}
{"prompt": "32787,32788,32789,32790", "answer": "32791"}
{"prompt": "9418", "answer": "9419"}
{"prompt": "37302,37303,37304,37305,37306,37307,37308,37309,37310", "answer": "37311"}
{"prompt": "35252,35253", "answer": "35254"}
{"prompt": "38828,38829,38830,38831,38832", "answer": "38833"}
{"prompt": "14930,14931,14932,14933,14934,14935,14936", "answer": "14937"}
{"prompt": "36050,36051,36052,36053", "answer": "36054"}
{"prompt": "23950,23951,23952,23953", "answer": "23954"}
{"prompt": "10317,10318", "answer": "10319"}
{"prompt": "24165,24166,24167,24168,24169,24170", "answer": "24171"}
{"prompt": "1177,1178,1179,1180", "answer": "1181"}
{"prompt": "10249,10250,10251,10252", "answer": "10253"}
{"prompt": "22572,22573,22574,22575,22576,22577,22578,22579", "answer": "22580"}
{"prompt": "447,448,449,450,451,452,453,454,455,456", "answer": "457"}
{"prompt": "18673,18674,18675", "answer": "18676"}
{"prompt": "9445,9446,9447,9448,9449", "answer": "9450"}
{"prompt": "13866,13867,13868,13869,13870,13871,13872,13873,13874", "answer": "13875"}
{"prompt": "3461,3462,3463,3464,3465,3466", "answer": "3467"}
{"prompt": "37692,37693,37694", "answer": "37695"}
{"prompt": "11632,11633", "answer": "11634"}
{"prompt": "21768,21769,21770,21771,21772,21773,21774,21775,21776", "answer": "21777"}
{"prompt": "28888,28889,28890,28891,28892,28893,28894,28895", "answer": "28896"}
{"prompt": "39535,39536,39537,39538,39539", "answer": "39540"}
{"prompt": "19464,19465", "answer": "19466"}
{"prompt": "13549,13550,13551", "answer": "13552"}
{"prompt": "16448", "answer": "16449"}
{"prompt": "43648,43649,43650,43651", "answer": "43652"}
{"prompt": "44011,44012,44013,44014,44015,44016", "answer": "44017"}
{"prompt": "27916,27917,27918", "answer": "27919"}
{"prompt": "6625,6626,6627,6628,6629,6630,6631,6632,6633", "answer": "6634"}
{"prompt": "14081,14082,14083,14084,14085", "answer": "14086"}
{"prompt": "14393,14394,14395,14396,14397,14398", "answer": "14399"}
{"prompt": "7098,7099,7100,7101", "answer": "7102"}
{"prompt": "20787,20788,20789,20790,20791,20792", "answer": "20793"}
{"prompt": "22982,22983", "answer": "22984"}
{"prompt": "7948,7949,7950,7951", "answer": "7952"}
{"prompt": "33437,33438,33439,33440,33441,33442,33443,33444,33445", "answer": "33446"}
{"prompt": "27167,27168,27169,27170,27171,27172,27173,27174,27175,27176", "answer": "27177"}
{"prompt": "12953,12954,12955,12956,12957,12958,12959,12960,12961,12962", "answer": "12963"}
{"prompt": "24994", "answer": "24995"}
{"prompt": "17273,17274", "answer": "17275"}
{"prompt": "13745,13746,13747", "answer": "13748"}
{"prompt": "886,887,888,889,890,891,892,893,894", "answer": "895"}
{"prompt": "6583,6584,6585,6586,6587,6588,6589,6590", "answer": "6591"}
{"prompt": "13049,13050,13051,13052", "answer": "13053"}
{"prompt": "44502,44503", "answer": "44504"}
{"prompt": "16188,16189,16190,16191,16192,16193,16194,16195,16196", "answer": "16197"}
{"prompt": "20716,20717,20718", "answer": "20719"}
{"prompt": "4441,4442,4443,4444,4445,4446,4447,4448", "answer": "4449"}
{"prompt": "25554,25555,25556", "answer": "25557"}
{"prompt": "32769,32770,32771,32772,32773,32774,32775,32776,32777", "answer": "32778"}
{"prompt": "25904,25905,25906,25907,25908,25909,25910,25911,25912,25913", "answer": "25914"}
{"prompt": "40833,40834,40835,40836,40837", "answer": "40838"}
{"prompt": "34718,34719,34720,34721,34722,34723,34724", "answer": "34725"}
{"prompt": "31879,31880,31881", "answer": "31882"}
{"prompt": "39526,39527,39528,39529,39530,39531", "answer": "39532"}
{"prompt": "5302,5303,5304,5305,5306,5307,5308", "answer": "5309"}
{"prompt": "31674,31675,31676,31677,31678,31679,31680,31681,31682,31683", "answer": "31684"}
{"prompt": "45178,45179", "answer": "45180"}
{"prompt": "23625,23626,23627,23628,23629,23630,23631,23632,23633,23634", "answer": "23635"}
{"prompt": "6151,6152,6153,6154,6155,6156", "answer": "6157"}
{"prompt": "7951,7952,7953", "answer": "7954"}
{"prompt": "44248,44249,44250,44251,44252,44253,44254,44255", "answer": "44256"}
{"prompt": "34376,34377", "answer": "34378"}
{"prompt": "19650,19651,19652,19653,19654,19655,19656", "answer": "19657"}
{"prompt": "44776,44777,44778,44779,44780,44781,44782,44783,44784", "answer": "44785"}
{"prompt": "19312,19313,19314", "answer": "19315"}
{"prompt": "11678,11679,11680,11681", "answer": "11682"}
{"prompt": "37322", "answer": "37323"}
{"prompt": "17615,17616,17617,17618,17619", "answer": "17620"}
{"prompt": "35166,35167,35168,35169,35170,35171,35172", "answer": "35173"}
{"prompt": "14526,14527,14528,14529,14530,14531", "answer": "14532"}
{"prompt": "33821,33822,33823", "answer": "33824"}
{"prompt": "14734,14735,14736,14737,14738,14739,14740,14741,14742,14743", "answer": "14744"}
{"prompt": "20799,20800,20801,20802,20803,20804,20805,20806,20807,20808", "answer": "20809"}
{"prompt": "8936,8937,8938,8939", "answer": "8940"}
{"prompt": "4332,4333,4334,4335,4336,4337,4338,4339", "answer": "4340"}
{"prompt": "35744,35745,35746,35747,35748", "answer": "35749"}
{"prompt": "18598,18599,18600", "answer": "18601"}
{"prompt": "11318,11319,11320,11321,11322", "answer": "11323"}
{"prompt": "30957", "answer": "30958"}
{"prompt": "35019", "answer": "35020"}
{"prompt": "24842,24843,24844,24845", "answer": "24846"}
{"prompt": "15866,15867,15868,15869,15870,15871", "answer": "15872"}
{"prompt": "16357,16358,16359,16360,16361,16362,16363,16364,16365,16366", "answer": "16367"}
{"prompt": "18976", "answer": "18977"}
{"prompt": "5101,5102,5103,5104,5105", "answer": "5106"}
{"prompt": "33833,33834,33835,33836,33837,33838,33839,33840,33841", "answer": "33842"}
{"prompt": "2839,2840", "answer": "2841"}
{"prompt": "12121,12122,12123,12124,12125,12126,12127", "answer": "12128"}
{"prompt": "1,2,3,4,5", "answer": "6"}
{"prompt": "17673,17674,17675,17676,17677,17678,17679,17680", "answer": "17681"}
{"prompt": "6099,6100,6101,6102,6103,6104", "answer": "6105"}
{"prompt": "5322,5323,5324,5325,5326,5327,5328", "answer": "5329"}
{"prompt": "5443", "answer": "5444"}
{"prompt": "22913,22914,22915,22916,22917,22918", "answer": "22919"}
{"prompt": "40450,40451,40452,40453,40454,40455,40456,40457,40458,40459", "answer": "40460"}
{"prompt": "44128", "answer": "44129"}
{"prompt": "30605,30606,30607,30608,30609,30610,30611,30612,30613", "answer": "30614"}
{"prompt": "73,74,75,76,77,78,79,80,81", "answer": "82"}
{"prompt": "37624", "answer": "37625"}
{"prompt": "7786,7787,7788", "answer": "7789"}
{"prompt": "17574,17575,17576", "answer": "17577"}
{"prompt": "42276,42277,42278,42279,42280,42281,42282", "answer": "42283"}
{"prompt": "22944,22945,22946", "answer": "22947"}
{"prompt": "41691,41692", "answer": "41693"}
{"prompt": "10395,10396,10397,10398", "answer": "10399"}
{"prompt": "22494,22495,22496,22497,22498,22499,22500,22501,22502", "answer": "22503"}
{"prompt": "22000,22001,22002,22003,22004,22005,22006,22007,22008,22009", "answer": "22010"}
{"prompt": "21355,21356", "answer": "21357"}
{"prompt": "28963,28964,28965", "answer": "28966"}
{"prompt": "14417,14418,14419,14420,14421,14422,14423,14424,14425,14426", "answer": "14427"}
{"prompt": "37538,37539,37540", "answer": "37541"}
{"prompt": "39016,39017,39018,39019,39020,39021,39022,39023,39024", "answer": "39025"}
{"prompt": "21816,21817,21818", "answer": "21819"}
{"prompt": "19315,19316,19317,19318,19319,19320,19321", "answer": "19322"}
{"prompt": "4711,4712,4713,4714,4715,4716,4717,4718,4719", "answer": "4720"}
{"prompt": "3772,3773,3774,3775,3776", "answer": "3777"}
{"prompt": "44006,44007,44008,44009,44010,44011", "answer": "44012"}
{"prompt": "42736,42737,42738,42739,42740", "answer": "42741"}
{"prompt": "44806,44807,44808", "answer": "44809"}
{"prompt": "10490,10491,10492,10493,10494,10495,10496,10497", "answer": "10498"}
{"prompt": "33026,33027,33028,33029,33030,33031", "answer": "33032"}
{"prompt": "27252,27253,27254", "answer": "27255"}
{"prompt": "3803,3804", "answer": "3805"}
{"prompt": "5647,5648,5649,5650", "answer": "5651"}
{"prompt": "22018,22019,22020,22021,22022", "answer": "22023"}
{"prompt": "29182,29183,29184,29185,29186,29187,29188,29189,29190,29191", "answer": "29192"}
{"prompt": "37435,37436,37437,37438,37439,37440,37441,37442,37443,37444", "answer": "37445"}
{"prompt": "37031,37032,37033,37034,37035,37036,37037,37038,37039,37040", "answer": "37041"}
{"prompt": "23944,23945,23946,23947,23948,23949,23950", "answer": "23951"}
{"prompt": "20054,20055,20056,20057,20058,20059,20060,20061,20062,20063", "answer": "20064"}
{"prompt": "37906,37907", "answer": "37908"}
{"prompt": "9475,9476,9477,9478,9479,9480,9481", "answer": "9482"}
{"prompt": "15115,15116,15117,15118,15119", "answer": "15120"}
{"prompt": "44926,44927,44928,44929,44930", "answer": "44931"}
{"prompt": "23268,23269,23270,23271,23272,23273,23274,23275,23276", "answer": "23277"}
{"prompt": "13793,13794,13795", "answer": "13796"}
{"prompt": "11455,11456,11457,11458,11459,11460", "answer": "11461"}
{"prompt": "27203,27204,27205,27206,27207,27208,27209", "answer": "27210"}
{"prompt": "21692,21693,21694,21695", "answer": "21696"}
{"prompt": "15897,15898", "answer": "15899"}
{"prompt": "10639,10640,10641,10642,10643,10644,10645,10646", "answer": "10647"}
{"prompt": "41547,41548", "answer": "41549"}
{"prompt": "7156,7157,7158,7159", "answer": "7160"}
{"prompt": "488,489", "answer": "490"}
{"prompt": "38358,38359,38360,38361,38362,38363,38364,38365,38366,38367", "answer": "38368"}
{"prompt": "12904,12905,12906,12907,12908,12909,12910", "answer": "12911"}
{"prompt": "8392,8393,8394,8395,8396,8397,8398,8399", "answer": "8400"}
{"prompt": "20766,20767,20768,20769,20770,20771", "answer": "20772"}
{"prompt": "30324,30325", "answer": "30326"}
{"prompt": "13129,13130,13131,13132,13133,13134,13135", "answer": "13136"}
{"prompt": "2393,2394,2395,2396,2397,2398,2399,2400,2401,2402", "answer": "2403"}
{"prompt": "5763,5764", "answer": "5765"}
{"prompt": "22097,22098,22099,22100", "answer": "22101"}
{"prompt": "17386,17387,17388,17389,17390,17391,17392,17393,17394,17395", "answer": "17396"}
{"prompt": "23289,23290,23291,23292,23293,23294", "answer": "23295"}
{"prompt": "2187,2188,2189", "answer": "2190"}
{"prompt": "3480,3481,3482,3483", "answer": "3484"}
{"prompt": "42047,42048,42049,42050,42051,42052,42053,42054,42055,42056", "answer": "42057"}
{"prompt": "17024,17025,17026", "answer": "17027"}
{"prompt": "19930,19931", "answer": "19932"}
{"prompt": "3457,3458", "answer": "3459"}
{"prompt": "25862,25863", "answer": "25864"}
{"prompt": "7414,7415,7416", "answer": "7417"}
{"prompt": "6959,6960,6961,6962,6963,6964,6965,6966", "answer": "6967"}
{"prompt": "26165,26166,26167,26168", "answer": "26169"}
{"prompt": "40751,40752,40753", "answer": "40754"}
{"prompt": "29293,29294,29295,29296,29297,29298,29299,29300,29301", "answer": "29302"}
{"prompt": "2416,2417,2418,2419,2420,2421,2422,2423,2424", "answer": "2425"}
{"prompt": "17450,17451,17452,17453,17454,17455,17456", "answer": "17457"}
{"prompt": "37840,37841,37842,37843,37844,37845,37846,37847,37848", "answer": "37849"}
{"prompt": "39327,39328,39329,39330,39331,39332,39333,39334,39335", "answer": "39336"}
{"prompt": "36295,36296,36297,36298,36299,36300,36301", "answer": "36302"}
{"prompt": "11928,11929,11930,11931,11932", "answer": "11933"}
{"prompt": "38020,38021,38022,38023,38024", "answer": "38025"}
{"prompt": "17594,17595,17596,17597,17598,17599,17600,17601,17602,17603", "answer": "17604"}
{"prompt": "26692,26693,26694", "answer": "26695"}
{"prompt": "19396,19397,19398,19399,19400,19401,19402,19403", "answer": "19404"}
{"prompt": "6089,6090", "answer": "6091"}
{"prompt": "5027,5028,5029,5030,5031,5032,5033", "answer": "5034"}
{"prompt": "26862,26863", "answer": "26864"}
{"prompt": "27880,27881,27882,27883,27884,27885,27886", "answer": "27887"}
{"prompt": "12353,12354,12355,12356,12357,12358,12359,12360,12361,12362", "answer": "12363"}
{"prompt": "31273,31274,31275,31276,31277,31278,31279", "answer": "31280"}
{"prompt": "42111,42112,42113", "answer": "42114"}
{"prompt": "17514,17515,17516,17517,17518", "answer": "17519"}
{"prompt": "9343,9344,9345,9346,9347,9348,9349,9350,9351", "answer": "9352"}
{"prompt": "22486", "answer": "22487"}
{"prompt": "43295,43296", "answer": "43297"}
{"prompt": "13964,13965,13966,13967,13968,13969,13970,13971", "answer": "13972"}
{"prompt": "26674,26675,26676,26677,26678,26679,26680,26681", "answer": "26682"}
{"prompt": "39452", "answer": "39453"}
{"prompt": "7626,7627,7628,7629,7630,7631,7632", "answer": "7633"}
{"prompt": "25531,25532,25533,25534,25535,25536,25537,25538,25539", "answer": "25540"}
{"prompt": "19359,19360", "answer": "19361"}
{"prompt": "30041", "answer": "30042"}
{"prompt": "5262,5263,5264,5265,5266", "answer": "5267"}
{"prompt": "38917,38918,38919,38920,38921,38922,38923,38924,38925", "answer": "38926"}
{"prompt": "24285,24286,24287,24288,24289", "answer": "24290"}
{"prompt": "20952,20953,20954,20955,20956,20957", "answer": "20958"}
{"prompt": "13984,13985,13986,13987,13988,13989,13990,13991", "answer": "13992"}
{"prompt": "22918,22919,22920,22921,22922,22923,22924,22925,22926", "answer": "22927"}
{"prompt": "12089", "answer": "12090"}
{"prompt": "19327,19328,19329,19330,19331,19332,19333,19334", "answer": "19335"}
{"prompt": "10177,10178", "answer": "10179"}
{"prompt": "25211,25212,25213,25214,25215,25216", "answer": "25217"}
{"prompt": "26855,26856,26857,26858,26859,26860,26861,26862", "answer": "26863"}
{"prompt": "11039,11040,11041,11042,11043,11044,11045", "answer": "11046"}
{"prompt": "16196,16197,16198,16199,16200,16201,16202,16203", "answer": "16204"}
{"prompt": "44537,44538,44539,44540,44541,44542,44543", "answer": "44544"}
{"prompt": "41688,41689,41690,41691", "answer": "41692"}
{"prompt": "304,305,306,307", "answer": "308"}
{"prompt": "14970,14971,14972,14973,14974,14975", "answer": "14976"}
{"prompt": "30675,30676,30677,30678,30679,30680", "answer": "30681"}
{"prompt": "43448,43449,43450,43451", "answer": "43452"}
{"prompt": "27951,27952", "answer": "27953"}
{"prompt": "5194,5195,5196,5197,5198,5199,5200,5201,5202,5203", "answer": "5204"}
{"prompt": "18083", "answer": "18084"}
{"prompt": "19405,19406,19407,19408,19409,19410,19411,19412,19413,19414", "answer": "19415"}
{"prompt": "23350,23351,23352,23353,23354,23355,23356,23357", "answer": "23358"}
{"prompt": "44906,44907,44908,44909,44910,44911,44912,44913,44914,44915", "answer": "44916"}
{"prompt": "18399,18400,18401,18402,18403,18404", "answer": "18405"}
{"prompt": "37615", "answer": "37616"}
{"prompt": "1388,1389", "answer": "1390"}
{"prompt": "4193,4194,4195,4196,4197,4198,4199", "answer": "4200"}
{"prompt": "34623,34624,34625,34626,34627,34628,34629", "answer": "34630"}
{"prompt": "42185,42186,42187,42188,42189", "answer": "42190"}
{"prompt": "6156,6157,6158,6159,6160,6161,6162", "answer": "6163"}
{"prompt": "4491,4492,4493,4494,4495,4496,4497", "answer": "4498"}
{"prompt": "27924", "answer": "27925"}
{"prompt": "19249,19250,19251,19252,19253,19254", "answer": "19255"}
{"prompt": "34597,34598,34599,34600,34601,34602,34603,34604,34605,34606", "answer": "34607"}
{"prompt": "30001,30002,30003", "answer": "30004"}
{"prompt": "45212,45213,45214", "answer": "45215"}
{"prompt": "41029,41030", "answer": "41031"}
{"prompt": "41588,41589,41590,41591", "answer": "41592"}
{"prompt": "42841,42842,42843,42844,42845,42846,42847,42848,42849", "answer": "42850"}
{"prompt": "26077,26078,26079,26080,26081,26082", "answer": "26083"}
{"prompt": "15881,15882,15883,15884,15885", "answer": "15886"}
{"prompt": "38015,38016,38017,38018,38019,38020", "answer": "38021"}
{"prompt": "31755,31756,31757,31758", "answer": "31759"}
{"prompt": "35535,35536,35537,35538,35539", "answer": "35540"}
{"prompt": "27609", "answer": "27610"}
{"prompt": "43844,43845,43846", "answer": "43847"}
{"prompt": "19079,19080,19081,19082,19083,19084,19085,19086,19087,19088", "answer": "19089"}
{"prompt": "17927,17928,17929,17930,17931", "answer": "17932"}
{"prompt": "26448", "answer": "26449"}
{"prompt": "17113,17114,17115,17116,17117,17118,17119", "answer": "17120"}
{"prompt": "12067", "answer": "12068"}
{"prompt": "43141,43142,43143,43144,43145,43146,43147,43148,43149,43150", "answer": "43151"}
{"prompt": "32243,32244,32245,32246,32247", "answer": "32248"}
{"prompt": "32162,32163", "answer": "32164"}
{"prompt": "18578,18579,18580,18581,18582,18583,18584,18585,18586", "answer": "18587"}
{"prompt": "20260,20261,20262", "answer": "20263"}
{"prompt": "18133,18134,18135,18136,18137,18138,18139", "answer": "18140"}
{"prompt": "20898,20899,20900,20901,20902", "answer": "20903"}
{"prompt": "29989,29990,29991,29992", "answer": "29993"}
{"prompt": "7781,7782,7783,7784,7785,7786", "answer": "7787"}
{"prompt": "43543,43544,43545,43546,43547,43548", "answer": "43549"}
{"prompt": "10048,10049,10050,10051,10052,10053,10054,10055", "answer": "10056"}
{"prompt": "176,177,178,179,180,181,182,183,184", "answer": "185"}
{"prompt": "40991", "answer": "40992"}
{"prompt": "22239,22240,22241", "answer": "22242"}
{"prompt": "33880,33881,33882,33883,33884,33885,33886,33887", "answer": "33888"}
{"prompt": "25675,25676,25677,25678,25679,25680,25681,25682,25683,25684", "answer": "25685"}
{"prompt": "12053,12054,12055,12056,12057,12058,12059,12060", "answer": "12061"}
{"prompt": "1280,1281,1282,1283,1284,1285,1286,1287,1288,1289", "answer": "1290"}
{"prompt": "5594", "answer": "5595"}
{"prompt": "12631,12632,12633", "answer": "12634"}
{"prompt": "29868", "answer": "29869"}
{"prompt": "39867,39868,39869", "answer": "39870"}
{"prompt": "37853,37854,37855,37856,37857,37858,37859,37860", "answer": "37861"}
{"prompt": "9376,9377", "answer": "9378"}
{"prompt": "18322,18323,18324,18325,18326,18327,18328,18329", "answer": "18330"}
{"prompt": "28661,28662,28663,28664,28665,28666,28667,28668,28669", "answer": "28670"}
{"prompt": "2081,2082,2083,2084,2085,2086,2087,2088,2089,2090", "answer": "2091"}
{"prompt": "8632,8633,8634,8635,8636", "answer": "8637"}
{"prompt": "39840,39841", "answer": "39842"}
{"prompt": "21032,21033", "answer": "21034"}
{"prompt": "40150,40151", "answer": "40152"}
{"prompt": "19360,19361,19362", "answer": "19363"}
{"prompt": "17576,17577,17578,17579,17580,17581,17582,17583,17584,17585", "answer": "17586"}
{"prompt": "22969,22970", "answer": "22971"}
{"prompt": "15114,15115", "answer": "15116"}
{"prompt": "5246,5247,5248,5249,5250,5251,5252,5253,5254", "answer": "5255"}
{"prompt": "3043,3044,3045,3046,3047,3048", "answer": "3049"}
{"prompt": "32831,32832,32833,32834,32835", "answer": "32836"}
{"prompt": "44129,44130,44131,44132", "answer": "44133"}
{"prompt": "18186,18187,18188,18189,18190,18191,18192", "answer": "18193"}
{"prompt": "7738", "answer": "7739"}
{"prompt": "43974", "answer": "43975"}
{"prompt": "20832,20833,20834,20835,20836,20837", "answer": "20838"}
{"prompt": "3520,3521,3522,3523,3524", "answer": "3525"}
{"prompt": "45299,45300", "answer": "45301"}
{"prompt": "23491,23492,23493,23494,23495,23496", "answer": "23497"}
{"prompt": "5332,5333,5334,5335,5336,5337,5338,5339,5340", "answer": "5341"}
{"prompt": "12440,12441,12442,12443,12444,12445,12446", "answer": "12447"}
{"prompt": "11636,11637,11638,11639,11640,11641,11642,11643,11644,11645", "answer": "11646"}
{"prompt": "23981,23982,23983,23984,23985,23986,23987,23988,23989", "answer": "23990"}
{"prompt": "4004,4005,4006,4007,4008,4009,4010,4011", "answer": "4012"}
{"prompt": "35111,35112,35113,35114,35115,35116,35117,35118", "answer": "35119"}
{"prompt": "17718,17719,17720,17721,17722,17723,17724", "answer": "17725"}
{"prompt": "44085,44086,44087,44088,44089,44090", "answer": "44091"}
{"prompt": "44823", "answer": "44824"}
{"prompt": "8613,8614,8615,8616,8617,8618,8619,8620", "answer": "8621"}
{"prompt": "37727,37728,37729,37730,37731,37732", "answer": "37733"}
{"prompt": "14899,14900,14901,14902,14903,14904,14905,14906,14907", "answer": "14908"}
{"prompt": "879,880", "answer": "881"}
{"prompt": "21432,21433,21434,21435", "answer": "21436"}
{"prompt": "34335,34336,34337,34338,34339,34340,34341,34342,34343", "answer": "34344"}
{"prompt": "42916,42917,42918,42919", "answer": "42920"}
{"prompt": "3974,3975,3976,3977,3978", "answer": "3979"}
{"prompt": "32447,32448,32449,32450,32451,32452,32453,32454,32455,32456", "answer": "32457"}
{"prompt": "36267,36268,36269,36270,36271,36272,36273", "answer": "36274"}
{"prompt": "28493,28494,28495,28496", "answer": "28497"}
{"prompt": "14014,14015,14016,14017", "answer": "14018"}
{"prompt": "14752,14753,14754,14755,14756,14757", "answer": "14758"}
{"prompt": "39460,39461,39462,39463,39464", "answer": "39465"}
{"prompt": "18462,18463,18464,18465", "answer": "18466"}
{"prompt": "38615,38616,38617,38618,38619,38620,38621,38622,38623,38624", "answer": "38625"}
{"prompt": "14389,14390,14391,14392,14393", "answer": "14394"}
{"prompt": "38354,38355,38356,38357,38358", "answer": "38359"}
{"prompt": "18806,18807,18808,18809,18810,18811,18812,18813,18814,18815", "answer": "18816"}
{"prompt": "19753", "answer": "19754"}
{"prompt": "26213,26214,26215,26216,26217,26218,26219,26220", "answer": "26221"}
{"prompt": "10646,10647,10648,10649,10650", "answer": "10651"}
{"prompt": "17943,17944,17945,17946,17947,17948,17949,17950,17951", "answer": "17952"}
{"prompt": "31002,31003,31004,31005,31006,31007,31008", "answer": "31009"}
{"prompt": "20837,20838,20839,20840,20841,20842,20843,20844", "answer": "20845"}
{"prompt": "15218", "answer": "15219"}
{"prompt": "8236,8237,8238,8239,8240,8241,8242", "answer": "8243"}
{"prompt": "3430,3431,3432,3433,3434,3435", "answer": "3436"}
{"prompt": "15999,16000", "answer": "16001"}
{"prompt": "10923,10924,10925,10926", "answer": "10927"}
{"prompt": "35019,35020", "answer": "35021"}
{"prompt": "17480,17481", "answer": "17482"}
{"prompt": "21375,21376,21377,21378,21379,21380,21381,21382", "answer": "21383"}
{"prompt": "24470,24471,24472,24473,24474,24475", "answer": "24476"}
{"prompt": "9892,9893,9894", "answer": "9895"}
{"prompt": "3650,3651,3652,3653,3654,3655,3656,3657,3658,3659", "answer": "3660"}
{"prompt": "42994,42995,42996,42997", "answer": "42998"}
{"prompt": "17027,17028,17029,17030,17031,17032", "answer": "17033"}
{"prompt": "10297,10298,10299,10300", "answer": "10301"}
{"prompt": "41273,41274", "answer": "41275"}
{"prompt": "837,838", "answer": "839"}
{"prompt": "27757,27758,27759,27760,27761,27762,27763,27764,27765", "answer": "27766"}
{"prompt": "18997,18998,18999,19000,19001,19002,19003,19004,19005", "answer": "19006"}
{"prompt": "15857,15858", "answer": "15859"}
{"prompt": "34854,34855", "answer": "34856"}
{"prompt": "29290,29291,29292,29293", "answer": "29294"}
{"prompt": "34231,34232,34233,34234", "answer": "34235"}
{"prompt": "22530", "answer": "22531"}
{"prompt": "7231,7232,7233,7234,7235,7236,7237,7238,7239,7240", "answer": "7241"}
{"prompt": "35402,35403,35404,35405,35406,35407,35408,35409,35410,35411", "answer": "35412"}
{"prompt": "29618,29619,29620,29621,29622,29623", "answer": "29624"}
{"prompt": "33222,33223,33224,33225,33226", "answer": "33227"}
{"prompt": "27445", "answer": "27446"}
{"prompt": "3524,3525", "answer": "3526"}
{"prompt": "5628", "answer": "5629"}
{"prompt": "30177,30178,30179,30180,30181,30182,30183,30184", "answer": "30185"}
{"prompt": "20089,20090,20091", "answer": "20092"}
{"prompt": "27722,27723,27724,27725,27726,27727,27728,27729", "answer": "27730"}
{"prompt": "508,509", "answer": "510"}
{"prompt": "713,714", "answer": "715"}
{"prompt": "15513,15514", "answer": "15515"}
{"prompt": "34829,34830", "answer": "34831"}
{"prompt": "28485", "answer": "28486"}
{"prompt": "39428,39429", "answer": "39430"}
{"prompt": "26936,26937", "answer": "26938"}
{"prompt": "18742", "answer": "18743"}
{"prompt": "2690,2691,2692,2693,2694,2695,2696,2697", "answer": "2698"}
{"prompt": "33185,33186,33187,33188,33189,33190", "answer": "33191"}
{"prompt": "3076,3077,3078,3079,3080,3081,3082", "answer": "3083"}
{"prompt": "45013,45014,45015,45016", "answer": "45017"}
{"prompt": "39464,39465,39466,39467,39468,39469,39470,39471,39472,39473", "answer": "39474"}
{"prompt": "4859,4860,4861,4862,4863,4864", "answer": "4865"}
{"prompt": "15021,15022,15023,15024,15025,15026,15027,15028,15029,15030", "answer": "15031"}
{"prompt": "24456,24457,24458", "answer": "24459"}
{"prompt": "14217", "answer": "14218"}
{"prompt": "39027,39028,39029,39030,39031", "answer": "39032"}
{"prompt": "4589,4590,4591,4592,4593,4594,4595,4596,4597", "answer": "4598"}
{"prompt": "34728,34729,34730,34731,34732,34733,34734,34735", "answer": "34736"}
{"prompt": "10223,10224,10225,10226,10227,10228", "answer": "10229"}
{"prompt": "42189,42190", "answer": "42191"}
{"prompt": "36120", "answer": "36121"}
{"prompt": "25630,25631,25632,25633,25634,25635,25636,25637", "answer": "25638"}
{"prompt": "28861,28862,28863,28864", "answer": "28865"}
{"prompt": "23543,23544,23545,23546", "answer": "23547"}
{"prompt": "42597,42598,42599", "answer": "42600"}
{"prompt": "34559,34560,34561,34562,34563", "answer": "34564"}
{"prompt": "11281", "answer": "11282"}
{"prompt": "32272,32273", "answer": "32274"}
{"prompt": "5783,5784,5785,5786,5787,5788,5789,5790,5791", "answer": "5792"}
{"prompt": "42724,42725,42726", "answer": "42727"}
{"prompt": "44142,44143,44144,44145,44146,44147,44148,44149,44150,44151", "answer": "44152"}
{"prompt": "29556,29557,29558,29559,29560,29561,29562,29563,29564", "answer": "29565"}
{"prompt": "14920", "answer": "14921"}
{"prompt": "18639,18640", "answer": "18641"}
{"prompt": "3776,3777,3778,3779,3780,3781,3782,3783,3784,3785", "answer": "3786"}
{"prompt": "36206,36207,36208,36209,36210,36211,36212,36213,36214", "answer": "36215"}
{"prompt": "39497,39498,39499,39500,39501,39502,39503,39504,39505,39506", "answer": "39507"}
{"prompt": "704,705,706,707,708,709,710,711,712,713", "answer": "714"}
{"prompt": "1261,1262,1263,1264,1265,1266,1267", "answer": "1268"}
{"prompt": "37159,37160,37161", "answer": "37162"}
{"prompt": "36431,36432,36433,36434,36435,36436,36437,36438,36439", "answer": "36440"}
{"prompt": "27357,27358,27359,27360", "answer": "27361"}
{"prompt": "30099,30100,30101", "answer": "30102"}
{"prompt": "8012,8013,8014,8015,8016,8017,8018,8019,8020", "answer": "8021"}
{"prompt": "15449,15450", "answer": "15451"}
{"prompt": "12412,12413,12414,12415,12416,12417", "answer": "12418"}
{"prompt": "14070,14071", "answer": "14072"}
{"prompt": "5979,5980,5981,5982,5983,5984,5985,5986,5987,5988", "answer": "5989"}
{"prompt": "29957,29958,29959,29960,29961,29962,29963", "answer": "29964"}
{"prompt": "10881,10882,10883,10884,10885,10886,10887,10888,10889,10890", "answer": "10891"}
{"prompt": "38424,38425,38426,38427,38428", "answer": "38429"}
{"prompt": "26780,26781,26782,26783,26784,26785,26786,26787,26788", "answer": "26789"}
{"prompt": "14823,14824,14825", "answer": "14826"}
{"prompt": "19865,19866,19867,19868,19869,19870,19871,19872", "answer": "19873"}
{"prompt": "5791,5792,5793,5794,5795,5796,5797,5798,5799,5800", "answer": "5801"}
{"prompt": "39347,39348,39349,39350", "answer": "39351"}
{"prompt": "19853,19854,19855,19856,19857,19858,19859,19860", "answer": "19861"}
{"prompt": "13597,13598,13599,13600,13601,13602,13603", "answer": "13604"}
{"prompt": "7826,7827", "answer": "7828"}
{"prompt": "19213,19214,19215,19216,19217", "answer": "19218"}
{"prompt": "1732,1733,1734", "answer": "1735"}
{"prompt": "24442,24443,24444,24445", "answer": "24446"}
{"prompt": "2259,2260,2261,2262,2263,2264,2265", "answer": "2266"}
{"prompt": "33300,33301,33302,33303,33304,33305,33306,33307", "answer": "33308"}
{"prompt": "38512,38513,38514,38515,38516,38517,38518,38519,38520", "answer": "38521"}
{"prompt": "45085,45086,45087,45088,45089", "answer": "45090"}
{"prompt": "13237,13238,13239,13240,13241,13242", "answer": "13243"}
{"prompt": "37354,37355,37356,37357,37358,37359,37360,37361", "answer": "37362"}
{"prompt": "35381", "answer": "35382"}
{"prompt": "42031,42032,42033,42034", "answer": "42035"}
{"prompt": "3303,3304,3305,3306,3307,3308,3309", "answer": "3310"}
{"prompt": "14275,14276,14277,14278,14279,14280,14281,14282,14283,14284", "answer": "14285"}
{"prompt": "30003,30004,30005,30006", "answer": "30007"}
{"prompt": "735,736,737,738,739,740,741,742", "answer": "743"}
{"prompt": "31551,31552", "answer": "31553"}
{"prompt": "701,702,703,704", "answer": "705"}
{"prompt": "39794,39795,39796,39797,39798,39799,39800,39801", "answer": "39802"}
{"prompt": "22502,22503", "answer": "22504"}
{"prompt": "4817,4818", "answer": "4819"}
{"prompt": "34110,34111", "answer": "34112"}
{"prompt": "22726,22727,22728,22729,22730,22731,22732,22733,22734,22735", "answer": "22736"}
{"prompt": "30661,30662,30663", "answer": "30664"}
{"prompt": "4053,4054,4055,4056", "answer": "4057"}
{"prompt": "23303,23304,23305,23306,23307", "answer": "23308"}
{"prompt": "29097,29098", "answer": "29099"}
{"prompt": "7687,7688,7689", "answer": "7690"}
{"prompt": "19874,19875,19876,19877", "answer": "19878"}
{"prompt": "43799,43800,43801,43802,43803,43804,43805,43806,43807", "answer": "43808"}
{"prompt": "21241", "answer": "21242"}
{"prompt": "8209,8210,8211,8212", "answer": "8213"}
{"prompt": "15340,15341,15342,15343,15344,15345,15346,15347,15348,15349", "answer": "15350"}
{"prompt": "16640,16641,16642", "answer": "16643"}
{"prompt": "11567,11568,11569,11570,11571", "answer": "11572"}
{"prompt": "1610,1611,1612,1613,1614,1615,1616,1617,1618", "answer": "1619"}
{"prompt": "39069,39070,39071", "answer": "39072"}
{"prompt": "12715,12716,12717,12718,12719,12720,12721", "answer": "12722"}
{"prompt": "30548,30549,30550,30551,30552", "answer": "30553"}
{"prompt": "34798,34799,34800", "answer": "34801"}
{"prompt": "18032,18033,18034,18035,18036", "answer": "18037"}
{"prompt": "43859,43860,43861,43862,43863,43864,43865", "answer": "43866"}
{"prompt": "1905,1906,1907,1908,1909,1910,1911", "answer": "1912"}
{"prompt": "9721,9722,9723,9724,9725,9726,9727", "answer": "9728"}
{"prompt": "14940,14941,14942,14943,14944,14945,14946,14947", "answer": "14948"}
{"prompt": "39888,39889,39890,39891,39892", "answer": "39893"}
{"prompt": "36197,36198,36199,36200,36201,36202,36203,36204,36205,36206", "answer": "36207"}
{"prompt": "30266,30267,30268", "answer": "30269"}
{"prompt": "14681,14682,14683,14684,14685,14686,14687", "answer": "14688"}
{"prompt": "15384", "answer": "15385"}
{"prompt": "43195,43196,43197,43198", "answer": "43199"}
{"prompt": "25154,25155,25156,25157,25158,25159", "answer": "25160"}
{"prompt": "9778,9779,9780,9781,9782,9783,9784,9785", "answer": "9786"}
{"prompt": "12113,12114,12115,12116,12117,12118,12119,12120,12121", "answer": "12122"}
{"prompt": "37816,37817,37818,37819,37820,37821,37822,37823,37824,37825", "answer": "37826"}
{"prompt": "42599,42600", "answer": "42601"}
{"prompt": "32456", "answer": "32457"}
{"prompt": "15305,15306", "answer": "15307"}
{"prompt": "39116,39117,39118", "answer": "39119"}
{"prompt": "38520,38521", "answer": "38522"}
{"prompt": "18830,18831,18832,18833,18834,18835,18836,18837", "answer": "18838"}
{"prompt": "10041,10042,10043,10044,10045,10046", "answer": "10047"}
{"prompt": "10915,10916,10917,10918,10919,10920,10921,10922", "answer": "10923"}
{"prompt": "1019,1020,1021,1022,1023,1024,1025,1026,1027", "answer": "1028"}
{"prompt": "42124,42125,42126,42127", "answer": "42128"}
{"prompt": "25603,25604", "answer": "25605"}
{"prompt": "15405,15406,15407", "answer": "15408"}
{"prompt": "22337,22338,22339", "answer": "22340"}
{"prompt": "18155,18156,18157,18158", "answer": "18159"}
{"prompt": "30068,30069,30070,30071,30072,30073,30074,30075", "answer": "30076"}
{"prompt": "42913,42914,42915,42916", "answer": "42917"}
{"prompt": "28903", "answer": "28904"}
{"prompt": "4768,4769", "answer": "4770"}
{"prompt": "26290,26291", "answer": "26292"}
{"prompt": "14923,14924,14925,14926,14927,14928,14929,14930", "answer": "14931"}
{"prompt": "31584,31585,31586,31587,31588", "answer": "31589"}
{"prompt": "13024,13025,13026,13027,13028", "answer": "13029"}
{"prompt": "4189,4190,4191,4192,4193", "answer": "4194"}
{"prompt": "24668,24669,24670,24671,24672,24673,24674,24675", "answer": "24676"}
{"prompt": "33395,33396,33397,33398,33399,33400,33401,33402,33403,33404", "answer": "33405"}
{"prompt": "17232", "answer": "17233"}
{"prompt": "6539", "answer": "6540"}
{"prompt": "4268,4269,4270,4271,4272,4273,4274,4275,4276", "answer": "4277"}
{"prompt": "35376,35377,35378,35379,35380,35381", "answer": "35382"}
{"prompt": "42256,42257", "answer": "42258"}
{"prompt": "9202,9203,9204", "answer": "9205"}
{"prompt": "12195,12196,12197,12198,12199,12200,12201,12202", "answer": "12203"}
{"prompt": "16624,16625,16626,16627,16628,16629", "answer": "16630"}
{"prompt": "15668,15669,15670,15671,15672,15673,15674,15675", "answer": "15676"}
{"prompt": "10748,10749,10750,10751,10752,10753,10754,10755", "answer": "10756"}
{"prompt": "41756,41757,41758,41759,41760,41761,41762,41763,41764,41765", "answer": "41766"}
{"prompt": "40896,40897,40898,40899,40900,40901,40902,40903", "answer": "40904"}
{"prompt": "4140,4141,4142,4143,4144,4145,4146,4147", "answer": "4148"}
{"prompt": "8138,8139,8140,8141,8142,8143,8144,8145", "answer": "8146"}
{"prompt": "34874,34875,34876,34877,34878,34879,34880,34881,34882,34883", "answer": "34884"}
{"prompt": "11077,11078,11079", "answer": "11080"}
{"prompt": "37918,37919,37920", "answer": "37921"}
{"prompt": "38525,38526,38527,38528,38529,38530,38531", "answer": "38532"}
{"prompt": "13409,13410,13411,13412,13413", "answer": "13414"}
{"prompt": "22216,22217,22218", "answer": "22219"}
{"prompt": "14700,14701,14702,14703,14704", "answer": "14705"}
{"prompt": "23496,23497,23498,23499", "answer": "23500"}
{"prompt": "29769,29770,29771,29772,29773,29774,29775,29776", "answer": "29777"}
{"prompt": "18202", "answer": "18203"}
{"prompt": "40926,40927,40928,40929,40930,40931,40932", "answer": "40933"}
{"prompt": "24936,24937,24938,24939", "answer": "24940"}
{"prompt": "10965,10966,10967", "answer": "10968"}
{"prompt": "8605,8606,8607,8608,8609", "answer": "8610"}
{"prompt": "11245", "answer": "11246"}
{"prompt": "6659,6660,6661,6662,6663,6664", "answer": "6665"}
{"prompt": "24514,24515,24516,24517,24518,24519,24520,24521", "answer": "24522"}
{"prompt": "19639,19640,19641,19642", "answer": "19643"}
{"prompt": "42406,42407,42408,42409,42410,42411,42412,42413,42414", "answer": "42415"}
{"prompt": "13071,13072,13073,13074,13075,13076,13077,13078,13079", "answer": "13080"}
{"prompt": "32649,32650,32651,32652,32653", "answer": "32654"}
{"prompt": "33428,33429,33430,33431,33432,33433,33434,33435", "answer": "33436"}
{"prompt": "21659,21660,21661,21662,21663,21664,21665,21666,21667,21668", "answer": "21669"}
{"prompt": "23530,23531,23532,23533", "answer": "23534"}
{"prompt": "43267,43268,43269,43270,43271,43272,43273", "answer": "43274"}
{"prompt": "22856,22857,22858,22859,22860", "answer": "22861"}
{"prompt": "9835,9836,9837,9838,9839,9840,9841,9842,9843,9844", "answer": "9845"}
{"prompt": "30914,30915", "answer": "30916"}
{"prompt": "15619,15620,15621,15622,15623,15624,15625,15626,15627", "answer": "15628"}
{"prompt": "1376,1377,1378,1379,1380,1381,1382,1383", "answer": "1384"}
{"prompt": "6590,6591,6592,6593,6594,6595,6596", "answer": "6597"}
{"prompt": "26489,26490,26491", "answer": "26492"}
{"prompt": "7767,7768,7769,7770,7771,7772", "answer": "7773"}
{"prompt": "41659", "answer": "41660"}
{"prompt": "20705,20706,20707,20708,20709,20710,20711,20712,20713", "answer": "20714"}
{"prompt": "37212,37213,37214,37215,37216", "answer": "37217"}
{"prompt": "2431,2432,2433", "answer": "2434"}
{"prompt": "16139,16140,16141", "answer": "16142"}
{"prompt": "106,107,108,109,110", "answer": "111"}
{"prompt": "38888,38889", "answer": "38890"}
{"prompt": "27957,27958,27959,27960,27961,27962,27963,27964,27965,27966", "answer": "27967"}
{"prompt": "44866,44867,44868,44869,44870,44871,44872", "answer": "44873"}
{"prompt": "35826,35827,35828,35829,35830,35831,35832", "answer": "35833"}
{"prompt": "3246,3247,3248,3249", "answer": "3250"}
{"prompt": "23677,23678,23679", "answer": "23680"}
{"prompt": "7391,7392,7393", "answer": "7394"}
{"prompt": "4880,4881,4882,4883,4884,4885,4886,4887,4888", "answer": "4889"}
{"prompt": "33597,33598,33599,33600,33601,33602", "answer": "33603"}
{"prompt": "18456,18457,18458,18459,18460,18461", "answer": "18462"}
{"prompt": "27363", "answer": "27364"}
{"prompt": "6937,6938,6939,6940,6941,6942", "answer": "6943"}
{"prompt": "30476,30477,30478,30479,30480,30481,30482,30483,30484,30485", "answer": "30486"}
{"prompt": "17991,17992,17993,17994,17995,17996,17997,17998", "answer": "17999"}
{"prompt": "35138,35139,35140,35141,35142,35143", "answer": "35144"}
{"prompt": "17443", "answer": "17444"}
{"prompt": "36871,36872,36873,36874", "answer": "36875"}
{"prompt": "37566,37567,37568,37569,37570,37571,37572,37573,37574,37575", "answer": "37576"}
{"prompt": "25101,25102,25103,25104,25105,25106,25107,25108,25109", "answer": "25110"}
{"prompt": "42394,42395,42396,42397,42398,42399,42400,42401,42402,42403", "answer": "42404"}
{"prompt": "34385", "answer": "34386"}
{"prompt": "21776,21777,21778,21779,21780,21781,21782,21783,21784", "answer": "21785"}
{"prompt": "5097,5098,5099,5100,5101", "answer": "5102"}
{"prompt": "9144,9145,9146,9147,9148", "answer": "9149"}
{"prompt": "260,261,262,263,264,265", "answer": "266"}
{"prompt": "40081,40082,40083,40084,40085,40086,40087", "answer": "40088"}
{"prompt": "23659,23660,23661,23662,23663,23664,23665", "answer": "23666"}
{"prompt": "33966,33967,33968,33969,33970,33971,33972,33973", "answer": "33974"}
{"prompt": "23341,23342,23343,23344,23345,23346,23347,23348,23349,23350", "answer": "23351"}
{"prompt": "24690,24691,24692,24693,24694,24695,24696,24697", "answer": "24698"}
{"prompt": "36681,36682,36683", "answer": "36684"}
{"prompt": "7065,7066,7067,7068,7069,7070,7071,7072,7073,7074", "answer": "7075"}
{"prompt": "11923,11924,11925,11926,11927,11928", "answer": "11929"}
{"prompt": "43826,43827,43828,43829,43830", "answer": "43831"}
{"prompt": "29692,29693", "answer": "29694"}
{"prompt": "26303", "answer": "26304"}
{"prompt": "3676,3677", "answer": "3678"}
{"prompt": "38119,38120,38121,38122", "answer": "38123"}
{"prompt": "1364,1365,1366,1367,1368,1369,1370", "answer": "1371"}
{"prompt": "31927,31928", "answer": "31929"}
{"prompt": "25624,25625,25626,25627,25628,25629,25630", "answer": "25631"}
{"prompt": "26363", "answer": "26364"}
{"prompt": "38169,38170,38171,38172,38173,38174,38175,38176", "answer": "38177"}
{"prompt": "29016", "answer": "29017"}
{"prompt": "25055,25056,25057,25058", "answer": "25059"}
{"prompt": "19018,19019,19020,19021", "answer": "19022"}
{"prompt": "44770,44771,44772,44773,44774,44775,44776", "answer": "44777"}
{"prompt": "23517,23518,23519,23520,23521,23522,23523,23524", "answer": "23525"}
{"prompt": "16842", "answer": "16843"}
{"prompt": "10349,10350,10351,10352,10353,10354,10355", "answer": "10356"}
{"prompt": "12570,12571,12572,12573", "answer": "12574"}
{"prompt": "34995,34996,34997,34998,34999", "answer": "35000"}
{"prompt": "5771,5772,5773,5774,5775,5776,5777,5778", "answer": "5779"}
{"prompt": "12256", "answer": "12257"}
{"prompt": "2708,2709,2710,2711,2712,2713,2714", "answer": "2715"}
{"prompt": "27121,27122,27123,27124,27125,27126,27127", "answer": "27128"}
{"prompt": "40753,40754,40755,40756,40757,40758,40759,40760,40761", "answer": "40762"}
{"prompt": "44261,44262,44263,44264,44265,44266,44267,44268,44269", "answer": "44270"}
{"prompt": "39306,39307,39308,39309,39310,39311,39312,39313,39314", "answer": "39315"}
{"prompt": "2864,2865,2866,2867", "answer": "2868"}
{"prompt": "45179,45180", "answer": "45181"}
{"prompt": "13279,13280", "answer": "13281"}
{"prompt": "4304,4305,4306,4307", "answer": "4308"}
{"prompt": "24952,24953,24954,24955,24956,24957", "answer": "24958"}
{"prompt": "27286,27287,27288", "answer": "27289"}
{"prompt": "41462,41463,41464,41465,41466,41467,41468,41469,41470,41471", "answer": "41472"}
{"prompt": "5088,5089,5090,5091,5092,5093,5094,5095,5096,5097", "answer": "5098"}
{"prompt": "3171,3172,3173,3174", "answer": "3175"}
{"prompt": "34830,34831", "answer": "34832"}
{"prompt": "18320,18321,18322", "answer": "18323"}
{"prompt": "35506,35507,35508,35509,35510,35511,35512", "answer": "35513"}
{"prompt": "43643,43644,43645,43646,43647", "answer": "43648"}
{"prompt": "4424,4425,4426,4427,4428,4429,4430,4431", "answer": "4432"}
{"prompt": "26345,26346,26347,26348,26349,26350", "answer": "26351"}
{"prompt": "43234,43235", "answer": "43236"}
{"prompt": "4028,4029,4030,4031,4032,4033,4034", "answer": "4035"}
{"prompt": "39593,39594,39595,39596,39597,39598", "answer": "39599"}
{"prompt": "42141", "answer": "42142"}
{"prompt": "4697,4698,4699,4700,4701,4702", "answer": "4703"}
{"prompt": "33325,33326,33327,33328,33329", "answer": "33330"}
{"prompt": "16549,16550,16551,16552,16553,16554,16555,16556,16557,16558", "answer": "16559"}
{"prompt": "27294,27295,27296", "answer": "27297"}
{"prompt": "32273,32274,32275,32276,32277,32278,32279,32280", "answer": "32281"}
{"prompt": "32806,32807,32808,32809,32810,32811,32812,32813,32814,32815", "answer": "32816"}
{"prompt": "10551,10552,10553,10554,10555,10556,10557,10558,10559,10560", "answer": "10561"}
{"prompt": "7562,7563,7564,7565,7566,7567,7568,7569", "answer": "7570"}
{"prompt": "13891,13892,13893,13894,13895,13896", "answer": "13897"}
{"prompt": "908,909,910,911", "answer": "912"}
{"prompt": "30785,30786,30787,30788,30789,30790", "answer": "30791"}
{"prompt": "42287,42288,42289,42290,42291,42292", "answer": "42293"}
{"prompt": "227,228,229,230", "answer": "231"}
{"prompt": "7260,7261,7262,7263,7264,7265,7266", "answer": "7267"}
{"prompt": "39386", "answer": "39387"}
{"prompt": "19931,19932,19933,19934,19935", "answer": "19936"}
{"prompt": "37965", "answer": "37966"}
{"prompt": "1415,1416", "answer": "1417"}
{"prompt": "22237,22238,22239", "answer": "22240"}
{"prompt": "33017,33018,33019", "answer": "33020"}
{"prompt": "6259,6260,6261,6262,6263,6264,6265,6266,6267", "answer": "6268"}
{"prompt": "28159,28160,28161", "answer": "28162"}
{"prompt": "31395,31396,31397,31398,31399", "answer": "31400"}
{"prompt": "20496,20497,20498,20499", "answer": "20500"}
{"prompt": "43902,43903,43904,43905,43906,43907,43908,43909", "answer": "43910"}
{"prompt": "36218,36219,36220,36221,36222,36223,36224,36225", "answer": "36226"}
{"prompt": "5233,5234,5235,5236,5237,5238,5239,5240,5241", "answer": "5242"}
{"prompt": "10435", "answer": "10436"}
{"prompt": "24901,24902,24903,24904,24905,24906", "answer": "24907"}
{"prompt": "8596,8597,8598,8599,8600,8601,8602,8603,8604", "answer": "8605"}
{"prompt": "3901,3902,3903,3904", "answer": "3905"}
{"prompt": "28120,28121,28122", "answer": "28123"}
{"prompt": "40055,40056,40057", "answer": "40058"}
{"prompt": "9664,9665,9666,9667,9668,9669,9670,9671,9672", "answer": "9673"}
{"prompt": "10810,10811,10812,10813", "answer": "10814"}
{"prompt": "6293", "answer": "6294"}
{"prompt": "8300,8301,8302,8303,8304,8305,8306", "answer": "8307"}
{"prompt": "34398", "answer": "34399"}
{"prompt": "18062,18063,18064,18065", "answer": "18066"}
{"prompt": "36928,36929,36930,36931,36932,36933,36934", "answer": "36935"}
{"prompt": "10778,10779,10780,10781,10782,10783,10784", "answer": "10785"}
{"prompt": "4380,4381", "answer": "4382"}
{"prompt": "37865,37866,37867,37868,37869,37870,37871,37872", "answer": "37873"}
{"prompt": "10668,10669,10670,10671,10672,10673,10674,10675,10676,10677", "answer": "10678"}
{"prompt": "13013,13014,13015,13016,13017,13018", "answer": "13019"}
{"prompt": "3642,3643,3644,3645,3646,3647,3648,3649", "answer": "3650"}
{"prompt": "11792,11793,11794,11795,11796,11797,11798,11799", "answer": "11800"}
{"prompt": "22935,22936,22937", "answer": "22938"}
{"prompt": "21336,21337,21338,21339", "answer": "21340"}
{"prompt": "10422,10423,10424,10425,10426,10427,10428,10429", "answer": "10430"}
{"prompt": "19231,19232,19233,19234,19235", "answer": "19236"}
{"prompt": "43865,43866,43867", "answer": "43868"}
{"prompt": "40013,40014,40015,40016,40017,40018,40019,40020,40021,40022", "answer": "40023"}
{"prompt": "27259,27260,27261,27262,27263,27264,27265", "answer": "27266"}
{"prompt": "44210,44211,44212", "answer": "44213"}
{"prompt": "30485", "answer": "30486"}
{"prompt": "32462,32463,32464,32465,32466,32467,32468,32469", "answer": "32470"}
{"prompt": "5321,5322", "answer": "5323"}
{"prompt": "40172,40173,40174,40175,40176,40177,40178,40179,40180", "answer": "40181"}
{"prompt": "33019,33020,33021,33022,33023,33024,33025,33026", "answer": "33027"}
{"prompt": "11962,11963,11964", "answer": "11965"}
{"prompt": "36171,36172,36173,36174,36175,36176,36177,36178,36179,36180", "answer": "36181"}
{"prompt": "12101,12102,12103,12104,12105,12106,12107,12108,12109", "answer": "12110"}
{"prompt": "40239,40240,40241,40242", "answer": "40243"}
{"prompt": "15913", "answer": "15914"}
{"prompt": "32141,32142,32143,32144", "answer": "32145"}
{"prompt": "39292,39293,39294,39295,39296,39297,39298", "answer": "39299"}
{"prompt": "19434,19435,19436", "answer": "19437"}
{"prompt": "41962,41963,41964,41965,41966,41967", "answer": "41968"}
{"prompt": "41622,41623,41624,41625,41626,41627,41628,41629", "answer": "41630"}
{"prompt": "1696,1697", "answer": "1698"}
{"prompt": "12768,12769,12770,12771,12772,12773,12774", "answer": "12775"}
{"prompt": "18322", "answer": "18323"}
{"prompt": "36276,36277,36278", "answer": "36279"}
{"prompt": "44784,44785,44786,44787,44788,44789,44790,44791,44792,44793", "answer": "44794"}
{"prompt": "35669,35670,35671,35672,35673,35674,35675,35676,35677", "answer": "35678"}
{"prompt": "28879,28880,28881,28882,28883,28884", "answer": "28885"}
{"prompt": "10458,10459,10460,10461,10462,10463", "answer": "10464"}
{"prompt": "21839,21840,21841,21842,21843,21844,21845,21846,21847,21848", "answer": "21849"}
{"prompt": "45219,45220,45221", "answer": "45222"}
{"prompt": "18892,18893,18894,18895", "answer": "18896"}
{"prompt": "6557", "answer": "6558"}
{"prompt": "33608,33609,33610", "answer": "33611"}
{"prompt": "44935,44936,44937,44938,44939,44940,44941,44942,44943", "answer": "44944"}
{"prompt": "33139,33140,33141,33142,33143", "answer": "33144"}
{"prompt": "16842", "answer": "16843"}
{"prompt": "24263,24264", "answer": "24265"}
{"prompt": "25122,25123,25124,25125,25126,25127,25128,25129", "answer": "25130"}
{"prompt": "13912", "answer": "13913"}
{"prompt": "36609,36610,36611,36612", "answer": "36613"}
{"prompt": "22062,22063,22064,22065,22066,22067,22068,22069", "answer": "22070"}
{"prompt": "249,250,251,252,253", "answer": "254"}
{"prompt": "5638,5639,5640,5641,5642,5643,5644,5645,5646,5647", "answer": "5648"}
{"prompt": "3037,3038,3039,3040,3041,3042,3043", "answer": "3044"}
{"prompt": "18906,18907,18908,18909", "answer": "18910"}
{"prompt": "30685,30686,30687", "answer": "30688"}
{"prompt": "21894,21895,21896,21897", "answer": "21898"}
{"prompt": "32575,32576,32577,32578,32579,32580,32581,32582,32583,32584", "answer": "32585"}
{"prompt": "26992,26993,26994,26995,26996,26997,26998", "answer": "26999"}
{"prompt": "36244,36245,36246,36247,36248,36249", "answer": "36250"}
{"prompt": "40093,40094,40095,40096", "answer": "40097"}
{"prompt": "41162,41163,41164", "answer": "41165"}
{"prompt": "26119,26120,26121,26122,26123,26124,26125,26126,26127,26128", "answer": "26129"}
{"prompt": "17732", "answer": "17733"}
{"prompt": "43476,43477,43478,43479", "answer": "43480"}
{"prompt": "39620,39621", "answer": "39622"}
{"prompt": "16203,16204", "answer": "16205"}
{"prompt": "31204", "answer": "31205"}
{"prompt": "27648,27649,27650,27651,27652,27653,27654,27655,27656", "answer": "27657"}
{"prompt": "16716,16717,16718,16719,16720,16721,16722,16723,16724,16725", "answer": "16726"}
{"prompt": "23524,23525,23526,23527", "answer": "23528"}
{"prompt": "15296,15297,15298,15299,15300,15301,15302,15303,15304,15305", "answer": "15306"}
{"prompt": "31835,31836,31837,31838,31839,31840,31841,31842,31843", "answer": "31844"}
{"prompt": "13330,13331,13332,13333", "answer": "13334"}
{"prompt": "27561,27562,27563,27564,27565,27566,27567,27568,27569,27570", "answer": "27571"}
{"prompt": "2684,2685,2686,2687,2688,2689,2690", "answer": "2691"}
{"prompt": "1597,1598,1599,1600,1601", "answer": "1602"}
{"prompt": "26937,26938,26939", "answer": "26940"}
{"prompt": "3946,3947,3948,3949,3950,3951,3952,3953,3954,3955", "answer": "3956"}
{"prompt": "22970,22971,22972,22973,22974", "answer": "22975"}
{"prompt": "33052,33053,33054,33055", "answer": "33056"}
{"prompt": "21964,21965,21966,21967,21968,21969,21970,21971,21972", "answer": "21973"}
{"prompt": "12605,12606", "answer": "12607"}
{"prompt": "30883,30884,30885,30886", "answer": "30887"}
{"prompt": "12607", "answer": "12608"}
{"prompt": "4392,4393", "answer": "4394"}
{"prompt": "36045,36046,36047", "answer": "36048"}
{"prompt": "26576,26577,26578,26579,26580,26581", "answer": "26582"}
{"prompt": "34262,34263,34264,34265,34266,34267,34268,34269,34270", "answer": "34271"}
{"prompt": "41135,41136,41137,41138,41139,41140,41141,41142,41143,41144", "answer": "41145"}
{"prompt": "25997,25998,25999,26000,26001,26002,26003", "answer": "26004"}
{"prompt": "15076,15077,15078,15079,15080,15081,15082", "answer": "15083"}
{"prompt": "4737,4738,4739,4740,4741,4742,4743,4744", "answer": "4745"}
{"prompt": "13288,13289,13290,13291,13292,13293,13294,13295,13296", "answer": "13297"}
{"prompt": "15763,15764,15765", "answer": "15766"}
{"prompt": "40138,40139,40140,40141,40142", "answer": "40143"}
{"prompt": "19604,19605,19606", "answer": "19607"}
{"prompt": "19094,19095", "answer": "19096"}
{"prompt": "4907,4908,4909", "answer": "4910"}
{"prompt": "2650,2651,2652,2653,2654,2655,2656,2657,2658", "answer": "2659"}
{"prompt": "38675,38676,38677", "answer": "38678"}
{"prompt": "25703,25704,25705,25706,25707,25708", "answer": "25709"}
{"prompt": "860,861,862,863", "answer": "864"}
{"prompt": "40333,40334,40335,40336,40337,40338", "answer": "40339"}
{"prompt": "36226,36227,36228,36229", "answer": "36230"}
{"prompt": "35316,35317,35318", "answer": "35319"}
{"prompt": "4703,4704,4705,4706,4707,4708,4709,4710", "answer": "4711"}
{"prompt": "3695,3696,3697,3698,3699,3700,3701,3702,3703,3704", "answer": "3705"}
{"prompt": "27736,27737", "answer": "27738"}
{"prompt": "17438,17439,17440,17441", "answer": "17442"}
{"prompt": "26559,26560,26561,26562", "answer": "26563"}
{"prompt": "20588,20589,20590,20591,20592,20593,20594", "answer": "20595"}
{"prompt": "34053,34054,34055,34056,34057,34058", "answer": "34059"}
{"prompt": "9851,9852,9853,9854,9855", "answer": "9856"}
{"prompt": "15637", "answer": "15638"}
{"prompt": "4464,4465,4466,4467", "answer": "4468"}
{"prompt": "6179,6180,6181,6182,6183,6184", "answer": "6185"}
{"prompt": "36632,36633,36634", "answer": "36635"}
{"prompt": "16861,16862,16863", "answer": "16864"}
{"prompt": "6651,6652,6653,6654,6655,6656,6657,6658", "answer": "6659"}
{"prompt": "43886,43887,43888", "answer": "43889"}
{"prompt": "28872,28873,28874,28875,28876", "answer": "28877"}
{"prompt": "23575,23576,23577,23578,23579,23580,23581,23582,23583,23584", "answer": "23585"}
{"prompt": "18355", "answer": "18356"}
{"prompt": "35013,35014,35015,35016", "answer": "35017"}
{"prompt": "5510,5511,5512", "answer": "5513"}
{"prompt": "42141,42142,42143,42144", "answer": "42145"}
{"prompt": "15712,15713,15714,15715,15716,15717,15718,15719,15720,15721", "answer": "15722"}
{"prompt": "15283,15284,15285,15286,15287,15288,15289,15290,15291", "answer": "15292"}
{"prompt": "2949,2950", "answer": "2951"}
{"prompt": "33774", "answer": "33775"}
{"prompt": "11769,11770,11771,11772,11773,11774,11775,11776,11777", "answer": "11778"}
{"prompt": "12782,12783,12784,12785,12786", "answer": "12787"}
{"prompt": "10740,10741,10742,10743", "answer": "10744"}
{"prompt": "29750,29751", "answer": "29752"}
{"prompt": "35555,35556,35557,35558,35559,35560", "answer": "35561"}
{"prompt": "22522,22523,22524,22525,22526,22527,22528,22529,22530", "answer": "22531"}
{"prompt": "5140,5141,5142,5143,5144", "answer": "5145"}
{"prompt": "24878,24879,24880,24881,24882", "answer": "24883"}
{"prompt": "21703,21704,21705,21706,21707", "answer": "21708"}
{"prompt": "25133,25134,25135,25136", "answer": "25137"}
{"prompt": "15261,15262,15263", "answer": "15264"}
{"prompt": "39966,39967,39968,39969,39970,39971,39972,39973,39974,39975", "answer": "39976"}
{"prompt": "9105", "answer": "9106"}
{"prompt": "19924,19925,19926,19927,19928,19929,19930", "answer": "19931"}
{"prompt": "4663,4664,4665,4666,4667,4668,4669", "answer": "4670"}
{"prompt": "30946,30947,30948,30949,30950", "answer": "30951"}
{"prompt": "30967,30968,30969,30970,30971,30972,30973,30974,30975,30976", "answer": "30977"}
{"prompt": "21134", "answer": "21135"}
{"prompt": "8529,8530", "answer": "8531"}
{"prompt": "15643,15644,15645,15646,15647", "answer": "15648"}
{"prompt": "29354,29355,29356,29357", "answer": "29358"}
{"prompt": "16696,16697,16698", "answer": "16699"}
{"prompt": "37501,37502", "answer": "37503"}
{"prompt": "22504,22505,22506,22507,22508,22509,22510,22511", "answer": "22512"}
{"prompt": "17973,17974,17975,17976,17977,17978,17979,17980,17981,17982", "answer": "17983"}
{"prompt": "24397", "answer": "24398"}
{"prompt": "44128,44129", "answer": "44130"}
{"prompt": "2784,2785,2786,2787,2788", "answer": "2789"}
{"prompt": "18774,18775,18776,18777", "answer": "18778"}
{"prompt": "20823,20824,20825,20826,20827,20828,20829,20830,20831", "answer": "20832"}
{"prompt": "13210,13211,13212,13213,13214,13215", "answer": "13216"}
{"prompt": "2881,2882,2883,2884", "answer": "2885"}
{"prompt": "13582,13583,13584,13585,13586,13587,13588,13589,13590,13591", "answer": "13592"}
{"prompt": "15349,15350,15351", "answer": "15352"}
{"prompt": "34890,34891,34892,34893", "answer": "34894"}
{"prompt": "16558,16559,16560,16561", "answer": "16562"}
{"prompt": "8944,8945,8946,8947,8948,8949,8950,8951,8952", "answer": "8953"}
{"prompt": "25812,25813,25814,25815,25816,25817,25818,25819,25820", "answer": "25821"}
{"prompt": "4259,4260,4261,4262,4263,4264,4265", "answer": "4266"}
{"prompt": "27924,27925,27926,27927,27928,27929,27930", "answer": "27931"}
{"prompt": "11807,11808,11809,11810,11811,11812", "answer": "11813"}
{"prompt": "16931,16932,16933,16934,16935", "answer": "16936"}
{"prompt": "8572,8573", "answer": "8574"}
{"prompt": "13591,13592,13593,13594,13595,13596,13597", "answer": "13598"}
{"prompt": "36314,36315,36316,36317,36318,36319,36320,36321", "answer": "36322"}
{"prompt": "29877,29878,29879,29880,29881,29882,29883,29884,29885", "answer": "29886"}
{"prompt": "9030,9031,9032", "answer": "9033"}
{"prompt": "12310,12311,12312,12313,12314,12315,12316,12317", "answer": "12318"}
{"prompt": "44183,44184,44185,44186,44187,44188,44189,44190,44191,44192", "answer": "44193"}
{"prompt": "11005,11006,11007,11008,11009,11010,11011,11012", "answer": "11013"}
{"prompt": "21339,21340,21341,21342,21343,21344,21345,21346,21347,21348", "answer": "21349"}
{"prompt": "43437,43438,43439,43440,43441,43442,43443,43444", "answer": "43445"}
{"prompt": "7252,7253,7254,7255,7256,7257,7258,7259,7260", "answer": "7261"}
{"prompt": "10104,10105,10106,10107", "answer": "10108"}
{"prompt": "11890,11891,11892,11893,11894,11895,11896", "answer": "11897"}
{"prompt": "16402,16403,16404,16405,16406,16407,16408", "answer": "16409"}
{"prompt": "19265,19266", "answer": "19267"}
{"prompt": "19403,19404,19405", "answer": "19406"}
{"prompt": "32777,32778,32779,32780", "answer": "32781"}
{"prompt": "17526,17527,17528,17529,17530,17531,17532,17533", "answer": "17534"}
{"prompt": "22590,22591,22592,22593,22594,22595,22596,22597,22598,22599", "answer": "22600"}
{"prompt": "37661,37662,37663,37664", "answer": "37665"}
{"prompt": "29843,29844,29845,29846,29847", "answer": "29848"}
{"prompt": "19540,19541,19542,19543", "answer": "19544"}
{"prompt": "32707,32708,32709,32710,32711,32712,32713,32714,32715", "answer": "32716"}
{"prompt": "4486,4487", "answer": "4488"}
{"prompt": "36480,36481,36482", "answer": "36483"}
{"prompt": "42872,42873,42874,42875,42876,42877,42878", "answer": "42879"}
{"prompt": "15616,15617,15618,15619", "answer": "15620"}
{"prompt": "27369,27370,27371,27372,27373,27374,27375,27376", "answer": "27377"}
{"prompt": "42096", "answer": "42097"}
{"prompt": "32547,32548,32549,32550,32551", "answer": "32552"}
{"prompt": "21313,21314,21315,21316", "answer": "21317"}
{"prompt": "33380,33381,33382,33383,33384", "answer": "33385"}
{"prompt": "20999,21000,21001,21002", "answer": "21003"}
{"prompt": "8336,8337,8338,8339,8340,8341", "answer": "8342"}
{"prompt": "2819,2820,2821,2822,2823,2824,2825", "answer": "2826"}
{"prompt": "33336,33337,33338,33339,33340,33341,33342,33343", "answer": "33344"}
{"prompt": "41800,41801,41802,41803,41804,41805,41806,41807,41808", "answer": "41809"}
{"prompt": "35064,35065,35066,35067,35068,35069,35070,35071,35072,35073", "answer": "35074"}
{"prompt": "14332,14333,14334,14335,14336,14337,14338,14339", "answer": "14340"}
{"prompt": "32194,32195,32196,32197", "answer": "32198"}
{"prompt": "27074,27075", "answer": "27076"}
{"prompt": "43041", "answer": "43042"}
{"prompt": "1143,1144,1145,1146,1147", "answer": "1148"}
{"prompt": "21628,21629,21630,21631,21632", "answer": "21633"}
{"prompt": "31067,31068,31069,31070,31071", "answer": "31072"}
{"prompt": "37540", "answer": "37541"}
{"prompt": "7989,7990,7991,7992,7993,7994,7995", "answer": "7996"}
{"prompt": "12877,12878", "answer": "12879"}
{"prompt": "26609,26610,26611,26612,26613,26614", "answer": "26615"}
{"prompt": "21577,21578,21579,21580,21581,21582,21583,21584", "answer": "21585"}
{"prompt": "29228,29229,29230,29231,29232,29233,29234", "answer": "29235"}
{"prompt": "18873,18874,18875", "answer": "18876"}
{"prompt": "27699,27700,27701,27702,27703", "answer": "27704"}
{"prompt": "39083,39084,39085,39086,39087,39088,39089", "answer": "39090"}
{"prompt": "26708,26709,26710", "answer": "26711"}
{"prompt": "35866,35867,35868,35869,35870,35871,35872,35873,35874", "answer": "35875"}
{"prompt": "11730,11731,11732,11733,11734,11735,11736", "answer": "11737"}
{"prompt": "44289,44290,44291,44292", "answer": "44293"}
{"prompt": "7861,7862,7863,7864,7865,7866,7867", "answer": "7868"}
{"prompt": "22666", "answer": "22667"}
{"prompt": "43426,43427,43428,43429", "answer": "43430"}
{"prompt": "897,898,899,900,901", "answer": "902"}
{"prompt": "40209,40210,40211,40212,40213,40214,40215,40216", "answer": "40217"}
{"prompt": "37982,37983,37984,37985,37986,37987,37988", "answer": "37989"}
{"prompt": "40254,40255,40256,40257,40258,40259,40260,40261", "answer": "40262"}
{"prompt": "1586,1587,1588,1589,1590", "answer": "1591"}
{"prompt": "13847,13848,13849", "answer": "13850"}
{"prompt": "5915,5916,5917,5918,5919,5920,5921,5922,5923,5924", "answer": "5925"}
{"prompt": "1089,1090,1091,1092,1093,1094,1095", "answer": "1096"}
{"prompt": "33352,33353,33354,33355,33356,33357", "answer": "33358"}
{"prompt": "11038,11039", "answer": "11040"}
{"prompt": "17456,17457,17458,17459", "answer": "17460"}
{"prompt": "37353,37354", "answer": "37355"}
{"prompt": "24360,24361,24362,24363", "answer": "24364"}
{"prompt": "15268,15269,15270,15271,15272,15273", "answer": "15274"}
{"prompt": "12556,12557", "answer": "12558"}
{"prompt": "13517,13518,13519,13520,13521,13522,13523,13524,13525", "answer": "13526"}
{"prompt": "29420,29421", "answer": "29422"}
{"prompt": "22585,22586,22587,22588,22589,22590", "answer": "22591"}
{"prompt": "43817,43818,43819", "answer": "43820"}
{"prompt": "876,877,878,879", "answer": "880"}
{"prompt": "5316,5317,5318,5319,5320,5321", "answer": "5322"}
{"prompt": "10607,10608,10609", "answer": "10610"}
{"prompt": "15900,15901,15902,15903,15904", "answer": "15905"}
{"prompt": "23955,23956,23957", "answer": "23958"}
{"prompt": "40388,40389,40390,40391,40392,40393,40394,40395,40396,40397", "answer": "40398"}
{"prompt": "38842,38843,38844,38845,38846,38847,38848,38849,38850", "answer": "38851"}
{"prompt": "36707,36708,36709,36710", "answer": "36711"}
{"prompt": "30798", "answer": "30799"}
{"prompt": "39158", "answer": "39159"}
{"prompt": "13971,13972,13973,13974,13975,13976,13977", "answer": "13978"}
{"prompt": "34436", "answer": "34437"}
{"prompt": "12214,12215,12216,12217", "answer": "12218"}
{"prompt": "7604,7605,7606,7607,7608,7609,7610", "answer": "7611"}
{"prompt": "8792,8793", "answer": "8794"}
{"prompt": "32364,32365,32366,32367,32368,32369,32370,32371", "answer": "32372"}
{"prompt": "18966", "answer": "18967"}
{"prompt": "4171,4172,4173,4174,4175,4176", "answer": "4177"}
{"prompt": "32702,32703,32704,32705,32706,32707", "answer": "32708"}
{"prompt": "18819,18820,18821", "answer": "18822"}
{"prompt": "2825,2826,2827,2828,2829", "answer": "2830"}
{"prompt": "41734,41735,41736,41737,41738", "answer": "41739"}
{"prompt": "39550,39551,39552,39553,39554,39555,39556", "answer": "39557"}
{"prompt": "44027,44028,44029,44030,44031,44032,44033,44034,44035,44036", "answer": "44037"}
{"prompt": "22317,22318,22319", "answer": "22320"}
{"prompt": "1590", "answer": "1591"}
{"prompt": "26806", "answer": "26807"}
{"prompt": "20032", "answer": "20033"}
{"prompt": "39036,39037,39038,39039,39040,39041,39042", "answer": "39043"}
{"prompt": "40887", "answer": "40888"}
{"prompt": "31984", "answer": "31985"}
{"prompt": "44484,44485,44486,44487,44488,44489,44490,44491", "answer": "44492"}
{"prompt": "25260,25261,25262", "answer": "25263"}
{"prompt": "570,571,572,573,574,575", "answer": "576"}
{"prompt": "37190,37191", "answer": "37192"}
{"prompt": "40404", "answer": "40405"}
{"prompt": "26681", "answer": "26682"}
{"prompt": "35886,35887,35888,35889,35890,35891,35892,35893,35894,35895", "answer": "35896"}
{"prompt": "8463", "answer": "8464"}
{"prompt": "26757,26758,26759,26760", "answer": "26761"}
{"prompt": "20555,20556,20557,20558,20559", "answer": "20560"}
{"prompt": "1497,1498,1499,1500,1501,1502,1503,1504,1505", "answer": "1506"}
{"prompt": "11908,11909,11910,11911,11912,11913,11914,11915", "answer": "11916"}
{"prompt": "21524,21525,21526,21527,21528,21529", "answer": "21530"}
{"prompt": "16378,16379,16380,16381,16382", "answer": "16383"}
{"prompt": "32064,32065,32066,32067,32068,32069,32070,32071", "answer": "32072"}
{"prompt": "18815,18816,18817,18818,18819", "answer": "18820"}
{"prompt": "25508,25509,25510,25511,25512,25513", "answer": "25514"}
{"prompt": "6823,6824,6825,6826,6827,6828,6829,6830,6831", "answer": "6832"}
{"prompt": "1370,1371,1372", "answer": "1373"}
{"prompt": "24429,24430,24431,24432,24433,24434,24435", "answer": "24436"}
{"prompt": "34748,34749,34750,34751,34752,34753,34754,34755", "answer": "34756"}
{"prompt": "8643,8644,8645,8646", "answer": "8647"}
{"prompt": "1740,1741,1742", "answer": "1743"}
{"prompt": "35126,35127,35128,35129,35130", "answer": "35131"}
{"prompt": "23025,23026,23027,23028,23029,23030,23031,23032,23033,23034", "answer": "23035"}
{"prompt": "32469,32470,32471,32472,32473,32474,32475,32476,32477", "answer": "32478"}
{"prompt": "5447,5448,5449,5450,5451,5452,5453,5454", "answer": "5455"}
{"prompt": "35151,35152,35153,35154,35155,35156,35157,35158,35159", "answer": "35160"}
{"prompt": "23508,23509,23510,23511,23512", "answer": "23513"}
{"prompt": "8445", "answer": "8446"}
{"prompt": "36064,36065,36066,36067,36068,36069,36070,36071", "answer": "36072"}
{"prompt": "38484", "answer": "38485"}
{"prompt": "32390,32391,32392,32393,32394,32395,32396,32397", "answer": "32398"}
{"prompt": "9672,9673,9674,9675,9676,9677,9678,9679", "answer": "9680"}
{"prompt": "10355,10356,10357,10358,10359,10360,10361,10362", "answer": "10363"}
{"prompt": "35083,35084,35085,35086,35087,35088,35089,35090", "answer": "35091"}
{"prompt": "28614", "answer": "28615"}
{"prompt": "43891,43892,43893,43894,43895,43896,43897,43898,43899", "answer": "43900"}
{"prompt": "6651", "answer": "6652"}
{"prompt": "16382,16383,16384,16385,16386,16387,16388,16389,16390", "answer": "16391"}
{"prompt": "2290,2291,2292,2293,2294,2295,2296", "answer": "2297"}
{"prompt": "11777,11778,11779,11780,11781,11782,11783,11784", "answer": "11785"}
{"prompt": "43243,43244,43245", "answer": "43246"}
{"prompt": "22712,22713,22714,22715,22716,22717", "answer": "22718"}
{"prompt": "43532,43533,43534,43535,43536", "answer": "43537"}
{"prompt": "2879,2880,2881", "answer": "2882"}
{"prompt": "38854,38855,38856", "answer": "38857"}
{"prompt": "38067,38068,38069,38070,38071", "answer": "38072"}
{"prompt": "15291,15292", "answer": "15293"}
{"prompt": "8095,8096,8097,8098,8099,8100,8101,8102,8103,8104", "answer": "8105"}
{"prompt": "20657", "answer": "20658"}
{"prompt": "31537,31538,31539", "answer": "31540"}
{"prompt": "23786,23787,23788,23789,23790,23791,23792,23793,23794,23795", "answer": "23796"}
{"prompt": "17840,17841,17842,17843,17844,17845,17846,17847,17848", "answer": "17849"}
{"prompt": "13476,13477,13478,13479,13480", "answer": "13481"}
{"prompt": "1307,1308", "answer": "1309"}
{"prompt": "36147,36148,36149,36150,36151,36152,36153", "answer": "36154"}
{"prompt": "285,286,287,288,289,290,291,292,293,294", "answer": "295"}
{"prompt": "16369,16370,16371", "answer": "16372"}
{"prompt": "607,608,609", "answer": "610"}
{"prompt": "17153,17154", "answer": "17155"}
{"prompt": "44559,44560,44561,44562", "answer": "44563"}
{"prompt": "6614,6615,6616,6617", "answer": "6618"}
{"prompt": "31635,31636,31637,31638,31639,31640,31641,31642,31643,31644", "answer": "31645"}
{"prompt": "9902,9903,9904,9905,9906,9907,9908,9909,9910,9911", "answer": "9912"}
{"prompt": "31236,31237,31238,31239,31240,31241,31242,31243,31244,31245", "answer": "31246"}
{"prompt": "12030,12031,12032,12033,12034,12035", "answer": "12036"}
{"prompt": "24683", "answer": "24684"}
{"prompt": "21100", "answer": "21101"}
{"prompt": "43749,43750,43751,43752,43753,43754,43755", "answer": "43756"}
{"prompt": "4621,4622,4623,4624,4625,4626,4627,4628,4629,4630", "answer": "4631"}
{"prompt": "412,413,414,415,416,417,418,419,420", "answer": "421"}
{"prompt": "22628,22629,22630,22631", "answer": "22632"}
{"prompt": "28828,28829,28830,28831,28832,28833,28834", "answer": "28835"}
{"prompt": "33044", "answer": "33045"}
{"prompt": "44930,44931,44932,44933,44934,44935", "answer": "44936"}
{"prompt": "34371,34372,34373,34374", "answer": "34375"}
{"prompt": "9312,9313,9314,9315,9316,9317", "answer": "9318"}
{"prompt": "24628,24629,24630,24631,24632,24633", "answer": "24634"}
{"prompt": "10081,10082,10083,10084,10085", "answer": "10086"}
{"prompt": "13575,13576,13577,13578,13579,13580,13581,13582", "answer": "13583"}
{"prompt": "10300,10301,10302,10303", "answer": "10304"}
{"prompt": "22937,22938,22939,22940,22941,22942,22943", "answer": "22944"}
{"prompt": "1372,1373,1374,1375,1376", "answer": "1377"}
{"prompt": "14788,14789", "answer": "14790"}
{"prompt": "21190,21191,21192,21193,21194,21195,21196,21197", "answer": "21198"}
{"prompt": "12628,12629,12630", "answer": "12631"}
{"prompt": "11087,11088,11089,11090,11091,11092", "answer": "11093"}
{"prompt": "20137,20138,20139,20140,20141,20142,20143", "answer": "20144"}
{"prompt": "28824", "answer": "28825"}
{"prompt": "33632,33633,33634,33635,33636", "answer": "33637"}
{"prompt": "3102,3103,3104", "answer": "3105"}
{"prompt": "10303", "answer": "10304"}
{"prompt": "25431,25432,25433,25434,25435,25436,25437,25438", "answer": "25439"}
{"prompt": "29897,29898,29899,29900,29901,29902", "answer": "29903"}
{"prompt": "10521,10522", "answer": "10523"}
{"prompt": "39210,39211,39212,39213,39214,39215", "answer": "39216"}
{"prompt": "43693,43694,43695,43696,43697,43698,43699", "answer": "43700"}
{"prompt": "33728,33729,33730", "answer": "33731"}
{"prompt": "27833,27834", "answer": "27835"}
{"prompt": "17327,17328,17329,17330,17331,17332,17333", "answer": "17334"}
{"prompt": "14341,14342,14343,14344,14345,14346,14347,14348,14349,14350", "answer": "14351"}
{"prompt": "6023,6024,6025,6026,6027,6028,6029", "answer": "6030"}
{"prompt": "37738,37739,37740,37741,37742,37743,37744,37745,37746", "answer": "37747"}
{"prompt": "39724,39725,39726,39727,39728,39729,39730,39731", "answer": "39732"}
{"prompt": "28732,28733,28734,28735,28736,28737,28738,28739,28740,28741", "answer": "28742"}
{"prompt": "36722,36723,36724", "answer": "36725"}
{"prompt": "35118,35119,35120,35121,35122,35123,35124,35125,35126", "answer": "35127"}
{"prompt": "21241,21242,21243,21244,21245,21246,21247,21248,21249", "answer": "21250"}
{"prompt": "15815,15816,15817", "answer": "15818"}
{"prompt": "17186,17187,17188,17189,17190", "answer": "17191"}
{"prompt": "43461,43462,43463,43464,43465,43466,43467", "answer": "43468"}
{"prompt": "32008", "answer": "32009"}
{"prompt": "10755,10756,10757", "answer": "10758"}
{"prompt": "25244,25245,25246,25247,25248,25249", "answer": "25250"}
{"prompt": "26892,26893,26894,26895,26896,26897,26898", "answer": "26899"}
{"prompt": "14588,14589,14590,14591,14592,14593", "answer": "14594"}
{"prompt": "20552,20553,20554,20555", "answer": "20556"}
{"prompt": "4018,4019", "answer": "4020"}
{"prompt": "34051,34052,34053", "answer": "34054"}
{"prompt": "2007,2008", "answer": "2009"}
{"prompt": "28091,28092,28093,28094,28095,28096,28097,28098,28099,28100", "answer": "28101"}
{"prompt": "27433,27434,27435,27436", "answer": "27437"}
{"prompt": "27201,27202,27203", "answer": "27204"}
{"prompt": "29213", "answer": "29214"}
{"prompt": "34692,34693,34694,34695,34696", "answer": "34697"}
{"prompt": "32257", "answer": "32258"}
{"prompt": "42878,42879,42880,42881,42882,42883,42884,42885,42886,42887", "answer": "42888"}
{"prompt": "23154,23155,23156,23157", "answer": "23158"}
{"prompt": "31020,31021,31022", "answer": "31023"}
{"prompt": "27059,27060,27061", "answer": "27062"}
{"prompt": "43180,43181", "answer": "43182"}
{"prompt": "973,974,975,976,977,978", "answer": "979"}
{"prompt": "43635,43636,43637,43638,43639,43640,43641,43642,43643", "answer": "43644"}
{"prompt": "8058,8059,8060,8061,8062,8063,8064,8065", "answer": "8066"}
{"prompt": "21939,21940,21941,21942,21943,21944,21945,21946,21947", "answer": "21948"}
{"prompt": "44543,44544,44545,44546,44547,44548,44549,44550", "answer": "44551"}
{"prompt": "40609,40610", "answer": "40611"}
{"prompt": "9815,9816", "answer": "9817"}
{"prompt": "43041,43042,43043,43044,43045,43046,43047,43048", "answer": "43049"}
{"prompt": "12589,12590,12591,12592,12593,12594,12595", "answer": "12596"}
{"prompt": "28150,28151", "answer": "28152"}
{"prompt": "42268,42269,42270,42271,42272,42273,42274,42275,42276", "answer": "42277"}
{"prompt": "911,912,913,914,915,916,917,918,919", "answer": "920"}
{"prompt": "13034,13035,13036,13037,13038,13039", "answer": "13040"}
{"prompt": "41666,41667,41668,41669,41670,41671,41672,41673,41674", "answer": "41675"}
{"prompt": "20080,20081,20082,20083,20084,20085,20086,20087,20088,20089", "answer": "20090"}
{"prompt": "41774,41775,41776,41777", "answer": "41778"}
{"prompt": "11429,11430,11431,11432,11433,11434,11435,11436", "answer": "11437"}
{"prompt": "45200,45201,45202,45203,45204", "answer": "45205"}
{"prompt": "1822,1823", "answer": "1824"}
{"prompt": "19724,19725", "answer": "19726"}
{"prompt": "16043", "answer": "16044"}
{"prompt": "24649", "answer": "24650"}
{"prompt": "6831,6832,6833,6834", "answer": "6835"}
{"prompt": "33872,33873,33874,33875,33876,33877,33878,33879,33880", "answer": "33881"}
{"prompt": "38573", "answer": "38574"}
{"prompt": "8332,8333,8334,8335,8336", "answer": "8337"}
{"prompt": "1579,1580", "answer": "1581"}
{"prompt": "16517,16518,16519,16520,16521,16522,16523,16524,16525,16526", "answer": "16527"}
{"prompt": "14482,14483,14484,14485,14486", "answer": "14487"}
{"prompt": "14398,14399,14400,14401,14402,14403,14404,14405", "answer": "14406"}
{"prompt": "32144,32145,32146,32147,32148,32149,32150", "answer": "32151"}
{"prompt": "667,668,669,670,671,672,673,674,675,676", "answer": "677"}
{"prompt": "41461,41462", "answer": "41463"}
{"prompt": "14454,14455,14456,14457", "answer": "14458"}
{"prompt": "22692,22693,22694,22695,22696,22697,22698", "answer": "22699"}
{"prompt": "31870", "answer": "31871"}
{"prompt": "10448,10449,10450,10451,10452,10453,10454,10455,10456,10457", "answer": "10458"}
{"prompt": "2116,2117,2118,2119", "answer": "2120"}
{"prompt": "3062,3063,3064,3065,3066,3067,3068", "answer": "3069"}
{"prompt": "30957", "answer": "30958"}
{"prompt": "40380,40381,40382,40383,40384,40385,40386", "answer": "40387"}
{"prompt": "14463,14464,14465,14466", "answer": "14467"}
{"prompt": "21848,21849,21850,21851,21852,21853,21854,21855,21856,21857", "answer": "21858"}
{"prompt": "10416", "answer": "10417"}
{"prompt": "10144,10145,10146,10147,10148,10149", "answer": "10150"}
{"prompt": "1180,1181,1182,1183,1184,1185,1186,1187,1188,1189", "answer": "1190"}
{"prompt": "42147,42148,42149,42150,42151", "answer": "42152"}
{"prompt": "36724,36725,36726,36727,36728,36729,36730", "answer": "36731"}
{"prompt": "750,751,752", "answer": "753"}
{"prompt": "4214,4215", "answer": "4216"}
{"prompt": "16848,16849,16850,16851,16852,16853,16854,16855", "answer": "16856"}
{"prompt": "40374,40375,40376", "answer": "40377"}
{"prompt": "24275,24276,24277,24278,24279,24280", "answer": "24281"}
{"prompt": "16375,16376,16377,16378", "answer": "16379"}
{"prompt": "26053", "answer": "26054"}
{"prompt": "8719,8720,8721,8722", "answer": "8723"}
{"prompt": "1257,1258", "answer": "1259"}
{"prompt": "5272,5273,5274,5275,5276,5277,5278,5279", "answer": "5280"}
{"prompt": "29412,29413", "answer": "29414"}
{"prompt": "30553,30554,30555,30556,30557,30558,30559,30560,30561,30562", "answer": "30563"}
{"prompt": "27034", "answer": "27035"}
{"prompt": "43019", "answer": "43020"}
{"prompt": "42420,42421,42422,42423,42424,42425,42426,42427,42428", "answer": "42429"}
{"prompt": "36829,36830,36831,36832,36833,36834,36835,36836,36837,36838", "answer": "36839"}
{"prompt": "20532,20533,20534,20535,20536,20537,20538,20539,20540", "answer": "20541"}
{"prompt": "27693,27694,27695,27696,27697,27698,27699", "answer": "27700"}
{"prompt": "36279,36280,36281", "answer": "36282"}
{"prompt": "34355,34356,34357,34358", "answer": "34359"}
{"prompt": "38928,38929", "answer": "38930"}
{"prompt": "31431,31432,31433,31434", "answer": "31435"}
{"prompt": "5105", "answer": "5106"}
{"prompt": "34545", "answer": "34546"}
{"prompt": "2855,2856,2857,2858,2859,2860", "answer": "2861"}
{"prompt": "42853", "answer": "42854"}
{"prompt": "18053,18054,18055,18056", "answer": "18057"}
{"prompt": "23165,23166", "answer": "23167"}
{"prompt": "26309,26310,26311,26312,26313", "answer": "26314"}
{"prompt": "15373,15374,15375,15376", "answer": "15377"}
{"prompt": "12979,12980,12981,12982,12983,12984,12985", "answer": "12986"}
{"prompt": "1879,1880", "answer": "1881"}
{"prompt": "3833,3834,3835,3836,3837,3838,3839", "answer": "3840"}
{"prompt": "18696,18697,18698,18699,18700,18701,18702,18703,18704,18705", "answer": "18706"}
{"prompt": "20078,20079,20080", "answer": "20081"}
{"prompt": "40797,40798,40799,40800,40801,40802,40803", "answer": "40804"}
{"prompt": "11979,11980,11981", "answer": "11982"}
{"prompt": "10020,10021,10022,10023,10024,10025,10026,10027", "answer": "10028"}
{"prompt": "37288,37289,37290,37291,37292,37293", "answer": "37294"}
{"prompt": "19491,19492,19493,19494,19495,19496,19497,19498,19499,19500", "answer": "19501"}
{"prompt": "33556,33557,33558,33559", "answer": "33560"}
{"prompt": "24397,24398,24399,24400,24401,24402,24403", "answer": "24404"}
{"prompt": "32383,32384,32385,32386,32387,32388,32389,32390", "answer": "32391"}
{"prompt": "43672,43673", "answer": "43674"}
{"prompt": "39434,39435,39436,39437,39438", "answer": "39439"}
{"prompt": "29123,29124", "answer": "29125"}
{"prompt": "13785,13786", "answer": "13787"}
{"prompt": "11322,11323,11324,11325", "answer": "11326"}
{"prompt": "26617,26618,26619,26620,26621,26622", "answer": "26623"}
{"prompt": "38943,38944,38945,38946,38947,38948,38949,38950", "answer": "38951"}
{"prompt": "37040,37041,37042,37043,37044", "answer": "37045"}
{"prompt": "35090,35091,35092,35093,35094,35095,35096,35097", "answer": "35098"}
{"prompt": "33446,33447,33448,33449,33450", "answer": "33451"}
{"prompt": "13404,13405,13406,13407,13408,13409", "answer": "13410"}
{"prompt": "30458", "answer": "30459"}
{"prompt": "27429,27430,27431", "answer": "27432"}
{"prompt": "43851,43852,43853,43854,43855,43856,43857,43858,43859", "answer": "43860"}
{"prompt": "18384,18385,18386,18387,18388,18389,18390,18391,18392", "answer": "18393"}
{"prompt": "38293,38294,38295,38296,38297,38298,38299,38300", "answer": "38301"}
{"prompt": "40677,40678,40679,40680,40681,40682,40683,40684,40685,40686", "answer": "40687"}
{"prompt": "9301,9302,9303,9304,9305,9306,9307", "answer": "9308"}
{"prompt": "2784", "answer": "2785"}
{"prompt": "2799,2800,2801,2802", "answer": "2803"}
{"prompt": "24494,24495,24496,24497,24498,24499,24500,24501,24502", "answer": "24503"}
{"prompt": "4522,4523,4524,4525,4526,4527,4528,4529,4530,4531", "answer": "4532"}
{"prompt": "24542,24543,24544,24545,24546,24547,24548,24549,24550,24551", "answer": "24552"}
{"prompt": "17778,17779,17780,17781,17782", "answer": "17783"}
{"prompt": "14916,14917,14918,14919,14920", "answer": "14921"}
{"prompt": "22550,22551,22552,22553,22554,22555", "answer": "22556"}
{"prompt": "4828,4829", "answer": "4830"}
{"prompt": "42515,42516,42517,42518,42519,42520,42521,42522,42523,42524", "answer": "42525"}
{"prompt": "9065,9066,9067,9068,9069,9070,9071,9072,9073,9074", "answer": "9075"}
{"prompt": "33190,33191,33192,33193,33194", "answer": "33195"}
{"prompt": "24449,24450,24451,24452,24453,24454,24455,24456", "answer": "24457"}
{"prompt": "22403,22404", "answer": "22405"}
{"prompt": "43231,43232", "answer": "43233"}
{"prompt": "11784,11785,11786,11787,11788,11789,11790,11791", "answer": "11792"}
{"prompt": "42097,42098,42099,42100,42101,42102", "answer": "42103"}
{"prompt": "10594,10595,10596,10597,10598,10599", "answer": "10600"}
{"prompt": "6688,6689,6690,6691,6692,6693,6694", "answer": "6695"}
{"prompt": "41779,41780,41781", "answer": "41782"}
{"prompt": "4719,4720,4721,4722,4723,4724,4725,4726", "answer": "4727"}
{"prompt": "34218,34219,34220,34221", "answer": "34222"}
{"prompt": "39869,39870", "answer": "39871"}
{"prompt": "1993,1994,1995,1996,1997,1998,1999,2000,2001,2002", "answer": "2003"}
{"prompt": "30426,30427,30428,30429,30430", "answer": "30431"}
{"prompt": "9286,9287,9288,9289,9290,9291,9292", "answer": "9293"}
{"prompt": "26855", "answer": "26856"}
{"prompt": "32542,32543,32544,32545,32546,32547", "answer": "32548"}
{"prompt": "515,516,517,518,519,520,521", "answer": "522"}
{"prompt": "40115", "answer": "40116"}
{"prompt": "43261,43262,43263", "answer": "43264"}
{"prompt": "21083,21084,21085,21086,21087,21088,21089", "answer": "21090"}
{"prompt": "19877", "answer": "19878"}
{"prompt": "29636,29637", "answer": "29638"}
{"prompt": "30213,30214,30215,30216,30217,30218,30219,30220,30221,30222", "answer": "30223"}
{"prompt": "33109,33110,33111,33112,33113,33114,33115,33116,33117", "answer": "33118"}
{"prompt": "28108,28109,28110,28111", "answer": "28112"}
{"prompt": "27907,27908,27909,27910,27911,27912,27913,27914,27915,27916", "answer": "27917"}
{"prompt": "15434,15435,15436,15437,15438,15439,15440", "answer": "15441"}
{"prompt": "8430,8431,8432,8433,8434,8435", "answer": "8436"}
{"prompt": "38750,38751,38752,38753,38754,38755,38756,38757,38758", "answer": "38759"}
{"prompt": "21866,21867,21868,21869,21870,21871", "answer": "21872"}
{"prompt": "3369,3370,3371,3372,3373,3374,3375,3376,3377,3378", "answer": "3379"}
{"prompt": "8609,8610,8611,8612,8613", "answer": "8614"}
{"prompt": "41930,41931", "answer": "41932"}
{"prompt": "2041,2042,2043,2044,2045", "answer": "2046"}
{"prompt": "16233,16234,16235,16236", "answer": "16237"}
{"prompt": "12830,12831,12832,12833,12834,12835", "answer": "12836"}
{"prompt": "45290,45291,45292,45293,45294,45295,45296,45297,45298,45299", "answer": "45300"}
{"prompt": "13202,13203,13204,13205,13206,13207,13208,13209,13210", "answer": "13211"}
{"prompt": "13815,13816,13817,13818,13819,13820,13821,13822,13823,13824", "answer": "13825"}
{"prompt": "33676,33677,33678,33679,33680,33681,33682", "answer": "33683"}
{"prompt": "22943", "answer": "22944"}
{"prompt": "33435", "answer": "33436"}
{"prompt": "34360,34361,34362", "answer": "34363"}
{"prompt": "16299,16300,16301,16302,16303,16304", "answer": "16305"}
{"prompt": "4265", "answer": "4266"}
{"prompt": "36552,36553,36554,36555,36556,36557", "answer": "36558"}
{"prompt": "20391,20392,20393,20394,20395,20396,20397,20398,20399", "answer": "20400"}
{"prompt": "44899", "answer": "44900"}
{"prompt": "26156,26157,26158,26159,26160,26161,26162,26163,26164,26165", "answer": "26166"}
{"prompt": "16000", "answer": "16001"}
{"prompt": "4657,4658,4659,4660,4661,4662,4663", "answer": "4664"}
{"prompt": "25925,25926,25927,25928,25929,25930", "answer": "25931"}
{"prompt": "14198,14199,14200", "answer": "14201"}
{"prompt": "43501,43502,43503,43504,43505,43506,43507,43508", "answer": "43509"}
{"prompt": "14565,14566,14567", "answer": "14568"}
{"prompt": "1818,1819,1820,1821,1822", "answer": "1823"}
{"prompt": "17909", "answer": "17910"}
{"prompt": "20515,20516,20517,20518", "answer": "20519"}
{"prompt": "642,643,644", "answer": "645"}
{"prompt": "27517,27518,27519,27520,27521,27522,27523,27524,27525,27526", "answer": "27527"}
{"prompt": "25480,25481,25482", "answer": "25483"}
{"prompt": "25410,25411,25412,25413,25414,25415,25416,25417,25418", "answer": "25419"}
{"prompt": "14284,14285,14286,14287,14288", "answer": "14289"}
{"prompt": "32062,32063,32064", "answer": "32065"}
{"prompt": "44413,44414,44415,44416", "answer": "44417"}
{"prompt": "19795,19796,19797,19798,19799,19800,19801,19802", "answer": "19803"}
{"prompt": "7302,7303,7304,7305,7306,7307", "answer": "7308"}
{"prompt": "30368", "answer": "30369"}
{"prompt": "29178,29179,29180,29181,29182", "answer": "29183"}
{"prompt": "28895,28896,28897,28898,28899,28900,28901,28902,28903", "answer": "28904"}
{"prompt": "37827,37828,37829,37830,37831,37832,37833", "answer": "37834"}
{"prompt": "1944,1945,1946,1947", "answer": "1948"}
{"prompt": "43316", "answer": "43317"}
{"prompt": "8447,8448,8449,8450,8451,8452,8453,8454,8455,8456", "answer": "8457"}
{"prompt": "32653,32654,32655,32656,32657,32658,32659", "answer": "32660"}
{"prompt": "31717,31718", "answer": "31719"}
{"prompt": "38842", "answer": "38843"}
{"prompt": "11362,11363,11364,11365", "answer": "11366"}
{"prompt": "17748", "answer": "17749"}
{"prompt": "44556,44557,44558,44559", "answer": "44560"}
{"prompt": "13127,13128,13129", "answer": "13130"}
{"prompt": "24289,24290,24291,24292,24293", "answer": "24294"}
{"prompt": "8356,8357,8358,8359,8360,8361,8362,8363", "answer": "8364"}
{"prompt": "18837,18838,18839,18840,18841,18842,18843,18844,18845", "answer": "18846"}
{"prompt": "41512,41513,41514,41515,41516,41517", "answer": "41518"}
{"prompt": "1247,1248", "answer": "1249"}
{"prompt": "42691,42692,42693,42694,42695,42696,42697", "answer": "42698"}
{"prompt": "37322,37323,37324,37325", "answer": "37326"}
{"prompt": "26976,26977,26978,26979,26980", "answer": "26981"}
{"prompt": "10156,10157,10158,10159,10160,10161", "answer": "10162"}
{"prompt": "34980,34981,34982,34983,34984", "answer": "34985"}
{"prompt": "17782,17783,17784,17785,17786,17787,17788,17789", "answer": "17790"}
{"prompt": "20473,20474,20475,20476,20477,20478,20479", "answer": "20480"}
{"prompt": "33063,33064,33065,33066,33067,33068", "answer": "33069"}
{"prompt": "2917,2918,2919,2920,2921,2922", "answer": "2923"}
{"prompt": "22815,22816,22817,22818,22819,22820,22821,22822", "answer": "22823"}
{"prompt": "35859,35860,35861,35862,35863,35864,35865,35866", "answer": "35867"}
{"prompt": "44500,44501,44502", "answer": "44503"}
{"prompt": "15541,15542,15543,15544,15545,15546,15547,15548,15549,15550", "answer": "15551"}
{"prompt": "2549,2550,2551,2552,2553,2554", "answer": "2555"}
{"prompt": "38582,38583,38584,38585,38586,38587,38588,38589", "answer": "38590"}
{"prompt": "42500,42501,42502,42503,42504,42505,42506,42507,42508,42509", "answer": "42510"}
{"prompt": "36003,36004,36005,36006,36007,36008,36009", "answer": "36010"}
{"prompt": "28590,28591,28592,28593,28594,28595,28596", "answer": "28597"}
{"prompt": "31211,31212,31213", "answer": "31214"}
{"prompt": "26222,26223,26224,26225,26226,26227,26228,26229", "answer": "26230"}
{"prompt": "22701,22702,22703,22704,22705,22706", "answer": "22707"}
{"prompt": "33709,33710,33711,33712,33713,33714,33715,33716,33717,33718", "answer": "33719"}
{"prompt": "36364,36365,36366,36367,36368", "answer": "36369"}
{"prompt": "35730,35731,35732,35733,35734,35735,35736,35737,35738,35739", "answer": "35740"}
{"prompt": "34724,34725,34726,34727,34728", "answer": "34729"}
{"prompt": "18329,18330,18331,18332,18333", "answer": "18334"}
{"prompt": "8731,8732,8733,8734,8735,8736,8737,8738", "answer": "8739"}
{"prompt": "2227,2228,2229,2230", "answer": "2231"}
{"prompt": "32727,32728,32729,32730,32731,32732", "answer": "32733"}
{"prompt": "34022", "answer": "34023"}
{"prompt": "37188,37189,37190", "answer": "37191"}
{"prompt": "28264,28265,28266,28267,28268,28269,28270,28271", "answer": "28272"}
{"prompt": "40596,40597,40598,40599,40600,40601,40602", "answer": "40603"}
{"prompt": "27368,27369", "answer": "27370"}
{"prompt": "41813,41814,41815,41816,41817", "answer": "41818"}
{"prompt": "20330,20331,20332,20333,20334,20335,20336,20337,20338", "answer": "20339"}
{"prompt": "35661,35662,35663,35664,35665,35666,35667,35668", "answer": "35669"}
{"prompt": "41867,41868,41869,41870,41871,41872", "answer": "41873"}
{"prompt": "2108", "answer": "2109"}
{"prompt": "28558,28559,28560,28561,28562,28563,28564,28565,28566", "answer": "28567"}
{"prompt": "36853,36854,36855,36856,36857,36858,36859,36860", "answer": "36861"}
{"prompt": "38481,38482,38483,38484", "answer": "38485"}
{"prompt": "41548,41549,41550,41551,41552,41553,41554,41555,41556", "answer": "41557"}
{"prompt": "43467,43468,43469,43470,43471,43472,43473,43474,43475,43476", "answer": "43477"}
{"prompt": "40919,40920,40921,40922,40923,40924,40925,40926", "answer": "40927"}
{"prompt": "12639,12640,12641,12642,12643,12644,12645,12646", "answer": "12647"}
{"prompt": "1126,1127,1128,1129,1130,1131,1132", "answer": "1133"}
{"prompt": "1058,1059", "answer": "1060"}
{"prompt": "24389,24390,24391,24392,24393,24394,24395,24396,24397", "answer": "24398"}
{"prompt": "9835", "answer": "9836"}
{"prompt": "17470,17471,17472,17473,17474", "answer": "17475"}
{"prompt": "21632,21633,21634", "answer": "21635"}
{"prompt": "4078,4079,4080,4081,4082,4083,4084,4085,4086,4087", "answer": "4088"}
{"prompt": "33234,33235,33236,33237", "answer": "33238"}
{"prompt": "26027,26028,26029,26030,26031,26032,26033,26034", "answer": "26035"}
{"prompt": "20272,20273,20274,20275,20276,20277,20278,20279,20280", "answer": "20281"}
{"prompt": "1988,1989,1990,1991,1992,1993", "answer": "1994"}
{"prompt": "23050", "answer": "23051"}
{"prompt": "42496,42497,42498,42499,42500", "answer": "42501"}
{"prompt": "11692,11693,11694,11695,11696,11697,11698,11699,11700,11701", "answer": "11702"}
{"prompt": "18590,18591,18592,18593,18594,18595,18596", "answer": "18597"}
{"prompt": "43373,43374,43375,43376", "answer": "43377"}
{"prompt": "19184,19185,19186,19187,19188,19189,19190,19191,19192,19193", "answer": "19194"}
{"prompt": "31817,31818,31819,31820,31821,31822,31823,31824", "answer": "31825"}
{"prompt": "8957,8958,8959,8960,8961", "answer": "8962"}
{"prompt": "21348,21349,21350,21351,21352", "answer": "21353"}
{"prompt": "19802,19803,19804,19805,19806,19807", "answer": "19808"}
{"prompt": "40369,40370,40371,40372,40373", "answer": "40374"}
{"prompt": "10784,10785,10786,10787,10788,10789,10790,10791,10792", "answer": "10793"}
{"prompt": "5828,5829,5830,5831,5832,5833,5834,5835,5836", "answer": "5837"}
{"prompt": "32477,32478,32479,32480,32481,32482,32483", "answer": "32484"}
{"prompt": "32522,32523", "answer": "32524"}
{"prompt": "44280,44281,44282,44283,44284,44285,44286,44287,44288,44289", "answer": "44290"}
{"prompt": "13443,13444,13445,13446,13447,13448", "answer": "13449"}
{"prompt": "26238,26239", "answer": "26240"}
{"prompt": "14656", "answer": "14657"}
{"prompt": "36557,36558,36559,36560,36561,36562,36563", "answer": "36564"}
{"prompt": "30988,30989", "answer": "30990"}
{"prompt": "10862,10863,10864,10865,10866,10867,10868,10869,10870", "answer": "10871"}
{"prompt": "30741,30742,30743,30744,30745,30746,30747,30748", "answer": "30749"}
{"prompt": "8313,8314,8315,8316,8317,8318,8319,8320,8321,8322", "answer": "8323"}
{"prompt": "803,804,805,806,807,808", "answer": "809"}
{"prompt": "12377,12378,12379,12380,12381,12382,12383,12384,12385,12386", "answer": "12387"}
{"prompt": "20032,20033,20034,20035,20036,20037,20038,20039,20040", "answer": "20041"}
{"prompt": "22359,22360,22361,22362,22363,22364,22365,22366,22367", "answer": "22368"}
{"prompt": "1798,1799,1800,1801", "answer": "1802"}
{"prompt": "8560,8561,8562,8563,8564,8565", "answer": "8566"}
{"prompt": "18525,18526,18527,18528,18529,18530,18531,18532,18533,18534", "answer": "18535"}
{"prompt": "4354,4355,4356,4357,4358", "answer": "4359"}
{"prompt": "3689,3690,3691,3692,3693,3694,3695", "answer": "3696"}
{"prompt": "11174,11175,11176,11177,11178,11179,11180,11181,11182", "answer": "11183"}
{"prompt": "19182", "answer": "19183"}
{"prompt": "36238,36239", "answer": "36240"}
{"prompt": "4728,4729,4730,4731,4732,4733,4734", "answer": "4735"}
{"prompt": "38162,38163,38164,38165,38166,38167,38168,38169", "answer": "38170"}
{"prompt": "21124,21125", "answer": "21126"}
{"prompt": "43073,43074,43075,43076,43077,43078,43079", "answer": "43080"}
{"prompt": "44831,44832,44833,44834,44835,44836", "answer": "44837"}
{"prompt": "43868,43869,43870,43871,43872", "answer": "43873"}
{"prompt": "43368,43369,43370,43371", "answer": "43372"}
{"prompt": "38332", "answer": "38333"}
{"prompt": "16333", "answer": "16334"}
{"prompt": "42428,42429,42430,42431,42432,42433", "answer": "42434"}
{"prompt": "29969,29970,29971,29972,29973,29974,29975", "answer": "29976"}
{"prompt": "5124,5125,5126,5127,5128,5129,5130,5131,5132,5133", "answer": "5134"}
{"prompt": "31826,31827,31828,31829", "answer": "31830"}
{"prompt": "20743,20744,20745,20746,20747,20748,20749,20750,20751", "answer": "20752"}
{"prompt": "33525", "answer": "33526"}
{"prompt": "23043,23044,23045,23046,23047,23048,23049,23050", "answer": "23051"}
{"prompt": "13394,13395,13396,13397,13398,13399,13400", "answer": "13401"}
{"prompt": "13215,13216,13217,13218,13219,13220,13221,13222,13223", "answer": "13224"}
{"prompt": "18608,18609,18610,18611,18612,18613,18614", "answer": "18615"}
{"prompt": "35652,35653,35654,35655,35656,35657,35658", "answer": "35659"}
{"prompt": "30966,30967", "answer": "30968"}
{"prompt": "21166,21167", "answer": "21168"}
{"prompt": "7732", "answer": "7733"}
{"prompt": "31125,31126,31127,31128,31129,31130,31131", "answer": "31132"}
{"prompt": "7052,7053,7054,7055,7056,7057,7058", "answer": "7059"}
{"prompt": "18433,18434,18435,18436,18437,18438,18439,18440", "answer": "18441"}
{"prompt": "44836,44837,44838,44839,44840,44841,44842,44843", "answer": "44844"}
{"prompt": "23964,23965,23966", "answer": "23967"}
{"prompt": "27165,27166,27167", "answer": "27168"}
{"prompt": "33952,33953,33954,33955,33956,33957", "answer": "33958"}
{"prompt": "27227,27228", "answer": "27229"}
{"prompt": "25421,25422,25423,25424,25425,25426,25427,25428,25429", "answer": "25430"}
{"prompt": "6856,6857,6858,6859", "answer": "6860"}
{"prompt": "12749,12750,12751,12752,12753,12754,12755,12756,12757,12758", "answer": "12759"}
{"prompt": "2599,2600,2601,2602,2603,2604,2605,2606,2607,2608", "answer": "2609"}
{"prompt": "32213,32214,32215", "answer": "32216"}
{"prompt": "20299,20300,20301,20302,20303,20304,20305,20306", "answer": "20307"}
{"prompt": "21095,21096,21097,21098,21099,21100", "answer": "21101"}
{"prompt": "15268", "answer": "15269"}
{"prompt": "28923,28924,28925,28926,28927,28928", "answer": "28929"}
{"prompt": "38784", "answer": "38785"}
{"prompt": "165,166,167,168,169", "answer": "170"}
{"prompt": "40978,40979,40980,40981,40982,40983", "answer": "40984"}
{"prompt": "36102", "answer": "36103"}
{"prompt": "30313,30314", "answer": "30315"}
{"prompt": "45124,45125,45126,45127,45128", "answer": "45129"}
{"prompt": "7577,7578,7579,7580,7581,7582,7583,7584,7585,7586", "answer": "7587"}
{"prompt": "3542,3543,3544,3545,3546", "answer": "3547"}
{"prompt": "24949,24950,24951,24952", "answer": "24953"}
{"prompt": "23457,23458,23459,23460,23461,23462,23463", "answer": "23464"}
{"prompt": "872,873,874,875", "answer": "876"}
{"prompt": "21607,21608,21609,21610,21611,21612,21613,21614,21615", "answer": "21616"}
{"prompt": "36500", "answer": "36501"}
{"prompt": "7146,7147,7148,7149,7150,7151,7152,7153,7154", "answer": "7155"}
{"prompt": "29492,29493,29494,29495,29496,29497,29498,29499,29500", "answer": "29501"}
{"prompt": "30249,30250,30251,30252,30253,30254,30255,30256,30257,30258", "answer": "30259"}
{"prompt": "19571,19572,19573,19574,19575,19576,19577,19578,19579,19580", "answer": "19581"}
{"prompt": "30474,30475,30476", "answer": "30477"}
{"prompt": "16128,16129,16130,16131,16132", "answer": "16133"}
{"prompt": "6004,6005,6006,6007", "answer": "6008"}
{"prompt": "27703,27704,27705,27706,27707,27708,27709,27710,27711,27712", "answer": "27713"}
{"prompt": "7483,7484,7485", "answer": "7486"}
{"prompt": "8372,8373,8374,8375,8376,8377,8378", "answer": "8379"}
{"prompt": "10703,10704,10705,10706,10707,10708,10709", "answer": "10710"}
{"prompt": "36354,36355,36356,36357,36358,36359,36360,36361", "answer": "36362"}
{"prompt": "37733,37734,37735,37736,37737,37738", "answer": "37739"}
{"prompt": "18249,18250", "answer": "18251"}
{"prompt": "9398,9399,9400,9401", "answer": "9402"}
{"prompt": "7285,7286,7287,7288,7289,7290", "answer": "7291"}
{"prompt": "7423,7424", "answer": "7425"}
{"prompt": "20648,20649,20650,20651,20652,20653,20654,20655,20656,20657", "answer": "20658"}
{"prompt": "21292,21293,21294,21295,21296,21297,21298,21299,21300", "answer": "21301"}
{"prompt": "23775,23776", "answer": "23777"}
{"prompt": "4944,4945,4946,4947,4948,4949,4950,4951,4952,4953", "answer": "4954"}
{"prompt": "14211,14212,14213,14214", "answer": "14215"}
{"prompt": "16714,16715,16716", "answer": "16717"}
{"prompt": "40957,40958", "answer": "40959"}
{"prompt": "3937,3938,3939,3940,3941,3942,3943,3944,3945,3946", "answer": "3947"}
{"prompt": "12035", "answer": "12036"}
{"prompt": "34800", "answer": "34801"}
{"prompt": "35049,35050,35051", "answer": "35052"}
{"prompt": "34899,34900,34901,34902,34903,34904,34905,34906", "answer": "34907"}
{"prompt": "31411,31412,31413,31414,31415,31416,31417,31418", "answer": "31419"}
{"prompt": "23537,23538,23539,23540", "answer": "23541"}
{"prompt": "22563,22564,22565,22566,22567,22568,22569", "answer": "22570"}
{"prompt": "14085,14086,14087,14088,14089,14090,14091,14092,14093", "answer": "14094"}
{"prompt": "28517,28518,28519,28520,28521,28522", "answer": "28523"}
{"prompt": "16420,16421,16422,16423,16424,16425,16426,16427,16428,16429", "answer": "16430"}
{"prompt": "39531,39532,39533,39534,39535", "answer": "39536"}
{"prompt": "27977,27978,27979,27980,27981,27982,27983,27984", "answer": "27985"}
{"prompt": "31607,31608,31609,31610,31611,31612,31613,31614,31615,31616", "answer": "31617"}
{"prompt": "1323,1324,1325,1326,1327,1328,1329,1330,1331,1332", "answer": "1333"}
{"prompt": "45210,45211,45212", "answer": "45213"}
{"prompt": "44301,44302", "answer": "44303"}
{"prompt": "22784,22785,22786,22787,22788,22789,22790", "answer": "22791"}
{"prompt": "2217,2218,2219,2220", "answer": "2221"}
{"prompt": "2301", "answer": "2302"}
{"prompt": "34369,34370,34371", "answer": "34372"}
{"prompt": "42218,42219,42220,42221", "answer": "42222"}
{"prompt": "36102,36103,36104,36105,36106", "answer": "36107"}
{"prompt": "14457,14458,14459,14460,14461,14462,14463", "answer": "14464"}
{"prompt": "44985,44986,44987", "answer": "44988"}
{"prompt": "37059,37060,37061,37062", "answer": "37063"}
{"prompt": "6437,6438,6439,6440,6441,6442,6443,6444", "answer": "6445"}
{"prompt": "32826,32827,32828,32829,32830,32831", "answer": "32832"}
{"prompt": "33525,33526", "answer": "33527"}
{"prompt": "3873,3874,3875,3876,3877", "answer": "3878"}
{"prompt": "37624,37625", "answer": "37626"}
{"prompt": "29743,29744,29745,29746,29747,29748,29749,29750", "answer": "29751"}
{"prompt": "27314,27315,27316,27317,27318", "answer": "27319"}
{"prompt": "39598,39599,39600,39601,39602,39603,39604,39605", "answer": "39606"}
{"prompt": "30248,30249", "answer": "30250"}
{"prompt": "28835,28836,28837,28838,28839,28840,28841,28842", "answer": "28843"}
{"prompt": "8590,8591,8592,8593,8594,8595,8596", "answer": "8597"}
{"prompt": "28374,28375,28376,28377,28378,28379", "answer": "28380"}
{"prompt": "42853,42854,42855,42856,42857", "answer": "42858"}
{"prompt": "41910,41911,41912,41913,41914,41915,41916", "answer": "41917"}
{"prompt": "25300", "answer": "25301"}
{"prompt": "34766,34767,34768,34769,34770,34771,34772", "answer": "34773"}
{"prompt": "18563,18564,18565,18566,18567,18568,18569,18570,18571", "answer": "18572"}
{"prompt": "37494,37495,37496,37497,37498,37499,37500,37501", "answer": "37502"}
{"prompt": "24848,24849,24850", "answer": "24851"}
{"prompt": "3546,3547,3548,3549,3550,3551,3552,3553,3554", "answer": "3555"}
{"prompt": "8604,8605", "answer": "8606"}
{"prompt": "5874,5875,5876,5877,5878,5879,5880,5881", "answer": "5882"}
{"prompt": "27327,27328,27329,27330,27331,27332,27333,27334,27335,27336", "answer": "27337"}
{"prompt": "31787", "answer": "31788"}
{"prompt": "1042,1043,1044", "answer": "1045"}
{"prompt": "1590,1591,1592,1593,1594,1595", "answer": "1596"}
{"prompt": "38474,38475,38476,38477,38478,38479,38480,38481", "answer": "38482"}
{"prompt": "15131,15132,15133", "answer": "15134"}
{"prompt": "44980,44981,44982,44983,44984,44985", "answer": "44986"}
{"prompt": "22998,22999,23000,23001,23002,23003,23004", "answer": "23005"}
{"prompt": "21695", "answer": "21696"}
{"prompt": "13040,13041,13042,13043,13044,13045,13046,13047,13048,13049", "answer": "13050"}
{"prompt": "21548,21549,21550,21551,21552,21553,21554", "answer": "21555"}
{"prompt": "35423,35424,35425,35426,35427,35428,35429", "answer": "35430"}
{"prompt": "12141,12142,12143,12144", "answer": "12145"}
{"prompt": "39953", "answer": "39954"}
{"prompt": "4821,4822,4823,4824,4825", "answer": "4826"}
{"prompt": "9652,9653,9654,9655,9656,9657", "answer": "9658"}
{"prompt": "19443,19444,19445,19446,19447,19448,19449,19450", "answer": "19451"}
{"prompt": "24616,24617", "answer": "24618"}
{"prompt": "28965,28966,28967,28968", "answer": "28969"}
{"prompt": "18821,18822", "answer": "18823"}
{"prompt": "34505,34506,34507,34508,34509,34510,34511,34512,34513,34514", "answer": "34515"}
{"prompt": "26431,26432", "answer": "26433"}
{"prompt": "37405,37406", "answer": "37407"}
{"prompt": "6673,6674,6675,6676,6677,6678,6679", "answer": "6680"}
{"prompt": "24617,24618,24619,24620,24621,24622,24623,24624", "answer": "24625"}
{"prompt": "22536,22537,22538,22539,22540,22541,22542,22543,22544", "answer": "22545"}
{"prompt": "17495,17496,17497,17498,17499,17500,17501", "answer": "17502"}
{"prompt": "14163,14164,14165,14166", "answer": "14167"}
{"prompt": "45319,45320", "answer": "45321"}
{"prompt": "35308,35309,35310,35311,35312,35313,35314,35315,35316", "answer": "35317"}
{"prompt": "31369,31370,31371,31372,31373", "answer": "31374"}
{"prompt": "34148,34149,34150,34151,34152,34153", "answer": "34154"}
{"prompt": "2466,2467,2468,2469,2470,2471,2472,2473", "answer": "2474"}
{"prompt": "14762,14763,14764,14765,14766,14767,14768", "answer": "14769"}
{"prompt": "38198,38199,38200,38201,38202", "answer": "38203"}
{"prompt": "11334,11335,11336,11337,11338,11339", "answer": "11340"}
{"prompt": "24593,24594,24595,24596,24597,24598", "answer": "24599"}
{"prompt": "28492,28493", "answer": "28494"}
{"prompt": "29301,29302", "answer": "29303"}
{"prompt": "10429,10430,10431", "answer": "10432"}
{"prompt": "5208,5209,5210", "answer": "5211"}
{"prompt": "36091,36092,36093,36094", "answer": "36095"}
{"prompt": "32008,32009,32010,32011,32012,32013", "answer": "32014"}
{"prompt": "26694,26695", "answer": "26696"}
{"prompt": "17052,17053,17054,17055,17056,17057,17058,17059,17060", "answer": "17061"}
{"prompt": "12691,12692", "answer": "12693"}
{"prompt": "20931,20932,20933,20934,20935,20936,20937,20938", "answer": "20939"}
{"prompt": "35748,35749", "answer": "35750"}
{"prompt": "42319,42320,42321,42322,42323,42324,42325,42326,42327,42328", "answer": "42329"}
{"prompt": "13210", "answer": "13211"}
{"prompt": "5616,5617,5618,5619", "answer": "5620"}
{"prompt": "24470", "answer": "24471"}
{"prompt": "41004,41005,41006,41007", "answer": "41008"}
{"prompt": "2232,2233,2234,2235", "answer": "2236"}
{"prompt": "19021", "answer": "19022"}
{"prompt": "14656,14657,14658,14659,14660,14661", "answer": "14662"}
{"prompt": "19434", "answer": "19435"}
{"prompt": "26343,26344,26345", "answer": "26346"}
{"prompt": "33636,33637,33638,33639,33640,33641", "answer": "33642"}
{"prompt": "37196,37197,37198,37199,37200,37201,37202,37203,37204", "answer": "37205"}
{"prompt": "7827,7828,7829,7830,7831", "answer": "7832"}
{"prompt": "18693,18694", "answer": "18695"}
{"prompt": "32081,32082,32083,32084", "answer": "32085"}
{"prompt": "37327", "answer": "37328"}
{"prompt": "18603,18604,18605,18606,18607,18608", "answer": "18609"}
{"prompt": "13436,13437,13438,13439,13440,13441,13442,13443", "answer": "13444"}
{"prompt": "5847", "answer": "5848"}
{"prompt": "296,297,298,299,300,301,302,303,304", "answer": "305"}
{"prompt": "10385", "answer": "10386"}
{"prompt": "17009,17010,17011,17012,17013,17014,17015,17016,17017,17018", "answer": "17019"}
{"prompt": "26965,26966,26967,26968", "answer": "26969"}
{"prompt": "32894,32895", "answer": "32896"}
{"prompt": "17360,17361,17362,17363,17364,17365,17366,17367", "answer": "17368"}
{"prompt": "5183", "answer": "5184"}
{"prompt": "36439,36440,36441,36442", "answer": "36443"}
{"prompt": "33818,33819,33820,33821", "answer": "33822"}
{"prompt": "33861,33862,33863,33864,33865", "answer": "33866"}
{"prompt": "1517,1518", "answer": "1519"}
{"prompt": "16537,16538,16539,16540,16541,16542,16543,16544", "answer": "16545"}
{"prompt": "23105,23106,23107", "answer": "23108"}
{"prompt": "24523,24524,24525,24526,24527,24528,24529,24530,24531", "answer": "24532"}
{"prompt": "33283", "answer": "33284"}
{"prompt": "44096,44097,44098,44099", "answer": "44100"}
{"prompt": "24070,24071,24072,24073,24074", "answer": "24075"}
{"prompt": "1197,1198,1199,1200,1201,1202", "answer": "1203"}
{"prompt": "11325,11326,11327,11328,11329,11330,11331,11332,11333,11334", "answer": "11335"}
{"prompt": "21542,21543,21544,21545", "answer": "21546"}
{"prompt": "361,362,363,364", "answer": "365"}
{"prompt": "40573,40574,40575,40576,40577,40578,40579,40580,40581", "answer": "40582"}
{"prompt": "20967,20968,20969", "answer": "20970"}
{"prompt": "4438,4439,4440,4441", "answer": "4442"}
{"prompt": "16961,16962", "answer": "16963"}
{"prompt": "43868", "answer": "43869"}
{"prompt": "997,998", "answer": "999"}
{"prompt": "5495,5496,5497,5498,5499,5500,5501", "answer": "5502"}
{"prompt": "15846,15847,15848,15849,15850,15851", "answer": "15852"}
{"prompt": "43699,43700,43701,43702,43703,43704,43705,43706", "answer": "43707"}
{"prompt": "15578,15579,15580,15581,15582,15583,15584,15585,15586,15587", "answer": "15588"}
{"prompt": "17199,17200,17201,17202,17203,17204,17205", "answer": "17206"}
{"prompt": "3931,3932,3933", "answer": "3934"}
{"prompt": "38601,38602,38603,38604", "answer": "38605"}
{"prompt": "26034,26035,26036,26037,26038,26039,26040", "answer": "26041"}
{"prompt": "42190", "answer": "42191"}
{"prompt": "39244,39245,39246,39247,39248,39249,39250,39251", "answer": "39252"}
{"prompt": "10324,10325,10326,10327,10328,10329", "answer": "10330"}
{"prompt": "24927,24928,24929", "answer": "24930"}
{"prompt": "40628,40629,40630,40631,40632,40633,40634,40635,40636", "answer": "40637"}
{"prompt": "18309,18310,18311,18312,18313,18314,18315", "answer": "18316"}
{"prompt": "21871,21872,21873,21874", "answer": "21875"}
{"prompt": "3661,3662,3663", "answer": "3664"}
{"prompt": "24923,24924,24925,24926,24927", "answer": "24928"}
{"prompt": "10852,10853,10854,10855,10856,10857,10858,10859,10860,10861", "answer": "10862"}
{"prompt": "10870,10871,10872,10873,10874,10875,10876,10877,10878", "answer": "10879"}
{"prompt": "17853", "answer": "17854"}
{"prompt": "17692,17693,17694", "answer": "17695"}
{"prompt": "45194,45195,45196,45197,45198,45199,45200", "answer": "45201"}
{"prompt": "35560,35561,35562,35563,35564,35565,35566", "answer": "35567"}
{"prompt": "26086,26087,26088,26089,26090,26091,26092,26093,26094", "answer": "26095"}
{"prompt": "27684,27685,27686,27687,27688,27689,27690,27691", "answer": "27692"}
{"prompt": "18976", "answer": "18977"}
{"prompt": "6328,6329,6330", "answer": "6331"}
{"prompt": "42198,42199", "answer": "42200"}
{"prompt": "39903,39904,39905,39906,39907,39908,39909,39910,39911,39912", "answer": "39913"}
{"prompt": "27800,27801,27802,27803,27804,27805,27806,27807,27808,27809", "answer": "27810"}
{"prompt": "30632,30633,30634,30635,30636,30637,30638,30639", "answer": "30640"}
{"prompt": "37019,37020,37021,37022,37023,37024,37025", "answer": "37026"}
{"prompt": "6844,6845,6846", "answer": "6847"}
{"prompt": "764,765,766,767,768,769,770,771,772,773", "answer": "774"}
{"prompt": "23729,23730,23731,23732,23733,23734,23735,23736", "answer": "23737"}
{"prompt": "5440,5441", "answer": "5442"}
{"prompt": "37825,37826,37827", "answer": "37828"}
{"prompt": "4571,4572,4573,4574,4575,4576", "answer": "4577"}
{"prompt": "22983,22984,22985,22986,22987,22988,22989,22990,22991,22992", "answer": "22993"}
{"prompt": "24581,24582,24583,24584,24585,24586,24587,24588,24589", "answer": "24590"}
{"prompt": "42678,42679,42680,42681,42682,42683,42684,42685", "answer": "42686"}
{"prompt": "37502,37503,37504,37505,37506,37507", "answer": "37508"}
{"prompt": "25380,25381,25382,25383,25384,25385", "answer": "25386"}
{"prompt": "22824,22825,22826,22827,22828,22829", "answer": "22830"}
{"prompt": "30754,30755,30756,30757,30758,30759,30760,30761,30762", "answer": "30763"}
{"prompt": "9705,9706,9707,9708,9709,9710,9711,9712,9713,9714", "answer": "9715"}
{"prompt": "20306,20307,20308,20309,20310,20311,20312,20313,20314,20315", "answer": "20316"}
{"prompt": "41084,41085,41086,41087", "answer": "41088"}
{"prompt": "31443,31444,31445,31446", "answer": "31447"}
{"prompt": "8711,8712,8713,8714,8715,8716,8717,8718,8719", "answer": "8720"}
{"prompt": "30687,30688,30689,30690,30691,30692,30693,30694", "answer": "30695"}
{"prompt": "6814,6815", "answer": "6816"}
{"prompt": "39118", "answer": "39119"}
{"prompt": "41471,41472,41473,41474,41475,41476,41477,41478,41479,41480", "answer": "41481"}
{"prompt": "11230,11231,11232,11233,11234,11235,11236", "answer": "11237"}
{"prompt": "4502,4503,4504,4505,4506,4507,4508,4509,4510", "answer": "4511"}
{"prompt": "43067,43068,43069,43070,43071,43072,43073", "answer": "43074"}
{"prompt": "38981,38982,38983,38984", "answer": "38985"}
{"prompt": "14661,14662", "answer": "14663"}
{"prompt": "16514", "answer": "16515"}
{"prompt": "18777,18778,18779,18780", "answer": "18781"}
{"prompt": "31133,31134,31135,31136,31137,31138,31139,31140", "answer": "31141"}
{"prompt": "876", "answer": "877"}
{"prompt": "17585,17586,17587,17588,17589,17590,17591,17592,17593,17594", "answer": "17595"}
{"prompt": "3815,3816,3817", "answer": "3818"}
{"prompt": "7618,7619,7620,7621,7622,7623,7624,7625,7626", "answer": "7627"}
{"prompt": "9193,9194,9195,9196,9197,9198,9199,9200,9201,9202", "answer": "9203"}
{"prompt": "3560", "answer": "3561"}
{"prompt": "19245,19246,19247,19248,19249", "answer": "19250"}
{"prompt": "4476,4477,4478,4479,4480,4481,4482,4483,4484", "answer": "4485"}
{"prompt": "32790,32791,32792,32793,32794,32795,32796,32797,32798", "answer": "32799"}
{"prompt": "22449,22450,22451,22452,22453,22454,22455,22456,22457,22458", "answer": "22459"}
{"prompt": "5671,5672,5673,5674", "answer": "5675"}
{"prompt": "0,1", "answer": "2"}
{"prompt": "2424,2425,2426,2427,2428,2429,2430,2431", "answer": "2432"}
{"prompt": "4229,4230", "answer": "4231"}
{"prompt": "7464,7465,7466,7467,7468,7469,7470,7471,7472,7473", "answer": "7474"}
{"prompt": "25615,25616,25617,25618,25619,25620,25621,25622,25623,25624", "answer": "25625"}
{"prompt": "23247", "answer": "23248"}
{"prompt": "18015,18016,18017,18018,18019,18020", "answer": "18021"}
{"prompt": "38176,38177,38178,38179,38180,38181,38182", "answer": "38183"}
{"prompt": "213,214,215,216,217,218", "answer": "219"}
{"prompt": "34845,34846,34847,34848,34849,34850,34851,34852,34853,34854", "answer": "34855"}
{"prompt": "26835", "answer": "26836"}
{"prompt": "11653,11654,11655,11656", "answer": "11657"}
{"prompt": "23429,23430,23431,23432,23433,23434,23435,23436,23437", "answer": "23438"}
{"prompt": "11262", "answer": "11263"}
{"prompt": "38856,38857,38858,38859,38860,38861,38862,38863,38864", "answer": "38865"}
{"prompt": "31794,31795", "answer": "31796"}
{"prompt": "42357,42358,42359", "answer": "42360"}
{"prompt": "25175,25176,25177,25178,25179,25180,25181", "answer": "25182"}
{"prompt": "33345,33346,33347,33348,33349,33350,33351,33352", "answer": "33353"}
{"prompt": "8299,8300", "answer": "8301"}
{"prompt": "5068,5069,5070,5071,5072,5073,5074", "answer": "5075"}
{"prompt": "18404,18405,18406,18407,18408,18409,18410,18411,18412", "answer": "18413"}
{"prompt": "35876,35877,35878,35879,35880,35881,35882,35883,35884", "answer": "35885"}
{"prompt": "20880,20881,20882,20883,20884,20885,20886", "answer": "20887"}
{"prompt": "41572,41573", "answer": "41574"}
{"prompt": "19147,19148,19149", "answer": "19150"}
{"prompt": "7648,7649,7650,7651,7652", "answer": "7653"}
{"prompt": "26168,26169,26170,26171", "answer": "26172"}
{"prompt": "1854,1855,1856,1857,1858,1859", "answer": "1860"}
{"prompt": "26743,26744,26745,26746", "answer": "26747"}
{"prompt": "27594,27595", "answer": "27596"}
{"prompt": "18949,18950,18951,18952,18953,18954,18955,18956,18957", "answer": "18958"}
{"prompt": "25141", "answer": "25142"}
{"prompt": "21695,21696,21697,21698,21699,21700,21701,21702,21703", "answer": "21704"}
{"prompt": "27634,27635,27636,27637,27638,27639,27640,27641,27642", "answer": "27643"}
{"prompt": "4487,4488,4489,4490,4491", "answer": "4492"}
{"prompt": "2172,2173,2174,2175,2176,2177,2178,2179,2180", "answer": "2181"}
{"prompt": "32206,32207,32208,32209,32210,32211,32212,32213", "answer": "32214"}
{"prompt": "38719,38720,38721,38722,38723,38724,38725,38726", "answer": "38727"}
{"prompt": "25727,25728,25729,25730,25731,25732,25733,25734,25735,25736", "answer": "25737"}
{"prompt": "17892,17893,17894,17895,17896,17897,17898,17899,17900,17901", "answer": "17902"}
{"prompt": "21002,21003,21004,21005,21006,21007,21008,21009,21010", "answer": "21011"}
{"prompt": "10900,10901,10902", "answer": "10903"}
{"prompt": "30768", "answer": "30769"}
{"prompt": "3572,3573,3574", "answer": "3575"}
{"prompt": "22095,22096,22097", "answer": "22098"}
{"prompt": "12488,12489,12490,12491,12492,12493", "answer": "12494"}
{"prompt": "3928,3929,3930", "answer": "3931"}
{"prompt": "24272,24273,24274,24275", "answer": "24276"}
{"prompt": "31038,31039,31040,31041,31042,31043,31044,31045", "answer": "31046"}
{"prompt": "10137,10138,10139,10140,10141,10142,10143,10144", "answer": "10145"}
{"prompt": "1911,1912,1913,1914,1915,1916,1917,1918,1919,1920", "answer": "1921"}
{"prompt": "43245", "answer": "43246"}
{"prompt": "1895,1896,1897,1898,1899,1900", "answer": "1901"}
{"prompt": "31362,31363,31364,31365,31366,31367,31368,31369", "answer": "31370"}
{"prompt": "41021,41022,41023,41024,41025,41026", "answer": "41027"}
{"prompt": "19200,19201,19202", "answer": "19203"}
{"prompt": "39351,39352,39353,39354,39355,39356,39357,39358,39359", "answer": "39360"}
{"prompt": "28505,28506,28507,28508,28509,28510,28511", "answer": "28512"}
{"prompt": "30199,30200,30201,30202,30203,30204,30205", "answer": "30206"}
{"prompt": "42455,42456,42457", "answer": "42458"}
{"prompt": "191,192", "answer": "193"}
{"prompt": "24994,24995,24996,24997,24998", "answer": "24999"}
{"prompt": "15108,15109,15110", "answer": "15111"}
{"prompt": "4680,4681,4682,4683,4684,4685,4686,4687,4688", "answer": "4689"}
{"prompt": "14714,14715,14716", "answer": "14717"}
{"prompt": "37548,37549,37550,37551,37552,37553,37554,37555", "answer": "37556"}
{"prompt": "28183,28184,28185,28186,28187,28188,28189,28190,28191,28192", "answer": "28193"}
{"prompt": "1864,1865,1866", "answer": "1867"}
{"prompt": "11016,11017,11018,11019,11020,11021,11022", "answer": "11023"}
{"prompt": "32715,32716,32717,32718,32719,32720", "answer": "32721"}
{"prompt": "21010,21011,21012,21013,21014,21015,21016", "answer": "21017"}
{"prompt": "33526,33527,33528,33529,33530,33531,33532,33533,33534", "answer": "33535"}
{"prompt": "20159,20160,20161,20162,20163,20164,20165", "answer": "20166"}
{"prompt": "23122,23123,23124,23125,23126,23127,23128", "answer": "23129"}
{"prompt": "4734,4735,4736", "answer": "4737"}
{"prompt": "38958,38959,38960,38961,38962,38963,38964,38965", "answer": "38966"}
{"prompt": "18990,18991,18992,18993,18994,18995,18996", "answer": "18997"}
{"prompt": "21537,21538,21539,21540,21541,21542", "answer": "21543"}
{"prompt": "9008,9009,9010", "answer": "9011"}
{"prompt": "38112,38113,38114,38115,38116,38117", "answer": "38118"}
{"prompt": "11310,11311,11312,11313,11314,11315,11316,11317,11318", "answer": "11319"}
{"prompt": "33807,33808,33809,33810,33811,33812,33813,33814,33815,33816", "answer": "33817"}
{"prompt": "22926,22927,22928,22929,22930,22931,22932,22933,22934,22935", "answer": "22936"}
{"prompt": "5220,5221,5222,5223,5224,5225,5226", "answer": "5227"}
{"prompt": "41531,41532,41533,41534,41535,41536,41537,41538,41539,41540", "answer": "41541"}
{"prompt": "3237,3238,3239", "answer": "3240"}
{"prompt": "15711,15712", "answer": "15713"}
{"prompt": "28643", "answer": "28644"}
{"prompt": "35668,35669", "answer": "35670"}
{"prompt": "40770,40771", "answer": "40772"}
{"prompt": "45165,45166,45167,45168,45169", "answer": "45170"}
{"prompt": "34026,34027,34028", "answer": "34029"}
{"prompt": "984,985,986,987,988,989,990", "answer": "991"}
{"prompt": "17113", "answer": "17114"}
{"prompt": "15356,15357,15358", "answer": "15359"}
{"prompt": "35832,35833,35834,35835,35836,35837,35838", "answer": "35839"}
{"prompt": "15685,15686,15687,15688,15689,15690,15691,15692,15693", "answer": "15694"}
{"prompt": "17287,17288,17289,17290,17291,17292,17293", "answer": "17294"}
{"prompt": "15938,15939,15940,15941,15942,15943,15944,15945,15946", "answer": "15947"}
{"prompt": "13285,13286,13287,13288", "answer": "13289"}
{"prompt": "17372,17373,17374,17375,17376,17377,17378", "answer": "17379"}
{"prompt": "13428,13429,13430,13431,13432,13433,13434,13435,13436", "answer": "13437"}
{"prompt": "26598,26599,26600,26601,26602,26603,26604", "answer": "26605"}
{"prompt": "25539,25540,25541,25542,25543,25544,25545,25546", "answer": "25547"}
{"prompt": "34786,34787,34788,34789,34790,34791,34792,34793", "answer": "34794"}
{"prompt": "18717,18718,18719,18720,18721,18722,18723", "answer": "18724"}
{"prompt": "11743,11744,11745,11746,11747,11748,11749,11750,11751", "answer": "11752"}
{"prompt": "25863,25864,25865", "answer": "25866"}
{"prompt": "16439,16440,16441,16442,16443,16444,16445,16446,16447,16448", "answer": "16449"}
{"prompt": "19474,19475,19476,19477,19478,19479,19480,19481,19482", "answer": "19483"}
{"prompt": "5161,5162,5163,5164", "answer": "5165"}
{"prompt": "37994,37995", "answer": "37996"}
{"prompt": "16244,16245,16246,16247,16248,16249,16250", "answer": "16251"}
{"prompt": "31177,31178,31179,31180,31181", "answer": "31182"}
{"prompt": "36348,36349,36350,36351,36352,36353,36354", "answer": "36355"}
{"prompt": "29211", "answer": "29212"}
{"prompt": "37706,37707,37708,37709,37710,37711,37712", "answer": "37713"}
{"prompt": "6795,6796,6797,6798", "answer": "6799"}
{"prompt": "20264,20265,20266,20267,20268,20269,20270,20271,20272", "answer": "20273"}
{"prompt": "17108,17109,17110,17111,17112,17113", "answer": "17114"}
{"prompt": "23437,23438,23439,23440,23441,23442,23443,23444,23445", "answer": "23446"}
{"prompt": "34490,34491,34492,34493,34494,34495", "answer": "34496"}
{"prompt": "37523,37524,37525,37526,37527,37528,37529,37530,37531,37532", "answer": "37533"}
{"prompt": "41183,41184,41185,41186,41187,41188,41189,41190,41191,41192", "answer": "41193"}
{"prompt": "3104,3105,3106,3107,3108,3109,3110,3111,3112", "answer": "3113"}
{"prompt": "42619,42620,42621,42622,42623,42624", "answer": "42625"}
{"prompt": "37144,37145,37146,37147,37148,37149,37150,37151,37152,37153", "answer": "37154"}
{"prompt": "36314", "answer": "36315"}
{"prompt": "20581,20582", "answer": "20583"}
{"prompt": "15550,15551,15552,15553,15554", "answer": "15555"}
{"prompt": "5044,5045,5046,5047,5048", "answer": "5049"}
{"prompt": "9292,9293,9294,9295,9296,9297,9298,9299,9300,9301", "answer": "9302"}
{"prompt": "7418,7419", "answer": "7420"}
{"prompt": "28674,28675,28676,28677,28678,28679,28680,28681", "answer": "28682"}
{"prompt": "25466", "answer": "25467"}
{"prompt": "5182,5183", "answer": "5184"}
{"prompt": "21440,21441,21442,21443,21444,21445,21446,21447,21448,21449", "answer": "21450"}
{"prompt": "30059,30060", "answer": "30061"}
{"prompt": "40365,40366,40367", "answer": "40368"}
{"prompt": "32636,32637,32638,32639,32640,32641", "answer": "32642"}
{"prompt": "25277,25278,25279,25280,25281,25282,25283,25284,25285", "answer": "25286"}
{"prompt": "16204,16205,16206,16207,16208", "answer": "16209"}
{"prompt": "20957,20958,20959,20960,20961,20962,20963,20964,20965", "answer": "20966"}
{"prompt": "6419,6420,6421", "answer": "6422"}
{"prompt": "11645,11646,11647,11648,11649,11650,11651,11652,11653", "answer": "11654"}
{"prompt": "22187,22188,22189,22190,22191,22192,22193", "answer": "22194"}
{"prompt": "11305,11306,11307,11308", "answer": "11309"}
{"prompt": "34296,34297,34298,34299,34300,34301,34302,34303", "answer": "34304"}
{"prompt": "9754,9755,9756,9757,9758,9759,9760,9761,9762", "answer": "9763"}
{"prompt": "33272,33273,33274,33275", "answer": "33276"}
{"prompt": "3595,3596,3597,3598,3599,3600,3601,3602", "answer": "3603"}
{"prompt": "33701,33702,33703,33704,33705,33706,33707", "answer": "33708"}
{"prompt": "36047,36048,36049,36050", "answer": "36051"}
{"prompt": "14965", "answer": "14966"}
{"prompt": "15768,15769,15770,15771,15772", "answer": "15773"}
{"prompt": "14539,14540", "answer": "14541"}
{"prompt": "23757,23758,23759,23760", "answer": "23761"}
{"prompt": "25262,25263,25264,25265,25266,25267,25268,25269", "answer": "25270"}
{"prompt": "30382,30383,30384,30385,30386,30387,30388,30389,30390", "answer": "30391"}
{"prompt": "9254,9255,9256,9257", "answer": "9258"}
{"prompt": "13312,13313,13314,13315,13316,13317,13318,13319,13320,13321", "answer": "13322"}
{"prompt": "34705,34706,34707,34708,34709,34710", "answer": "34711"}
{"prompt": "17566,17567,17568,17569,17570,17571,17572", "answer": "17573"}
{"prompt": "1126", "answer": "1127"}
{"prompt": "37275,37276,37277,37278,37279,37280", "answer": "37281"}
{"prompt": "10907,10908,10909,10910,10911,10912,10913,10914,10915", "answer": "10916"}
{"prompt": "2922,2923,2924", "answer": "2925"}
{"prompt": "38890,38891,38892,38893,38894,38895,38896,38897,38898,38899", "answer": "38900"}
{"prompt": "21730,21731,21732", "answer": "21733"}
{"prompt": "43850,43851", "answer": "43852"}
{"prompt": "7319,7320,7321,7322,7323,7324,7325,7326,7327,7328", "answer": "7329"}
{"prompt": "27345,27346,27347,27348", "answer": "27349"}
{"prompt": "5297,5298,5299", "answer": "5300"}
{"prompt": "10161,10162,10163,10164,10165,10166,10167,10168,10169", "answer": "10170"}
{"prompt": "26622,26623,26624,26625,26626,26627", "answer": "26628"}
{"prompt": "3125,3126,3127,3128,3129,3130,3131,3132,3133", "answer": "3134"}
{"prompt": "40864,40865,40866,40867,40868,40869,40870,40871", "answer": "40872"}
{"prompt": "43723,43724,43725,43726,43727,43728,43729,43730", "answer": "43731"}
{"prompt": "45244,45245,45246,45247,45248,45249,45250,45251", "answer": "45252"}
{"prompt": "28729,28730,28731,28732", "answer": "28733"}
{"prompt": "42784,42785", "answer": "42786"}
{"prompt": "24850,24851,24852,24853,24854", "answer": "24855"}
{"prompt": "18654,18655,18656,18657,18658,18659", "answer": "18660"}
{"prompt": "32020,32021,32022,32023,32024,32025,32026", "answer": "32027"}
{"prompt": "29309,29310,29311,29312,29313,29314,29315,29316,29317,29318", "answer": "29319"}
{"prompt": "10609,10610,10611", "answer": "10612"}
{"prompt": "44872,44873,44874,44875,44876,44877,44878,44879", "answer": "44880"}
{"prompt": "13123,13124,13125,13126,13127", "answer": "13128"}
{"prompt": "5124", "answer": "5125"}
{"prompt": "39548,39549,39550", "answer": "39551"}
{"prompt": "1747,1748,1749,1750,1751,1752,1753", "answer": "1754"}
{"prompt": "11,12,13", "answer": "14"}
{"prompt": "36785,36786,36787,36788,36789,36790,36791", "answer": "36792"}
{"prompt": "24657,24658,24659", "answer": "24660"}
{"prompt": "43928,43929,43930,43931,43932,43933,43934,43935", "answer": "43936"}
{"prompt": "38378", "answer": "38379"}
{"prompt": "156,157,158,159,160,161,162,163,164,165", "answer": "166"}
{"prompt": "11460,11461,11462,11463,11464,11465,11466", "answer": "11467"}
{"prompt": "18119,18120,18121,18122,18123", "answer": "18124"}
{"prompt": "1859", "answer": "1860"}
{"prompt": "4581,4582,4583,4584,4585,4586,4587,4588,4589", "answer": "4590"}
{"prompt": "22039,22040,22041,22042,22043,22044,22045", "answer": "22046"}
{"prompt": "30914", "answer": "30915"}
{"prompt": "10606,10607", "answer": "10608"}
{"prompt": "42866,42867,42868,42869,42870,42871,42872", "answer": "42873"}
{"prompt": "1455,1456,1457,1458,1459", "answer": "1460"}
{"prompt": "16855,16856,16857,16858,16859,16860,16861", "answer": "16862"}
{"prompt": "549,550,551,552,553,554,555,556,557", "answer": "558"}
{"prompt": "41357,41358,41359,41360,41361,41362,41363,41364,41365,41366", "answer": "41367"}
{"prompt": "42746,42747", "answer": "42748"}
{"prompt": "2302,2303,2304,2305,2306,2307,2308", "answer": "2309"}
{"prompt": "40940,40941", "answer": "40942"}
{"prompt": "18069,18070,18071,18072,18073,18074,18075", "answer": "18076"}
{"prompt": "11369,11370,11371", "answer": "11372"}
{"prompt": "6029,6030,6031,6032,6033,6034", "answer": "6035"}
{"prompt": "37347,37348,37349,37350,37351,37352,37353", "answer": "37354"}
{"prompt": "20726,20727", "answer": "20728"}
{"prompt": "23247,23248,23249,23250,23251", "answer": "23252"}
{"prompt": "10862", "answer": "10863"}
{"prompt": "36044,36045", "answer": "36046"}
{"prompt": "19357,19358,19359", "answer": "19360"}
{"prompt": "43227,43228,43229,43230,43231", "answer": "43232"}
{"prompt": "25361,25362,25363,25364,25365,25366,25367,25368,25369,25370", "answer": "25371"}
{"prompt": "17279,17280,17281,17282,17283,17284,17285,17286,17287", "answer": "17288"}
{"prompt": "40670", "answer": "40671"}
{"prompt": "25556,25557,25558,25559,25560,25561,25562,25563,25564,25565", "answer": "25566"}
{"prompt": "34495,34496,34497", "answer": "34498"}
{"prompt": "42600,42601,42602,42603,42604", "answer": "42605"}
{"prompt": "43626", "answer": "43627"}
{"prompt": "36127", "answer": "36128"}
{"prompt": "4052,4053", "answer": "4054"}
{"prompt": "10807,10808,10809,10810", "answer": "10811"}
{"prompt": "12994,12995,12996,12997,12998,12999,13000,13001", "answer": "13002"}
{"prompt": "29597,29598,29599,29600,29601,29602,29603", "answer": "29604"}
{"prompt": "29609,29610,29611,29612,29613,29614,29615,29616,29617,29618", "answer": "29619"}
{"prompt": "36094,36095,36096", "answer": "36097"}
{"prompt": "21033", "answer": "21034"}
{"prompt": "16902,16903,16904,16905,16906,16907,16908,16909", "answer": "16910"}
{"prompt": "29732,29733,29734,29735,29736,29737,29738", "answer": "29739"}
{"prompt": "16112,16113,16114", "answer": "16115"}
{"prompt": "4556,4557,4558,4559,4560,4561,4562,4563,4564", "answer": "4565"}
{"prompt": "22807,22808,22809,22810,22811,22812,22813,22814,22815", "answer": "22816"}
{"prompt": "31182,31183", "answer": "31184"}
{"prompt": "12839,12840,12841,12842", "answer": "12843"}
{"prompt": "26175,26176,26177,26178,26179", "answer": "26180"}
{"prompt": "19254,19255,19256,19257,19258,19259", "answer": "19260"}
{"prompt": "21501,21502,21503,21504,21505,21506,21507,21508,21509,21510", "answer": "21511"}
{"prompt": "1459,1460,1461", "answer": "1462"}
{"prompt": "7082", "answer": "7083"}
{"prompt": "11592,11593", "answer": "11594"}
{"prompt": "10362,10363,10364,10365,10366,10367,10368,10369", "answer": "10370"}
{"prompt": "35184,35185,35186,35187,35188,35189,35190", "answer": "35191"}
{"prompt": "37780,37781,37782,37783,37784,37785,37786,37787,37788,37789", "answer": "37790"}
{"prompt": "21884,21885", "answer": "21886"}
{"prompt": "14670,14671,14672,14673,14674,14675,14676,14677", "answer": "14678"}
{"prompt": "12398,12399,12400,12401,12402,12403,12404", "answer": "12405"}
{"prompt": "40771,40772,40773,40774,40775", "answer": "40776"}
{"prompt": "13079", "answer": "13080"}
{"prompt": "25285,25286,25287,25288,25289,25290", "answer": "25291"}
{"prompt": "33930,33931", "answer": "33932"}
{"prompt": "9932,9933,9934,9935", "answer": "9936"}
{"prompt": "6486,6487,6488,6489,6490,6491,6492,6493,6494", "answer": "6495"}
{"prompt": "19500,19501,19502,19503", "answer": "19504"}
{"prompt": "32641,32642,32643,32644,32645,32646,32647,32648,32649", "answer": "32650"}
{"prompt": "35692,35693,35694,35695,35696,35697,35698,35699,35700,35701", "answer": "35702"}
{"prompt": "36769,36770,36771,36772,36773,36774,36775,36776", "answer": "36777"}
{"prompt": "16708,16709,16710,16711,16712", "answer": "16713"}
{"prompt": "34022,34023,34024,34025,34026", "answer": "34027"}
{"prompt": "33507,33508,33509,33510,33511,33512,33513,33514,33515", "answer": "33516"}
{"prompt": "20233,20234,20235,20236", "answer": "20237"}
{"prompt": "25272,25273,25274,25275,25276,25277", "answer": "25278"}
{"prompt": "23388", "answer": "23389"}
{"prompt": "42861,42862,42863,42864,42865,42866", "answer": "42867"}
{"prompt": "10279,10280,10281,10282,10283,10284,10285,10286,10287,10288", "answer": "10289"}
{"prompt": "37893,37894,37895,37896,37897,37898,37899,37900", "answer": "37901"}
{"prompt": "3959,3960,3961,3962,3963,3964,3965,3966", "answer": "3967"}
{"prompt": "23827,23828,23829,23830,23831,23832,23833,23834,23835,23836", "answer": "23837"}
{"prompt": "41644,41645,41646,41647,41648,41649,41650,41651,41652,41653", "answer": "41654"}
{"prompt": "40618,40619,40620,40621", "answer": "40622"}
{"prompt": "34312,34313,34314,34315,34316,34317", "answer": "34318"}
{"prompt": "42262,42263,42264,42265", "answer": "42266"}
{"prompt": "3267,3268,3269,3270,3271,3272,3273,3274,3275,3276", "answer": "3277"}
{"prompt": "43764,43765,43766,43767,43768", "answer": "43769"}
{"prompt": "7689,7690,7691,7692,7693", "answer": "7694"}
{"prompt": "13487,13488,13489", "answer": "13490"}
{"prompt": "16029,16030,16031,16032,16033,16034,16035,16036,16037,16038", "answer": "16039"}
{"prompt": "36273,36274,36275,36276", "answer": "36277"}
{"prompt": "25943,25944,25945,25946,25947,25948", "answer": "25949"}
{"prompt": "27659,27660,27661,27662,27663", "answer": "27664"}
{"prompt": "21425,21426,21427,21428,21429,21430", "answer": "21431"}
{"prompt": "9074,9075,9076,9077,9078", "answer": "9079"}
{"prompt": "1084,1085,1086,1087", "answer": "1088"}
{"prompt": "42102", "answer": "42103"}
{"prompt": "13413,13414,13415,13416,13417,13418", "answer": "13419"}
{"prompt": "5266,5267,5268", "answer": "5269"}
{"prompt": "37010,37011,37012,37013,37014,37015,37016", "answer": "37017"}
{"prompt": "24633,24634,24635,24636,24637,24638,24639", "answer": "24640"}
{"prompt": "40963,40964,40965,40966,40967,40968,40969", "answer": "40970"}
{"prompt": "31928,31929,31930,31931,31932,31933,31934,31935,31936", "answer": "31937"}
{"prompt": "15358,15359,15360,15361,15362", "answer": "15363"}
{"prompt": "36461,36462,36463,36464,36465", "answer": "36466"}
{"prompt": "5482,5483,5484,5485,5486,5487", "answer": "5488"}
{"prompt": "723,724,725,726,727,728,729,730,731", "answer": "732"}
{"prompt": "23875,23876,23877,23878,23879,23880", "answer": "23881"}
{"prompt": "27162,27163,27164,27165", "answer": "27166"}
{"prompt": "43891", "answer": "43892"}
{"prompt": "25569,25570,25571,25572,25573,25574", "answer": "25575"}
{"prompt": "10130,10131,10132,10133,10134", "answer": "10135"}
{"prompt": "4158,4159,4160,4161,4162,4163", "answer": "4164"}
{"prompt": "17982,17983,17984,17985,17986,17987,17988,17989", "answer": "17990"}
{"prompt": "22137,22138,22139,22140", "answer": "22141"}
{"prompt": "41014,41015,41016,41017", "answer": "41018"}
{"prompt": "33627,33628,33629,33630,33631,33632", "answer": "33633"}
{"prompt": "32238,32239,32240,32241,32242,32243", "answer": "32244"}
{"prompt": "31967,31968,31969,31970", "answer": "31971"}
{"prompt": "24796,24797,24798,24799", "answer": "24800"}
{"prompt": "28928,28929,28930,28931,28932,28933,28934,28935", "answer": "28936"}
{"prompt": "19193,19194,19195,19196,19197,19198,19199,19200", "answer": "19201"}
{"prompt": "33228,33229,33230", "answer": "33231"}
{"prompt": "12493,12494,12495,12496,12497", "answer": "12498"}
{"prompt": "26491,26492,26493,26494,26495,26496,26497,26498", "answer": "26499"}
{"prompt": "11269,11270,11271,11272,11273,11274,11275,11276,11277,11278", "answer": "11279"}
{"prompt": "13234,13235,13236,13237", "answer": "13238"}
{"prompt": "30967", "answer": "30968"}
{"prompt": "472,473,474,475,476,477,478,479,480", "answer": "481"}
{"prompt": "42543,42544,42545,42546,42547,42548,42549", "answer": "42550"}
{"prompt": "42887", "answer": "42888"}
{"prompt": "9429,9430,9431,9432,9433,9434,9435,9436,9437,9438", "answer": "9439"}
{"prompt": "18059,18060,18061,18062", "answer": "18063"}
{"prompt": "24782,24783,24784,24785", "answer": "24786"}
{"prompt": "9585,9586,9587,9588,9589,9590,9591", "answer": "9592"}
{"prompt": "20262,20263,20264", "answer": "20265"}
{"prompt": "36860,36861,36862,36863,36864,36865,36866,36867", "answer": "36868"}
{"prompt": "13142,13143,13144,13145,13146,13147,13148,13149", "answer": "13150"}
{"prompt": "27409,27410,27411,27412,27413,27414,27415", "answer": "27416"}
{"prompt": "38379,38380,38381,38382,38383,38384,38385", "answer": "38386"}
{"prompt": "16821,16822,16823,16824,16825", "answer": "16826"}
{"prompt": "12574,12575", "answer": "12576"}
{"prompt": "27449,27450,27451,27452,27453,27454,27455", "answer": "27456"}
{"prompt": "30042,30043,30044", "answer": "30045"}
{"prompt": "22666,22667,22668,22669,22670,22671,22672,22673,22674,22675", "answer": "22676"}
{"prompt": "7432,7433,7434,7435,7436,7437,7438,7439,7440", "answer": "7441"}
{"prompt": "6966,6967,6968,6969,6970", "answer": "6971"}
{"prompt": "41179,41180,41181,41182,41183", "answer": "41184"}
{"prompt": "12539,12540,12541", "answer": "12542"}
{"prompt": "16946,16947,16948,16949,16950,16951", "answer": "16952"}
{"prompt": "40006,40007,40008,40009,40010,40011,40012,40013", "answer": "40014"}
{"prompt": "1218,1219,1220,1221,1222,1223,1224,1225,1226", "answer": "1227"}
{"prompt": "3309,3310,3311,3312,3313,3314,3315,3316", "answer": "3317"}
{"prompt": "8131,8132,8133,8134,8135,8136,8137,8138", "answer": "8139"}
{"prompt": "35179,35180,35181,35182,35183,35184", "answer": "35185"}
{"prompt": "43730", "answer": "43731"}
{"prompt": "36391,36392,36393,36394,36395,36396,36397,36398,36399,36400", "answer": "36401"}
{"prompt": "45,46,47,48,49,50,51,52,53", "answer": "54"}
{"prompt": "44327,44328", "answer": "44329"}
{"prompt": "43899,43900,43901,43902", "answer": "43903"}
{"prompt": "689,690,691,692,693,694", "answer": "695"}
{"prompt": "43567,43568,43569", "answer": "43570"}
{"prompt": "5699,5700,5701", "answer": "5702"}
{"prompt": "37880,37881,37882,37883,37884,37885,37886,37887,37888", "answer": "37889"}
{"prompt": "13333,13334,13335,13336,13337,13338,13339,13340", "answer": "13341"}
{"prompt": "1489,1490,1491,1492,1493,1494,1495,1496,1497", "answer": "1498"}
{"prompt": "24939,24940", "answer": "24941"}
{"prompt": "31921,31922,31923,31924", "answer": "31925"}
{"prompt": "35358,35359,35360,35361,35362,35363,35364,35365,35366,35367", "answer": "35368"}
{"prompt": "894,895,896,897", "answer": "898"}
{"prompt": "38881,38882,38883,38884,38885,38886,38887,38888", "answer": "38889"}
{"prompt": "33931,33932,33933,33934,33935", "answer": "33936"}
{"prompt": "24820,24821,24822,24823,24824", "answer": "24825"}
{"prompt": "14106", "answer": "14107"}
{"prompt": "12482,12483,12484,12485,12486,12487,12488", "answer": "12489"}
{"prompt": "38159,38160", "answer": "38161"}
{"prompt": "23499,23500,23501,23502,23503,23504,23505,23506,23507,23508", "answer": "23509"}
{"prompt": "12738,12739,12740,12741,12742,12743,12744,12745,12746", "answer": "12747"}
{"prompt": "17732,17733,17734,17735,17736,17737,17738,17739", "answer": "17740"}
{"prompt": "22720,22721,22722,22723,22724,22725,22726", "answer": "22727"}
{"prompt": "35499", "answer": "35500"}
{"prompt": "13917", "answer": "13918"}
{"prompt": "6996,6997", "answer": "6998"}
{"prompt": "45186,45187,45188,45189,45190,45191,45192,45193,45194", "answer": "45195"}
{"prompt": "37406,37407,37408,37409,37410,37411", "answer": "37412"}
{"prompt": "21367", "answer": "21368"}
{"prompt": "25913,25914,25915,25916,25917,25918,25919,25920", "answer": "25921"}
{"prompt": "15242,15243,15244,15245,15246,15247,15248,15249,15250", "answer": "15251"}
{"prompt": "12799,12800", "answer": "12801"}
{"prompt": "15384,15385,15386,15387", "answer": "15388"}
{"prompt": "36874,36875,36876,36877", "answer": "36878"}
{"prompt": "19887,19888,19889,19890,19891", "answer": "19892"}
{"prompt": "16366,16367,16368,16369", "answer": "16370"}
{"prompt": "7537,7538,7539,7540,7541,7542,7543,7544", "answer": "7545"}
{"prompt": "29329,29330,29331,29332,29333,29334,29335,29336", "answer": "29337"}
{"prompt": "29242,29243,29244,29245,29246,29247,29248,29249,29250,29251", "answer": "29252"}
{"prompt": "30268,30269,30270,30271,30272,30273,30274,30275,30276", "answer": "30277"}
{"prompt": "16831,16832", "answer": "16833"}
{"prompt": "20457,20458,20459,20460,20461", "answer": "20462"}
{"prompt": "7514,7515,7516,7517", "answer": "7518"}
{"prompt": "4877,4878,4879,4880", "answer": "4881"}
{"prompt": "17743,17744,17745,17746,17747,17748", "answer": "17749"}
{"prompt": "19724", "answer": "19725"}
{"prompt": "2575,2576,2577,2578", "answer": "2579"}
{"prompt": "37580,37581,37582,37583,37584,37585,37586,37587,37588,37589", "answer": "37590"}
{"prompt": "8554,8555,8556,8557,8558,8559,8560", "answer": "8561"}
{"prompt": "16337", "answer": "16338"}
{"prompt": "8231,8232,8233,8234,8235,8236", "answer": "8237"}
{"prompt": "18493,18494,18495,18496,18497", "answer": "18498"}
{"prompt": "3659", "answer": "3660"}
{"prompt": "8111,8112,8113,8114,8115,8116", "answer": "8117"}
{"prompt": "32300,32301,32302,32303", "answer": "32304"}
{"prompt": "36768,36769", "answer": "36770"}
{"prompt": "20492", "answer": "20493"}
{"prompt": "13262,13263,13264,13265,13266,13267,13268", "answer": "13269"}
{"prompt": "43531,43532", "answer": "43533"}
{"prompt": "14262,14263,14264,14265,14266,14267", "answer": "14268"}
{"prompt": "21837,21838,21839", "answer": "21840"}
{"prompt": "14583,14584,14585,14586,14587", "answer": "14588"}
{"prompt": "31561", "answer": "31562"}
{"prompt": "28579", "answer": "28580"}
{"prompt": "3609,3610,3611,3612,3613,3614,3615,3616", "answer": "3617"}
{"prompt": "7283,7284,7285", "answer": "7286"}
{"prompt": "27602,27603,27604,27605,27606,27607,27608,27609", "answer": "27610"}
{"prompt": "20242,20243,20244,20245,20246,20247,20248,20249,20250,20251", "answer": "20252"}
{"prompt": "32902,32903,32904,32905,32906,32907,32908,32909,32910", "answer": "32911"}
{"prompt": "3904,3905,3906,3907,3908,3909,3910", "answer": "3911"}
{"prompt": "41301,41302,41303,41304,41305,41306,41307,41308,41309", "answer": "41310"}
{"prompt": "44980", "answer": "44981"}
{"prompt": "40386,40387,40388", "answer": "40389"}
{"prompt": "39922,39923,39924,39925,39926", "answer": "39927"}
{"prompt": "11278", "answer": "11279"}
{"prompt": "15826,15827", "answer": "15828"}
{"prompt": "32153,32154,32155,32156,32157,32158,32159", "answer": "32160"}
{"prompt": "26439,26440,26441,26442,26443,26444,26445,26446,26447,26448", "answer": "26449"}
{"prompt": "6231,6232,6233,6234,6235,6236", "answer": "6237"}
{"prompt": "8780,8781,8782", "answer": "8783"}
{"prompt": "19666,19667,19668,19669,19670,19671,19672,19673", "answer": "19674"}
{"prompt": "26261,26262,26263,26264,26265,26266,26267", "answer": "26268"}
{"prompt": "33752,33753,33754,33755,33756,33757", "answer": "33758"}
{"prompt": "39884,39885,39886,39887,39888", "answer": "39889"}
{"prompt": "2008,2009,2010,2011,2012", "answer": "2013"}
{"prompt": "19754,19755,19756,19757,19758,19759,19760,19761,19762,19763", "answer": "19764"}
{"prompt": "14080,14081", "answer": "14082"}
{"prompt": "34354,34355", "answer": "34356"}
{"prompt": "1168,1169,1170", "answer": "1171"}
{"prompt": "17876,17877,17878,17879,17880,17881,17882", "answer": "17883"}
{"prompt": "8172,8173,8174,8175,8176", "answer": "8177"}
{"prompt": "43026,43027,43028,43029,43030,43031,43032,43033,43034,43035", "answer": "43036"}
{"prompt": "34358,34359,34360", "answer": "34361"}
{"prompt": "11051,11052,11053,11054,11055,11056,11057,11058,11059", "answer": "11060"}
{"prompt": "7610,7611,7612,7613,7614,7615,7616,7617,7618", "answer": "7619"}
{"prompt": "22893,22894,22895", "answer": "22896"}
{"prompt": "12298,12299,12300,12301", "answer": "12302"}
{"prompt": "44685,44686,44687,44688,44689,44690,44691,44692", "answer": "44693"}
{"prompt": "20627,20628,20629,20630,20631,20632", "answer": "20633"}
{"prompt": "5105,5106,5107,5108,5109,5110,5111", "answer": "5112"}
{"prompt": "45135,45136", "answer": "45137"}
{"prompt": "45079,45080,45081,45082,45083,45084,45085", "answer": "45086"}
{"prompt": "15215,15216,15217", "answer": "15218"}
{"prompt": "33730,33731,33732,33733", "answer": "33734"}
{"prompt": "38307,38308,38309", "answer": "38310"}
{"prompt": "27119,27120,27121", "answer": "27122"}
{"prompt": "16277,16278,16279,16280,16281,16282", "answer": "16283"}
{"prompt": "9698,9699,9700", "answer": "9701"}
{"prompt": "7853,7854,7855,7856,7857,7858,7859,7860,7861", "answer": "7862"}
{"prompt": "37541,37542,37543,37544,37545,37546,37547,37548", "answer": "37549"}
{"prompt": "11548,11549,11550,11551,11552,11553,11554,11555,11556", "answer": "11557"}
{"prompt": "33852,33853,33854,33855,33856,33857,33858,33859,33860,33861", "answer": "33862"}
{"prompt": "23238,23239,23240,23241,23242,23243,23244,23245,23246,23247", "answer": "23248"}
{"prompt": "44759,44760,44761,44762,44763,44764,44765,44766", "answer": "44767"}
{"prompt": "15597,15598,15599,15600,15601,15602,15603,15604,15605", "answer": "15606"}
{"prompt": "25358,25359,25360,25361", "answer": "25362"}
{"prompt": "7780,7781", "answer": "7782"}
{"prompt": "36340,36341,36342,36343,36344,36345,36346,36347,36348", "answer": "36349"}
{"prompt": "14138,14139,14140,14141,14142,14143,14144,14145", "answer": "14146"}
{"prompt": "41931,41932,41933,41934,41935,41936", "answer": "41937"}
{"prompt": "34833,34834,34835,34836,34837,34838,34839", "answer": "34840"}
{"prompt": "39488,39489,39490,39491,39492,39493,39494,39495,39496,39497", "answer": "39498"}
{"prompt": "930,931,932,933,934,935,936,937,938,939", "answer": "940"}
{"prompt": "15851,15852,15853,15854,15855,15856,15857", "answer": "15858"}
{"prompt": "4456,4457,4458", "answer": "4459"}
{"prompt": "36838,36839", "answer": "36840"}
{"prompt": "5581,5582,5583,5584,5585,5586,5587,5588,5589", "answer": "5590"}
{"prompt": "5748,5749,5750,5751,5752,5753,5754", "answer": "5755"}
{"prompt": "15394,15395,15396,15397,15398,15399", "answer": "15400"}
{"prompt": "18007,18008,18009,18010,18011,18012,18013,18014,18015", "answer": "18016"}
{"prompt": "26326,26327,26328,26329,26330,26331,26332,26333,26334", "answer": "26335"}
{"prompt": "6131,6132,6133,6134,6135,6136,6137,6138,6139", "answer": "6140"}
{"prompt": "22010,22011,22012,22013,22014,22015,22016,22017,22018", "answer": "22019"}
{"prompt": "19534,19535,19536,19537,19538,19539,19540", "answer": "19541"}
{"prompt": "6803,6804,6805", "answer": "6806"}
{"prompt": "41348,41349,41350,41351", "answer": "41352"}
{"prompt": "36000,36001,36002,36003", "answer": "36004"}
{"prompt": "24034,24035,24036,24037,24038,24039,24040", "answer": "24041"}
{"prompt": "42383,42384,42385,42386", "answer": "42387"}
{"prompt": "36505,36506,36507,36508,36509,36510,36511,36512", "answer": "36513"}
{"prompt": "35603,35604", "answer": "35605"}
{"prompt": "17868,17869,17870,17871,17872,17873,17874,17875,17876", "answer": "17877"}
{"prompt": "9090,9091,9092,9093,9094,9095,9096", "answer": "9097"}
{"prompt": "33293,33294,33295", "answer": "33296"}
{"prompt": "30938,30939,30940,30941,30942,30943", "answer": "30944"}
{"prompt": "11092,11093,11094,11095,11096,11097,11098", "answer": "11099"}
{"prompt": "41093,41094", "answer": "41095"}
{"prompt": "39738,39739,39740,39741,39742,39743,39744", "answer": "39745"}
{"prompt": "8912", "answer": "8913"}
{"prompt": "40159,40160", "answer": "40161"}
{"prompt": "41834,41835,41836", "answer": "41837"}
{"prompt": "12746,12747,12748,12749", "answer": "12750"}
{"prompt": "40570,40571,40572,40573", "answer": "40574"}
{"prompt": "28330,28331,28332,28333,28334,28335,28336,28337,28338", "answer": "28339"}
{"prompt": "24605,24606,24607,24608,24609,24610,24611,24612,24613", "answer": "24614"}
{"prompt": "19524,19525,19526,19527,19528,19529,19530,19531,19532,19533", "answer": "19534"}
{"prompt": "5575,5576", "answer": "5577"}
{"prompt": "42403,42404", "answer": "42405"}
{"prompt": "3535,3536,3537,3538,3539,3540", "answer": "3541"}
{"prompt": "8221", "answer": "8222"}
{"prompt": "3133,3134,3135,3136,3137,3138,3139,3140", "answer": "3141"}
{"prompt": "19242", "answer": "19243"}
{"prompt": "3866", "answer": "3867"}
{"prompt": "326,327,328,329,330,331,332,333,334", "answer": "335"}
{"prompt": "27511,27512,27513,27514,27515,27516,27517", "answer": "27518"}
{"prompt": "41257,41258,41259,41260,41261,41262,41263", "answer": "41264"}
{"prompt": "6535,6536,6537,6538,6539", "answer": "6540"}
{"prompt": "12737,12738", "answer": "12739"}
{"prompt": "16825,16826,16827,16828", "answer": "16829"}
{"prompt": "32477", "answer": "32478"}
{"prompt": "24100,24101,24102,24103,24104", "answer": "24105"}
{"prompt": "7817,7818,7819,7820,7821,7822,7823,7824,7825,7826", "answer": "7827"}
{"prompt": "10406", "answer": "10407"}
{"prompt": "41785,41786,41787,41788,41789,41790,41791,41792,41793,41794", "answer": "41795"}
{"prompt": "3525,3526,3527,3528", "answer": "3529"}
{"prompt": "16655,16656,16657,16658,16659,16660", "answer": "16661"}
{"prompt": "2064,2065,2066,2067,2068,2069,2070", "answer": "2071"}
{"prompt": "7664,7665,7666,7667,7668,7669,7670,7671,7672", "answer": "7673"}
{"prompt": "38492", "answer": "38493"}
{"prompt": "9019,9020,9021,9022,9023,9024,9025,9026,9027,9028", "answer": "9029"}
{"prompt": "36748", "answer": "36749"}
{"prompt": "39870,39871,39872,39873,39874,39875", "answer": "39876"}
{"prompt": "22185,22186,22187", "answer": "22188"}
{"prompt": "39109", "answer": "39110"}
{"prompt": "3466,3467", "answer": "3468"}
{"prompt": "36779,36780,36781,36782,36783", "answer": "36784"}
{"prompt": "40610,40611,40612,40613,40614,40615,40616,40617,40618", "answer": "40619"}
{"prompt": "5883,5884,5885,5886,5887,5888", "answer": "5889"}
{"prompt": "29928,29929,29930,29931", "answer": "29932"}
{"prompt": "25757,25758,25759,25760,25761,25762,25763,25764,25765", "answer": "25766"}
{"prompt": "23655,23656,23657,23658,23659", "answer": "23660"}
{"prompt": "20388,20389,20390,20391", "answer": "20392"}
{"prompt": "22378,22379,22380,22381,22382,22383,22384,22385", "answer": "22386"}
{"prompt": "31049,31050,31051,31052,31053,31054,31055", "answer": "31056"}
{"prompt": "7058,7059,7060,7061,7062,7063,7064,7065", "answer": "7066"}
{"prompt": "34984,34985,34986", "answer": "34987"}
{"prompt": "41582,41583,41584,41585,41586,41587,41588", "answer": "41589"}
{"prompt": "1136,1137,1138,1139,1140,1141,1142,1143", "answer": "1144"}
{"prompt": "25145,25146,25147,25148", "answer": "25149"}
{"prompt": "41902,41903,41904,41905,41906,41907,41908,41909,41910", "answer": "41911"}
{"prompt": "2697", "answer": "2698"}
{"prompt": "30116,30117,30118,30119,30120,30121,30122", "answer": "30123"}
{"prompt": "9805", "answer": "9806"}
{"prompt": "21107,21108,21109,21110,21111,21112,21113,21114,21115", "answer": "21116"}
{"prompt": "34392,34393,34394,34395,34396,34397,34398", "answer": "34399"}
{"prompt": "307,308,309", "answer": "310"}
{"prompt": "1248,1249,1250,1251,1252,1253,1254,1255,1256,1257", "answer": "1258"}
{"prompt": "21153,21154,21155,21156,21157", "answer": "21158"}
{"prompt": "1516,1517", "answer": "1518"}
{"prompt": "17551,17552,17553,17554,17555,17556,17557,17558,17559", "answer": "17560"}
{"prompt": "28596,28597,28598,28599,28600,28601,28602,28603,28604,28605", "answer": "28606"}
{"prompt": "24403,24404,24405,24406,24407,24408,24409,24410,24411", "answer": "24412"}
{"prompt": "41927,41928,41929,41930", "answer": "41931"}
{"prompt": "33758,33759,33760,33761,33762,33763,33764,33765,33766,33767", "answer": "33768"}
{"prompt": "44039,44040,44041,44042,44043,44044,44045,44046,44047", "answer": "44048"}
{"prompt": "8848,8849,8850,8851,8852,8853,8854,8855", "answer": "8856"}
{"prompt": "31472,31473,31474,31475,31476,31477,31478,31479", "answer": "31480"}
{"prompt": "20378,20379,20380,20381,20382", "answer": "20383"}
{"prompt": "3450,3451,3452,3453,3454", "answer": "3455"}
{"prompt": "37134,37135,37136", "answer": "37137"}
{"prompt": "36785", "answer": "36786"}
{"prompt": "3636,3637,3638,3639,3640,3641,3642", "answer": "3643"}
{"prompt": "14777,14778,14779,14780,14781,14782,14783,14784", "answer": "14785"}
{"prompt": "14844,14845,14846,14847,14848,14849,14850,14851,14852,14853", "answer": "14854"}
{"prompt": "23890,23891,23892,23893,23894,23895,23896,23897", "answer": "23898"}
{"prompt": "23708", "answer": "23709"}
{"prompt": "32445,32446,32447", "answer": "32448"}
{"prompt": "31504", "answer": "31505"}
{"prompt": "5553,5554,5555,5556,5557,5558,5559,5560", "answer": "5561"}
{"prompt": "20641", "answer": "20642"}
{"prompt": "7681,7682", "answer": "7683"}
{"prompt": "43091,43092,43093,43094,43095,43096", "answer": "43097"}
{"prompt": "15829,15830", "answer": "15831"}
{"prompt": "39187,39188,39189,39190,39191,39192,39193", "answer": "39194"}
{"prompt": "28819,28820,28821,28822,28823,28824", "answer": "28825"}
{"prompt": "4909,4910", "answer": "4911"}
{"prompt": "17250,17251,17252,17253,17254", "answer": "17255"}
{"prompt": "24002,24003,24004,24005,24006,24007,24008,24009", "answer": "24010"}
{"prompt": "34629,34630,34631,34632,34633,34634,34635", "answer": "34636"}
{"prompt": "15932,15933,15934,15935,15936,15937,15938", "answer": "15939"}
{"prompt": "24558,24559,24560,24561,24562,24563,24564,24565,24566,24567", "answer": "24568"}
{"prompt": "40722,40723,40724,40725,40726,40727", "answer": "40728"}
{"prompt": "23760,23761,23762,23763,23764,23765,23766", "answer": "23767"}
{"prompt": "688", "answer": "689"}
{"prompt": "9081,9082,9083,9084,9085,9086,9087,9088,9089,9090", "answer": "9091"}
{"prompt": "23452,23453,23454,23455,23456", "answer": "23457"}
{"prompt": "10878,10879,10880,10881", "answer": "10882"}
{"prompt": "27779,27780,27781,27782,27783,27784", "answer": "27785"}
{"prompt": "40885,40886,40887", "answer": "40888"}
{"prompt": "16014,16015,16016,16017,16018,16019", "answer": "16020"}
{"prompt": "5397,5398,5399,5400,5401,5402,5403,5404,5405", "answer": "5406"}
{"prompt": "18223,18224,18225,18226,18227,18228,18229,18230,18231,18232", "answer": "18233"}
{"prompt": "26696,26697,26698,26699", "answer": "26700"}
{"prompt": "13993,13994", "answer": "13995"}
{"prompt": "32013,32014,32015,32016,32017", "answer": "32018"}
{"prompt": "24079,24080,24081,24082,24083,24084", "answer": "24085"}
{"prompt": "13500,13501,13502", "answer": "13503"}
{"prompt": "8505,8506,8507,8508,8509,8510,8511,8512", "answer": "8513"}
{"prompt": "2119,2120,2121,2122,2123,2124,2125", "answer": "2126"}
{"prompt": "29767,29768,29769", "answer": "29770"}
{"prompt": "26278,26279,26280,26281,26282,26283,26284", "answer": "26285"}
{"prompt": "21804", "answer": "21805"}
{"prompt": "30680", "answer": "30681"}
{"prompt": "18789,18790,18791", "answer": "18792"}
{"prompt": "38060,38061", "answer": "38062"}
{"prompt": "2440,2441,2442,2443,2444,2445,2446,2447", "answer": "2448"}
{"prompt": "12533,12534,12535,12536,12537,12538,12539", "answer": "12540"}
{"prompt": "33486,33487,33488,33489,33490,33491,33492,33493,33494,33495", "answer": "33496"}
{"prompt": "4782,4783,4784,4785,4786,4787,4788", "answer": "4789"}
{"prompt": "27920,27921,27922", "answer": "27923"}
{"prompt": "26321,26322,26323,26324,26325,26326", "answer": "26327"}
{"prompt": "14975,14976,14977", "answer": "14978"}
{"prompt": "32008", "answer": "32009"}
{"prompt": "28614,28615,28616", "answer": "28617"}
{"prompt": "7997,7998", "answer": "7999"}
{"prompt": "23776,23777,23778,23779,23780,23781", "answer": "23782"}
{"prompt": "20165,20166,20167,20168,20169,20170", "answer": "20171"}
{"prompt": "31626,31627,31628,31629,31630,31631,31632,31633,31634,31635", "answer": "31636"}
{"prompt": "33243,33244,33245,33246,33247,33248,33249,33250,33251,33252", "answer": "33253"}
{"prompt": "32293,32294,32295", "answer": "32296"}
{"prompt": "36361,36362,36363,36364", "answer": "36365"}
{"prompt": "15387,15388,15389,15390,15391,15392,15393,15394", "answer": "15395"}
{"prompt": "12404,12405,12406,12407,12408,12409,12410,12411,12412", "answer": "12413"}
{"prompt": "23222,23223,23224,23225", "answer": "23226"}
{"prompt": "7673,7674,7675,7676,7677,7678,7679,7680,7681", "answer": "7682"}
{"prompt": "29328,29329", "answer": "29330"}
{"prompt": "20886,20887,20888,20889,20890", "answer": "20891"}
{"prompt": "14828,14829,14830,14831,14832", "answer": "14833"}
{"prompt": "12948,12949,12950,12951,12952,12953", "answer": "12954"}
{"prompt": "18596", "answer": "18597"}
{"prompt": "14539", "answer": "14540"}
{"prompt": "29910", "answer": "29911"}
{"prompt": "38153,38154,38155,38156,38157,38158,38159", "answer": "38160"}
{"prompt": "32505,32506,32507,32508,32509,32510,32511,32512", "answer": "32513"}
{"prompt": "36925,36926,36927,36928", "answer": "36929"}
{"prompt": "34758,34759,34760,34761,34762,34763,34764,34765,34766", "answer": "34767"}
{"prompt": "21871", "answer": "21872"}
{"prompt": "26003,26004,26005,26006,26007,26008,26009,26010,26011", "answer": "26012"}
{"prompt": "40670,40671,40672,40673,40674,40675,40676,40677", "answer": "40678"}
{"prompt": "14937,14938,14939,14940", "answer": "14941"}
{"prompt": "39648,39649,39650,39651,39652,39653", "answer": "39654"}
{"prompt": "43658,43659,43660,43661,43662,43663,43664", "answer": "43665"}
{"prompt": "41548", "answer": "41549"}
{"prompt": "9418", "answer": "9419"}
{"prompt": "40063,40064,40065,40066,40067,40068,40069,40070,40071,40072", "answer": "40073"}
{"prompt": "16352,16353,16354,16355,16356,16357", "answer": "16358"}
{"prompt": "10386,10387,10388,10389,10390,10391,10392,10393,10394,10395", "answer": "10396"}
{"prompt": "24445,24446,24447,24448,24449", "answer": "24450"}
{"prompt": "2090,2091,2092,2093,2094", "answer": "2095"}
{"prompt": "16124,16125,16126,16127,16128", "answer": "16129"}
{"prompt": "8517,8518,8519,8520,8521,8522", "answer": "8523"}
{"prompt": "27222,27223,27224,27225,27226,27227", "answer": "27228"}
{"prompt": "16072,16073,16074,16075,16076,16077,16078,16079,16080,16081", "answer": "16082"}
{"prompt": "40261,40262", "answer": "40263"}
{"prompt": "38092,38093,38094,38095,38096,38097,38098,38099", "answer": "38100"}
{"prompt": "38560,38561,38562,38563,38564,38565,38566,38567", "answer": "38568"}
{"prompt": "44167,44168,44169,44170,44171,44172,44173,44174,44175,44176", "answer": "44177"}
{"prompt": "2094,2095,2096,2097,2098,2099,2100", "answer": "2101"}
{"prompt": "14531", "answer": "14532"}
{"prompt": "9032,9033,9034,9035,9036,9037,9038,9039,9040,9041", "answer": "9042"}
{"prompt": "18897,18898,18899,18900,18901,18902,18903", "answer": "18904"}
{"prompt": "42462,42463,42464,42465,42466,42467", "answer": "42468"}
{"prompt": "337,338,339,340,341,342", "answer": "343"}
{"prompt": "36085,36086,36087,36088,36089,36090,36091", "answer": "36092"}
{"prompt": "25835,25836,25837,25838,25839,25840,25841,25842,25843,25844", "answer": "25845"}
{"prompt": "25565,25566,25567,25568,25569", "answer": "25570"}
{"prompt": "40903", "answer": "40904"}
{"prompt": "2235,2236,2237,2238,2239,2240,2241,2242", "answer": "2243"}
{"prompt": "13418,13419,13420,13421,13422,13423,13424,13425", "answer": "13426"}
{"prompt": "714,715", "answer": "716"}
{"prompt": "22196,22197,22198", "answer": "22199"}
{"prompt": "13489,13490,13491,13492", "answer": "13493"}
{"prompt": "12083,12084,12085,12086,12087,12088,12089", "answer": "12090"}
{"prompt": "33610,33611,33612,33613,33614,33615,33616", "answer": "33617"}
{"prompt": "23395,23396", "answer": "23397"}
{"prompt": "28008,28009,28010,28011,28012,28013,28014,28015", "answer": "28016"}
{"prompt": "31386", "answer": "31387"}
{"prompt": "15693,15694,15695,15696,15697,15698,15699", "answer": "15700"}
{"prompt": "5651,5652,5653,5654,5655,5656,5657,5658,5659", "answer": "5660"}
{"prompt": "36264,36265,36266,36267", "answer": "36268"}
{"prompt": "5455,5456", "answer": "5457"}
{"prompt": "30957,30958,30959,30960,30961,30962,30963,30964,30965,30966", "answer": "30967"}
{"prompt": "1560,1561,1562,1563,1564,1565,1566,1567,1568", "answer": "1569"}
{"prompt": "36592", "answer": "36593"}
{"prompt": "7485,7486,7487,7488,7489,7490,7491,7492,7493,7494", "answer": "7495"}
{"prompt": "29175,29176,29177", "answer": "29178"}
{"prompt": "15534,15535,15536,15537", "answer": "15538"}
{"prompt": "26965", "answer": "26966"}
{"prompt": "41087,41088,41089,41090,41091,41092,41093", "answer": "41094"}
{"prompt": "5716,5717,5718", "answer": "5719"}
{"prompt": "6861,6862,6863,6864,6865,6866,6867,6868,6869,6870", "answer": "6871"}
{"prompt": "13557,13558,13559,13560,13561,13562,13563", "answer": "13564"}
{"prompt": "19371,19372,19373,19374,19375,19376,19377,19378,19379,19380", "answer": "19381"}
{"prompt": "20986,20987,20988,20989", "answer": "20990"}
{"prompt": "41382,41383,41384", "answer": "41385"}
{"prompt": "7957,7958,7959,7960,7961,7962,7963", "answer": "7964"}
{"prompt": "9124,9125,9126,9127,9128", "answer": "9129"}
{"prompt": "34221,34222,34223", "answer": "34224"}
{"prompt": "8226,8227,8228,8229,8230", "answer": "8231"}
{"prompt": "7710,7711,7712,7713,7714,7715,7716", "answer": "7717"}
{"prompt": "1634,1635,1636", "answer": "1637"}
{"prompt": "10757,10758,10759,10760,10761,10762,10763,10764", "answer": "10765"}
{"prompt": "6145,6146,6147,6148,6149,6150,6151", "answer": "6152"}
{"prompt": "20411,20412", "answer": "20413"}
{"prompt": "3814,3815", "answer": "3816"}
{"prompt": "19269,19270,19271", "answer": "19272"}
{"prompt": "28223,28224", "answer": "28225"}
{"prompt": "41560,41561,41562,41563,41564,41565,41566", "answer": "41567"}
{"prompt": "14577,14578", "answer": "14579"}
{"prompt": "39684,39685,39686,39687,39688,39689,39690,39691,39692", "answer": "39693"}
{"prompt": "42448,42449,42450,42451,42452,42453,42454,42455", "answer": "42456"}
{"prompt": "17813,17814", "answer": "17815"}
{"prompt": "14029,14030,14031", "answer": "14032"}
{"prompt": "26719,26720", "answer": "26721"}
{"prompt": "33829,33830,33831,33832,33833", "answer": "33834"}
{"prompt": "9740,9741,9742,9743,9744,9745,9746,9747,9748,9749", "answer": "9750"}
{"prompt": "1769", "answer": "1770"}
{"prompt": "28566,28567,28568,28569,28570,28571,28572,28573,28574", "answer": "28575"}
{"prompt": "40531,40532", "answer": "40533"}
{"prompt": "1951", "answer": "1952"}
{"prompt": "11472,11473,11474", "answer": "11475"}
{"prompt": "831,832,833,834", "answer": "835"}
{"prompt": "39052,39053,39054,39055,39056,39057,39058,39059,39060", "answer": "39061"}
{"prompt": "45178", "answer": "45179"}
{"prompt": "40350,40351", "answer": "40352"}
{"prompt": "40444", "answer": "40445"}
{"prompt": "43776,43777,43778,43779,43780,43781,43782,43783", "answer": "43784"}
{"prompt": "24058,24059,24060,24061,24062,24063,24064,24065", "answer": "24066"}
{"prompt": "11946,11947,11948,11949,11950,11951,11952,11953", "answer": "11954"}
{"prompt": "19266,19267", "answer": "19268"}
{"prompt": "29251,29252,29253,29254,29255,29256,29257,29258,29259,29260", "answer": "29261"}
{"prompt": "41296,41297,41298,41299,41300,41301", "answer": "41302"}
{"prompt": "37533,37534,37535,37536,37537,37538", "answer": "37539"}
{"prompt": "44692,44693,44694,44695,44696,44697,44698", "answer": "44699"}
{"prompt": "7411,7412,7413,7414", "answer": "7415"}
{"prompt": "17140,17141,17142,17143", "answer": "17144"}
{"prompt": "32600,32601,32602,32603,32604,32605,32606,32607", "answer": "32608"}
{"prompt": "11887,11888,11889,11890", "answer": "11891"}
{"prompt": "38498,38499,38500,38501,38502,38503,38504,38505,38506,38507", "answer": "38508"}
{"prompt": "23736,23737", "answer": "23738"}
{"prompt": "30148,30149,30150,30151", "answer": "30152"}
{"prompt": "13018,13019,13020,13021,13022,13023,13024", "answer": "13025"}
{"prompt": "29148,29149,29150,29151,29152,29153", "answer": "29154"}
{"prompt": "9601,9602,9603,9604,9605,9606,9607,9608,9609", "answer": "9610"}
{"prompt": "32004,32005,32006", "answer": "32007"}
{"prompt": "3807,3808,3809,3810", "answer": "3811"}
{"prompt": "29362,29363,29364,29365,29366,29367,29368,29369,29370,29371", "answer": "29372"}
{"prompt": "43768,43769", "answer": "43770"}
{"prompt": "44476,44477,44478,44479,44480,44481,44482,44483", "answer": "44484"}
{"prompt": "17958", "answer": "17959"}
{"prompt": "32052,32053,32054,32055,32056,32057,32058,32059,32060", "answer": "32061"}
{"prompt": "44961,44962,44963,44964,44965,44966,44967", "answer": "44968"}
{"prompt": "24998,24999,25000,25001,25002,25003,25004", "answer": "25005"}
{"prompt": "23679", "answer": "23680"}
{"prompt": "38645,38646,38647", "answer": "38648"}
{"prompt": "27949,27950,27951", "answer": "27952"}
{"prompt": "11494,11495,11496,11497,11498,11499,11500,11501", "answer": "11502"}
{"prompt": "1827,1828,1829,1830,1831,1832", "answer": "1833"}
{"prompt": "1087,1088,1089", "answer": "1090"}
{"prompt": "2328,2329,2330,2331,2332,2333,2334,2335,2336", "answer": "2337"}
{"prompt": "31019,31020", "answer": "31021"}
{"prompt": "272,273,274,275,276,277", "answer": "278"}
{"prompt": "17931,17932,17933,17934,17935,17936", "answer": "17937"}
{"prompt": "31022,31023,31024,31025,31026", "answer": "31027"}
{"prompt": "41445,41446,41447,41448,41449,41450", "answer": "41451"}
{"prompt": "19582,19583,19584,19585,19586,19587,19588,19589,19590", "answer": "19591"}
{"prompt": "19835,19836,19837,19838,19839,19840,19841,19842,19843,19844", "answer": "19845"}
{"prompt": "21047,21048", "answer": "21049"}
{"prompt": "37763,37764,37765,37766,37767,37768,37769", "answer": "37770"}
{"prompt": "41924,41925,41926,41927", "answer": "41928"}
{"prompt": "27957", "answer": "27958"}
{"prompt": "530,531,532,533,534,535,536,537", "answer": "538"}
{"prompt": "29566,29567,29568,29569,29570,29571,29572,29573", "answer": "29574"}
{"prompt": "30915", "answer": "30916"}
{"prompt": "34534,34535", "answer": "34536"}
{"prompt": "26151,26152,26153,26154,26155,26156", "answer": "26157"}
{"prompt": "9257,9258,9259,9260,9261,9262,9263,9264", "answer": "9265"}
{"prompt": "34950,34951,34952,34953,34954,34955,34956,34957,34958,34959", "answer": "34960"}
{"prompt": "14677,14678", "answer": "14679"}
{"prompt": "8494", "answer": "8495"}
{"prompt": "28484", "answer": "28485"}
{"prompt": "33896,33897,33898,33899,33900", "answer": "33901"}
{"prompt": "16575", "answer": "16576"}
{"prompt": "40510,40511,40512,40513,40514,40515,40516,40517", "answer": "40518"}
{"prompt": "31431", "answer": "31432"}
{"prompt": "21519,21520,21521,21522,21523,21524", "answer": "21525"}
{"prompt": "2328", "answer": "2329"}
{"prompt": "37482,37483,37484", "answer": "37485"}
{"prompt": "33100,33101,33102,33103,33104,33105,33106,33107,33108,33109", "answer": "33110"}
{"prompt": "41540,41541,41542,41543,41544,41545,41546", "answer": "41547"}
{"prompt": "36964,36965,36966,36967,36968,36969,36970,36971", "answer": "36972"}
{"prompt": "7727,7728,7729,7730,7731,7732", "answer": "7733"}
{"prompt": "30790,30791,30792,30793,30794,30795,30796,30797,30798", "answer": "30799"}
{"prompt": "1153,1154,1155,1156,1157,1158,1159,1160,1161", "answer": "1162"}
{"prompt": "44230", "answer": "44231"}
{"prompt": "7732,7733,7734,7735,7736,7737,7738", "answer": "7739"}
{"prompt": "6495,6496,6497,6498,6499,6500", "answer": "6501"}
{"prompt": "7387,7388,7389,7390,7391", "answer": "7392"}
{"prompt": "21031,21032", "answer": "21033"}
{"prompt": "32607,32608,32609", "answer": "32610"}
{"prompt": "21149,21150,21151,21152,21153", "answer": "21154"}
{"prompt": "28511,28512,28513,28514,28515,28516,28517", "answer": "28518"}
{"prompt": "32491,32492,32493,32494,32495,32496,32497", "answer": "32498"}
{"prompt": "12189,12190,12191,12192,12193,12194,12195", "answer": "12196"}
{"prompt": "13280", "answer": "13281"}
{"prompt": "27855,27856,27857,27858,27859,27860,27861", "answer": "27862"}
{"prompt": "31951,31952,31953,31954,31955,31956,31957,31958,31959", "answer": "31960"}
{"prompt": "34204,34205,34206,34207,34208,34209,34210", "answer": "34211"}
{"prompt": "13196,13197,13198,13199,13200,13201,13202", "answer": "13203"}
{"prompt": "8423", "answer": "8424"}
{"prompt": "25045,25046,25047,25048,25049,25050,25051,25052", "answer": "25053"}
{"prompt": "38932,38933,38934,38935,38936,38937", "answer": "38938"}
{"prompt": "31779,31780,31781,31782,31783,31784,31785", "answer": "31786"}
{"prompt": "26273,26274,26275,26276,26277,26278", "answer": "26279"}
{"prompt": "26239,26240,26241,26242,26243,26244,26245,26246,26247,26248", "answer": "26249"}
{"prompt": "30711,30712,30713,30714,30715,30716,30717,30718", "answer": "30719"}
{"prompt": "30979,30980,30981,30982,30983,30984,30985,30986,30987,30988", "answer": "30989"}
{"prompt": "34005,34006,34007,34008,34009,34010,34011,34012,34013", "answer": "34014"}
{"prompt": "37169,37170,37171,37172,37173,37174,37175,37176", "answer": "37177"}
{"prompt": "43968,43969,43970,43971,43972,43973,43974", "answer": "43975"}
{"prompt": "37381,37382,37383,37384,37385,37386,37387,37388", "answer": "37389"}
{"prompt": "22882,22883", "answer": "22884"}
{"prompt": "22458,22459", "answer": "22460"}
{"prompt": "1132,1133,1134,1135,1136", "answer": "1137"}
{"prompt": "27131,27132,27133,27134,27135,27136,27137,27138,27139,27140", "answer": "27141"}
{"prompt": "27642,27643,27644,27645,27646,27647,27648", "answer": "27649"}
{"prompt": "1013,1014,1015,1016", "answer": "1017"}
{"prompt": "14381,14382,14383,14384,14385,14386,14387,14388,14389", "answer": "14390"}
{"prompt": "44379,44380,44381,44382,44383,44384", "answer": "44385"}
{"prompt": "25960,25961,25962,25963,25964,25965", "answer": "25966"}
{"prompt": "16070", "answer": "16071"}
{"prompt": "40670", "answer": "40671"}
{"prompt": "12439", "answer": "12440"}
{"prompt": "31405,31406", "answer": "31407"}
{"prompt": "14130,14131", "answer": "14132"}
{"prompt": "16255,16256,16257,16258,16259,16260,16261,16262", "answer": "16263"}
{"prompt": "2642,2643,2644,2645,2646,2647,2648,2649,2650", "answer": "2651"}
{"prompt": "7251,7252", "answer": "7253"}
{"prompt": "33481,33482,33483,33484,33485,33486", "answer": "33487"}
{"prompt": "9351,9352,9353,9354,9355,9356,9357,9358", "answer": "9359"}
{"prompt": "33580,33581,33582,33583,33584,33585,33586,33587,33588,33589", "answer": "33590"}
{"prompt": "239,240,241,242", "answer": "243"}
{"prompt": "38767,38768,38769,38770,38771,38772", "answer": "38773"}
{"prompt": "19450,19451", "answer": "19452"}
{"prompt": "30432", "answer": "30433"}
{"prompt": "8435,8436,8437,8438,8439,8440,8441,8442,8443", "answer": "8444"}
{"prompt": "23584,23585,23586,23587,23588,23589,23590,23591,23592", "answer": "23593"}
{"prompt": "37191,37192,37193,37194,37195,37196", "answer": "37197"}
{"prompt": "11060,11061,11062,11063,11064,11065,11066,11067", "answer": "11068"}
{"prompt": "34188,34189,34190,34191,34192", "answer": "34193"}
{"prompt": "11262,11263,11264,11265,11266,11267,11268,11269", "answer": "11270"}
{"prompt": "1004,1005,1006,1007,1008,1009", "answer": "1010"}
{"prompt": "23592", "answer": "23593"}
{"prompt": "24175,24176,24177,24178,24179,24180,24181,24182,24183", "answer": "24184"}
{"prompt": "10846,10847,10848,10849,10850,10851", "answer": "10852"}
{"prompt": "40552,40553,40554,40555,40556,40557,40558,40559,40560", "answer": "40561"}
{"prompt": "39667,39668,39669,39670,39671,39672,39673,39674,39675,39676", "answer": "39677"}
{"prompt": "701", "answer": "702"}
{"prompt": "29053,29054,29055,29056", "answer": "29057"}
{"prompt": "26466,26467", "answer": "26468"}
{"prompt": "32554,32555", "answer": "32556"}
{"prompt": "12044,12045,12046,12047,12048,12049,12050,12051,12052,12053", "answer": "12054"}
{"prompt": "35422,35423", "answer": "35424"}
{"prompt": "35912,35913,35914,35915,35916", "answer": "35917"}
{"prompt": "31332,31333,31334,31335,31336", "answer": "31337"}
{"prompt": "26061,26062,26063", "answer": "26064"}
{"prompt": "14882,14883,14884,14885,14886,14887,14888,14889,14890", "answer": "14891"}
{"prompt": "12321,12322", "answer": "12323"}
{"prompt": "22078", "answer": "22079"}
{"prompt": "25491,25492,25493,25494,25495,25496", "answer": "25497"}
{"prompt": "31970,31971,31972,31973,31974,31975,31976,31977", "answer": "31978"}
{"prompt": "6846,6847,6848,6849", "answer": "6850"}
{"prompt": "3933,3934,3935,3936,3937", "answer": "3938"}
{"prompt": "42016,42017", "answer": "42018"}
{"prompt": "19220,19221,19222,19223,19224,19225,19226,19227", "answer": "19228"}
{"prompt": "15954,15955,15956", "answer": "15957"}
{"prompt": "39042,39043,39044,39045,39046,39047", "answer": "39048"}
{"prompt": "43755,43756,43757,43758", "answer": "43759"}
{"prompt": "33650,33651,33652,33653,33654,33655,33656,33657", "answer": "33658"}
{"prompt": "22173,22174,22175,22176", "answer": "22177"}
{"prompt": "6059,6060,6061,6062,6063,6064,6065", "answer": "6066"}
{"prompt": "30314,30315,30316,30317", "answer": "30318"}
{"prompt": "20357", "answer": "20358"}
{"prompt": "5156,5157,5158,5159,5160,5161", "answer": "5162"}
{"prompt": "10618,10619,10620,10621,10622,10623", "answer": "10624"}
{"prompt": "41743,41744,41745,41746,41747,41748,41749", "answer": "41750"}
{"prompt": "41653,41654", "answer": "41655"}
{"prompt": "18729,18730,18731,18732,18733,18734,18735,18736", "answer": "18737"}
{"prompt": "19992,19993,19994,19995,19996,19997,19998,19999", "answer": "20000"}
{"prompt": "31582", "answer": "31583"}
{"prompt": "1624,1625,1626,1627,1628,1629,1630,1631,1632", "answer": "1633"}
{"prompt": "15787,15788,15789,15790,15791,15792", "answer": "15793"}
{"prompt": "40885", "answer": "40886"}
{"prompt": "15913,15914,15915,15916", "answer": "15917"}
{"prompt": "44483,44484", "answer": "44485"}
{"prompt": "32060,32061,32062", "answer": "32063"}
{"prompt": "26965", "answer": "26966"}
{"prompt": "4645", "answer": "4646"}
{"prompt": "28409,28410,28411,28412,28413,28414", "answer": "28415"}
{"prompt": "2232", "answer": "2233"}
{"prompt": "44586,44587,44588,44589,44590", "answer": "44591"}
{"prompt": "15916,15917,15918,15919,15920,15921", "answer": "15922"}
{"prompt": "10922,10923", "answer": "10924"}
{"prompt": "34986,34987,34988,34989,34990,34991,34992,34993", "answer": "34994"}
{"prompt": "11675", "answer": "11676"}
{"prompt": "2788,2789,2790,2791,2792,2793,2794", "answer": "2795"}
{"prompt": "33892,33893,33894,33895,33896", "answer": "33897"}
{"prompt": "20657,20658,20659,20660,20661,20662,20663,20664,20665,20666", "answer": "20667"}
{"prompt": "8479,8480,8481,8482,8483,8484,8485", "answer": "8486"}
{"prompt": "35472,35473", "answer": "35474"}
{"prompt": "15858,15859,15860,15861,15862,15863,15864,15865,15866", "answer": "15867"}
{"prompt": "36239,36240,36241,36242,36243,36244", "answer": "36245"}
{"prompt": "25528,25529,25530,25531", "answer": "25532"}
{"prompt": "23665,23666,23667,23668", "answer": "23669"}
{"prompt": "4808", "answer": "4809"}
{"prompt": "24533,24534,24535,24536,24537,24538,24539,24540,24541,24542", "answer": "24543"}
{"prompt": "30031,30032,30033", "answer": "30034"}
{"prompt": "14957,14958,14959,14960,14961,14962,14963,14964,14965", "answer": "14966"}
{"prompt": "32270,32271,32272", "answer": "32273"}
{"prompt": "29672,29673,29674,29675,29676,29677,29678,29679", "answer": "29680"}
{"prompt": "8065,8066,8067,8068,8069,8070,8071", "answer": "8072"}
{"prompt": "13531,13532,13533,13534,13535,13536,13537,13538", "answer": "13539"}
{"prompt": "6357,6358,6359,6360", "answer": "6361"}
{"prompt": "8111", "answer": "8112"}
{"prompt": "34592,34593,34594,34595,34596,34597", "answer": "34598"}
{"prompt": "39859,39860,39861,39862,39863,39864,39865,39866,39867", "answer": "39868"}
{"prompt": "34857,34858", "answer": "34859"}
{"prompt": "34662,34663,34664,34665,34666,34667,34668,34669", "answer": "34670"}
{"prompt": "43602,43603,43604,43605,43606,43607,43608", "answer": "43609"}
{"prompt": "6932,6933,6934,6935,6936,6937", "answer": "6938"}
{"prompt": "34419,34420,34421,34422,34423,34424,34425,34426", "answer": "34427"}
{"prompt": "28994", "answer": "28995"}
{"prompt": "16586,16587,16588", "answer": "16589"}
{"prompt": "5423,5424,5425,5426,5427,5428,5429,5430", "answer": "5431"}
{"prompt": "29858,29859", "answer": "29860"}
{"prompt": "11877,11878,11879", "answer": "11880"}
{"prompt": "28058,28059,28060,28061,28062,28063,28064,28065,28066,28067", "answer": "28068"}
{"prompt": "21570,21571,21572,21573,21574,21575,21576,21577", "answer": "21578"}
{"prompt": "7827", "answer": "7828"}
{"prompt": "11587,11588,11589,11590,11591,11592", "answer": "11593"}
{"prompt": "558,559,560,561,562,563,564,565,566", "answer": "567"}
{"prompt": "18177,18178,18179,18180,18181,18182,18183,18184,18185,18186", "answer": "18187"}
{"prompt": "4207,4208,4209,4210,4211,4212,4213,4214", "answer": "4215"}
{"prompt": "3096,3097,3098,3099,3100,3101,3102", "answer": "3103"}
{"prompt": "19451,19452,19453,19454,19455,19456,19457", "answer": "19458"}
{"prompt": "33541,33542", "answer": "33543"}
{"prompt": "37655,37656,37657,37658,37659", "answer": "37660"}
{"prompt": "30930,30931", "answer": "30932"}
{"prompt": "6184,6185", "answer": "6186"}
{"prompt": "27902,27903,27904,27905,27906,27907", "answer": "27908"}
{"prompt": "23396,23397,23398,23399,23400", "answer": "23401"}
{"prompt": "38145,38146,38147,38148,38149,38150,38151,38152,38153", "answer": "38154"}
{"prompt": "27360,27361,27362,27363", "answer": "27364"}
{"prompt": "32854,32855,32856,32857,32858,32859", "answer": "32860"}
{"prompt": "9614,9615,9616", "answer": "9617"}
{"prompt": "30618,30619", "answer": "30620"}
{"prompt": "29981,29982,29983,29984,29985,29986,29987,29988,29989", "answer": "29990"}
{"prompt": "21260,21261,21262,21263,21264,21265,21266,21267,21268,21269", "answer": "21270"}
{"prompt": "27107,27108,27109,27110", "answer": "27111"}
{"prompt": "2867,2868,2869,2870", "answer": "2871"}
{"prompt": "43061,43062,43063,43064,43065,43066,43067", "answer": "43068"}
{"prompt": "9225,9226,9227", "answer": "9228"}
{"prompt": "10527,10528,10529", "answer": "10530"}
{"prompt": "32962,32963,32964", "answer": "32965"}
{"prompt": "41777,41778,41779", "answer": "41780"}
{"prompt": "45260,45261,45262,45263", "answer": "45264"}
{"prompt": "19132,19133,19134,19135,19136,19137", "answer": "19138"}
{"prompt": "34350,34351,34352,34353,34354", "answer": "34355"}
{"prompt": "13463,13464,13465,13466,13467,13468,13469,13470", "answer": "13471"}
{"prompt": "5288,5289", "answer": "5290"}
{"prompt": "6598,6599,6600", "answer": "6601"}
{"prompt": "26361,26362,26363", "answer": "26364"}
{"prompt": "27089,27090,27091,27092,27093,27094,27095,27096,27097,27098", "answer": "27099"}
{"prompt": "20808,20809,20810,20811,20812,20813,20814,20815,20816", "answer": "20817"}
{"prompt": "5065,5066,5067,5068", "answer": "5069"}
{"prompt": "12109,12110,12111,12112,12113", "answer": "12114"}
{"prompt": "21951,21952,21953,21954,21955", "answer": "21956"}
{"prompt": "12692,12693,12694,12695,12696,12697,12698,12699,12700,12701", "answer": "12702"}
{"prompt": "23400,23401", "answer": "23402"}
{"prompt": "33908,33909,33910,33911,33912", "answer": "33913"}
{"prompt": "6983", "answer": "6984"}
{"prompt": "37155,37156,37157,37158,37159", "answer": "37160"}
{"prompt": "6457,6458,6459,6460,6461,6462,6463,6464,6465,6466", "answer": "6467"}
{"prompt": "23065,23066,23067,23068", "answer": "23069"}
{"prompt": "41506", "answer": "41507"}
{"prompt": "1055,1056,1057,1058", "answer": "1059"}
{"prompt": "40404", "answer": "40405"}
{"prompt": "37046,37047,37048,37049,37050,37051,37052,37053,37054", "answer": "37055"}
{"prompt": "11413,11414,11415", "answer": "11416"}
{"prompt": "42056,42057,42058,42059", "answer": "42060"}
{"prompt": "15610", "answer": "15611"}
{"prompt": "17765,17766,17767,17768,17769,17770,17771,17772", "answer": "17773"}
{"prompt": "28955,28956,28957,28958,28959,28960,28961,28962,28963", "answer": "28964"}
{"prompt": "2893,2894", "answer": "2895"}
{"prompt": "42307,42308,42309,42310", "answer": "42311"}
{"prompt": "26878,26879", "answer": "26880"}
{"prompt": "21591,21592,21593,21594,21595,21596", "answer": "21597"}
{"prompt": "25249,25250,25251", "answer": "25252"}
{"prompt": "9810,9811,9812,9813,9814,9815", "answer": "9816"}
{"prompt": "33343,33344,33345", "answer": "33346"}
{"prompt": "25442,25443,25444,25445,25446", "answer": "25447"}
{"prompt": "38939,38940,38941,38942,38943", "answer": "38944"}
{"prompt": "38407,38408,38409,38410,38411,38412,38413,38414,38415,38416", "answer": "38417"}
{"prompt": "37340,37341,37342,37343,37344,37345,37346,37347", "answer": "37348"}
{"prompt": "12075,12076,12077,12078,12079,12080,12081,12082,12083", "answer": "12084"}
{"prompt": "10547,10548,10549,10550,10551", "answer": "10552"}
{"prompt": "16044,16045,16046,16047", "answer": "16048"}
{"prompt": "17166,17167,17168,17169,17170,17171,17172", "answer": "17173"}
{"prompt": "6907,6908,6909,6910,6911,6912,6913,6914", "answer": "6915"}
{"prompt": "5816,5817,5818,5819", "answer": "5820"}
{"prompt": "34464,34465,34466,34467,34468,34469", "answer": "34470"}
{"prompt": "11339,11340,11341,11342,11343,11344,11345,11346,11347,11348", "answer": "11349"}
{"prompt": "43983,43984,43985,43986", "answer": "43987"}
{"prompt": "21537", "answer": "21538"}
{"prompt": "2723,2724,2725", "answer": "2726"}
{"prompt": "35512,35513,35514,35515,35516,35517,35518,35519,35520,35521", "answer": "35522"}
{"prompt": "44224,44225", "answer": "44226"}
{"prompt": "1676", "answer": "1677"}
{"prompt": "11248,11249,11250,11251", "answer": "11252"}
{"prompt": "37388,37389,37390,37391,37392,37393,37394,37395", "answer": "37396"}
{"prompt": "7509,7510,7511,7512,7513,7514", "answer": "7515"}
{"prompt": "37491,37492,37493,37494", "answer": "37495"}
{"prompt": "30498,30499,30500,30501,30502", "answer": "30503"}
{"prompt": "24753,24754,24755,24756,24757,24758,24759", "answer": "24760"}
{"prompt": "7246,7247,7248,7249,7250,7251", "answer": "7252"}
{"prompt": "9650,9651,9652", "answer": "9653"}
{"prompt": "26566,26567,26568,26569,26570", "answer": "26571"}
{"prompt": "29163,29164,29165,29166,29167,29168,29169,29170,29171,29172", "answer": "29173"}
{"prompt": "23456,23457", "answer": "23458"}
{"prompt": "14627,14628,14629", "answer": "14630"}
{"prompt": "37246,37247,37248,37249,37250", "answer": "37251"}
{"prompt": "29765", "answer": "29766"}
{"prompt": "44446,44447,44448,44449,44450,44451,44452,44453,44454,44455", "answer": "44456"}
{"prompt": "26627,26628,26629,26630,26631,26632,26633,26634,26635,26636", "answer": "26637"}
{"prompt": "595", "answer": "596"}
{"prompt": "22992", "answer": "22993"}
{"prompt": "6898,6899,6900,6901,6902,6903,6904,6905,6906,6907", "answer": "6908"}
{"prompt": "23463,23464,23465,23466,23467,23468", "answer": "23469"}
{"prompt": "3540,3541,3542", "answer": "3543"}
{"prompt": "3349,3350,3351,3352,3353", "answer": "3354"}
{"prompt": "36071,36072,36073,36074,36075,36076,36077,36078,36079", "answer": "36080"}
{"prompt": "3288,3289,3290,3291,3292,3293,3294,3295,3296", "answer": "3297"}
{"prompt": "6312,6313,6314,6315,6316", "answer": "6317"}
{"prompt": "19950,19951", "answer": "19952"}
{"prompt": "17861,17862,17863", "answer": "17864"}
{"prompt": "2308,2309,2310,2311", "answer": "2312"}
{"prompt": "15120,15121,15122,15123,15124,15125,15126,15127,15128", "answer": "15129"}
{"prompt": "14131,14132,14133,14134", "answer": "14135"}
{"prompt": "23034,23035,23036", "answer": "23037"}
{"prompt": "779,780,781,782", "answer": "783"}
{"prompt": "40655,40656,40657,40658,40659,40660,40661,40662,40663", "answer": "40664"}
{"prompt": "4850", "answer": "4851"}
{"prompt": "7906,7907", "answer": "7908"}
{"prompt": "40351,40352,40353,40354,40355,40356,40357,40358,40359", "answer": "40360"}
{"prompt": "12202,12203,12204,12205,12206,12207,12208,12209,12210,12211", "answer": "12212"}
{"prompt": "42643,42644,42645,42646,42647,42648,42649,42650,42651", "answer": "42652"}
{"prompt": "17794,17795,17796,17797,17798", "answer": "17799"}
{"prompt": "1965,1966,1967,1968,1969,1970,1971,1972,1973", "answer": "1974"}
{"prompt": "25025,25026,25027,25028,25029", "answer": "25030"}
{"prompt": "27044,27045,27046,27047,27048,27049,27050,27051,27052", "answer": "27053"}
{"prompt": "5740,5741,5742", "answer": "5743"}
{"prompt": "7775", "answer": "7776"}
{"prompt": "8071,8072,8073,8074,8075,8076", "answer": "8077"}
{"prompt": "19999,20000,20001,20002,20003,20004,20005,20006", "answer": "20007"}
{"prompt": "14619,14620,14621,14622,14623,14624,14625,14626", "answer": "14627"}
{"prompt": "31668,31669,31670,31671,31672,31673", "answer": "31674"}
{"prompt": "27737,27738,27739,27740,27741,27742,27743,27744,27745", "answer": "27746"}
{"prompt": "4019,4020,4021,4022,4023,4024,4025,4026,4027,4028", "answer": "4029"}
{"prompt": "12343,12344,12345", "answer": "12346"}
{"prompt": "28425,28426,28427,28428,28429,28430,28431,28432,28433,28434", "answer": "28435"}
{"prompt": "30317,30318,30319,30320,30321,30322,30323,30324", "answer": "30325"}
{"prompt": "23360,23361,23362,23363,23364,23365", "answer": "23366"}
{"prompt": "35555", "answer": "35556"}
{"prompt": "34855,34856,34857", "answer": "34858"}
{"prompt": "5713,5714,5715", "answer": "5716"}
{"prompt": "13795,13796,13797,13798,13799,13800,13801,13802,13803", "answer": "13804"}
{"prompt": "44492,44493,44494,44495", "answer": "44496"}
{"prompt": "44626,44627,44628,44629,44630,44631,44632", "answer": "44633"}
{"prompt": "4126,4127,4128,4129,4130,4131,4132", "answer": "4133"}
{"prompt": "29931,29932,29933,29934,29935,29936,29937", "answer": "29938"}
{"prompt": "15812,15813,15814,15815", "answer": "15816"}
{"prompt": "9307,9308,9309,9310", "answer": "9311"}
{"prompt": "28165,28166,28167,28168,28169,28170,28171,28172,28173,28174", "answer": "28175"}
{"prompt": "38818,38819,38820,38821", "answer": "38822"}
{"prompt": "6806,6807,6808,6809,6810,6811,6812,6813,6814", "answer": "6815"}
{"prompt": "20174,20175,20176,20177,20178,20179,20180,20181", "answer": "20182"}
{"prompt": "11760,11761,11762,11763,11764", "answer": "11765"}
{"prompt": "44705,44706,44707,44708,44709", "answer": "44710"}
{"prompt": "16887,16888,16889,16890,16891,16892,16893,16894,16895", "answer": "16896"}
{"prompt": "22793,22794,22795,22796,22797,22798,22799", "answer": "22800"}
{"prompt": "42741,42742,42743,42744,42745,42746", "answer": "42747"}
{"prompt": "19137,19138,19139,19140,19141,19142,19143", "answer": "19144"}
{"prompt": "33887,33888,33889,33890", "answer": "33891"}
{"prompt": "31618,31619", "answer": "31620"}
{"prompt": "29623,29624,29625,29626,29627,29628,29629,29630,29631", "answer": "29632"}
{"prompt": "773,774,775,776,777,778,779", "answer": "780"}
{"prompt": "12015,12016,12017,12018,12019,12020,12021,12022,12023", "answer": "12024"}
{"prompt": "37465,37466,37467,37468,37469,37470,37471,37472,37473", "answer": "37474"}
{"prompt": "13001,13002,13003,13004,13005,13006,13007,13008,13009,13010", "answer": "13011"}
{"prompt": "2299,2300,2301", "answer": "2302"}
{"prompt": "4431,4432,4433,4434,4435,4436,4437,4438", "answer": "4439"}
{"prompt": "11681,11682", "answer": "11683"}
{"prompt": "8248,8249,8250,8251,8252,8253,8254,8255", "answer": "8256"}
{"prompt": "21278,21279,21280,21281,21282,21283,21284", "answer": "21285"}
{"prompt": "939,940,941,942,943,944,945,946", "answer": "947"}
{"prompt": "33088,33089,33090,33091,33092,33093", "answer": "33094"}
{"prompt": "25144,25145", "answer": "25146"}
{"prompt": "30807,30808,30809,30810,30811,30812", "answer": "30813"}
{"prompt": "34999,35000,35001,35002,35003,35004,35005,35006", "answer": "35007"}
{"prompt": "22247,22248,22249,22250,22251,22252,22253,22254,22255", "answer": "22256"}
{"prompt": "39238,39239,39240,39241,39242,39243,39244", "answer": "39245"}
{"prompt": "10499,10500,10501,10502,10503,10504,10505,10506,10507", "answer": "10508"}
{"prompt": "34972,34973,34974,34975,34976,34977,34978,34979,34980", "answer": "34981"}
{"prompt": "13703,13704,13705,13706,13707,13708,13709", "answer": "13710"}
{"prompt": "11222,11223,11224,11225,11226", "answer": "11227"}
{"prompt": "31141,31142,31143", "answer": "31144"}
{"prompt": "880", "answer": "881"}
{"prompt": "5701,5702,5703,5704,5705,5706,5707,5708,5709", "answer": "5710"}
{"prompt": "44289", "answer": "44290"}
{"prompt": "5836,5837,5838,5839,5840", "answer": "5841"}
{"prompt": "10586,10587,10588,10589,10590,10591,10592,10593,10594", "answer": "10595"}
{"prompt": "27247,27248,27249,27250,27251,27252", "answer": "27253"}
{"prompt": "11026,11027,11028,11029", "answer": "11030"}
{"prompt": "2148,2149,2150,2151,2152,2153,2154,2155", "answer": "2156"}
{"prompt": "11873,11874,11875,11876,11877", "answer": "11878"}
{"prompt": "43531", "answer": "43532"}
{"prompt": "5467,5468,5469", "answer": "5470"}
{"prompt": "7875,7876,7877,7878,7879", "answer": "7880"}
{"prompt": "44416,44417,44418,44419,44420,44421", "answer": "44422"}
{"prompt": "27748,27749,27750,27751,27752,27753,27754,27755,27756,27757", "answer": "27758"}
{"prompt": "31701,31702,31703,31704,31705,31706,31707,31708,31709,31710", "answer": "31711"}
{"prompt": "1832,1833,1834,1835,1836,1837,1838,1839,1840", "answer": "1841"}
{"prompt": "28161,28162,28163,28164,28165", "answer": "28166"}
{"prompt": "10709,10710,10711,10712,10713,10714,10715,10716,10717", "answer": "10718"}
{"prompt": "8698,8699,8700,8701,8702", "answer": "8703"}
{"prompt": "10337,10338,10339", "answer": "10340"}
{"prompt": "41429,41430", "answer": "41431"}
{"prompt": "16704,16705,16706,16707,16708", "answer": "16709"}
{"prompt": "15730,15731,15732", "answer": "15733"}
{"prompt": "18020,18021,18022,18023,18024,18025", "answer": "18026"}
{"prompt": "43987,43988,43989", "answer": "43990"}
{"prompt": "10799,10800,10801,10802,10803,10804,10805,10806,10807", "answer": "10808"}
{"prompt": "34319,34320,34321,34322,34323,34324,34325,34326", "answer": "34327"}
{"prompt": "21889,21890,21891,21892,21893,21894", "answer": "21895"}
{"prompt": "10435", "answer": "10436"}
{"prompt": "26912,26913,26914,26915,26916,26917,26918,26919", "answer": "26920"}
{"prompt": "26063,26064,26065,26066,26067", "answer": "26068"}
{"prompt": "4393,4394,4395", "answer": "4396"}
{"prompt": "41322,41323,41324,41325,41326,41327,41328,41329,41330", "answer": "41331"}
{"prompt": "10004,10005,10006,10007", "answer": "10008"}
{"prompt": "42577,42578,42579", "answer": "42580"}
{"prompt": "27030,27031,27032,27033,27034", "answer": "27035"}
{"prompt": "1202", "answer": "1203"}
{"prompt": "15220", "answer": "15221"}
{"prompt": "184,185", "answer": "186"}
{"prompt": "26980,26981,26982,26983,26984,26985", "answer": "26986"}
{"prompt": "17449,17450", "answer": "17451"}
{"prompt": "42207,42208,42209,42210,42211", "answer": "42212"}
{"prompt": "16321,16322,16323,16324,16325,16326,16327,16328,16329,16330", "answer": "16331"}
{"prompt": "39201,39202,39203,39204,39205", "answer": "39206"}
{"prompt": "31510,31511", "answer": "31512"}
{"prompt": "41506,41507,41508,41509,41510,41511,41512", "answer": "41513"}
{"prompt": "28746,28747,28748,28749,28750,28751", "answer": "28752"}
{"prompt": "17076", "answer": "17077"}
{"prompt": "39929,39930,39931", "answer": "39932"}
{"prompt": "39637,39638,39639,39640", "answer": "39641"}
{"prompt": "36689,36690,36691,36692,36693,36694,36695,36696,36697,36698", "answer": "36699"}
{"prompt": "39758,39759,39760,39761,39762,39763,39764,39765", "answer": "39766"}
{"prompt": "40129,40130,40131,40132,40133,40134,40135,40136,40137,40138", "answer": "40139"}
{"prompt": "37016,37017,37018,37019", "answer": "37020"}
{"prompt": "40905,40906,40907,40908,40909,40910,40911", "answer": "40912"}
{"prompt": "31291,31292,31293,31294,31295,31296,31297", "answer": "31298"}
{"prompt": "28624,28625,28626,28627,28628,28629", "answer": "28630"}
{"prompt": "18267,18268,18269,18270,18271,18272", "answer": "18273"}
{"prompt": "10369,10370,10371,10372", "answer": "10373"}
{"prompt": "24908,24909,24910,24911,24912,24913,24914,24915,24916", "answer": "24917"}
{"prompt": "30976,30977,30978,30979", "answer": "30980"}
{"prompt": "35884,35885,35886", "answer": "35887"}
{"prompt": "31644,31645,31646,31647", "answer": "31648"}
{"prompt": "36815,36816,36817,36818,36819", "answer": "36820"}
{"prompt": "23820,23821,23822,23823,23824,23825,23826,23827", "answer": "23828"}
{"prompt": "26303,26304,26305,26306,26307,26308,26309", "answer": "26310"}
{"prompt": "28769,28770,28771,28772,28773,28774,28775,28776,28777", "answer": "28778"}
{"prompt": "13647,13648,13649,13650,13651,13652,13653,13654", "answer": "13655"}
{"prompt": "9486,9487,9488,9489,9490,9491,9492", "answer": "9493"}
{"prompt": "24109,24110,24111,24112,24113,24114,24115", "answer": "24116"}
{"prompt": "44892,44893", "answer": "44894"}
{"prompt": "44638,44639,44640", "answer": "44641"}
{"prompt": "20670,20671,20672,20673,20674,20675,20676,20677", "answer": "20678"}
{"prompt": "31881,31882,31883,31884,31885,31886,31887,31888", "answer": "31889"}
{"prompt": "8404,8405,8406,8407,8408,8409,8410,8411,8412,8413", "answer": "8414"}
{"prompt": "4999,5000,5001", "answer": "5002"}
{"prompt": "35643,35644,35645,35646,35647", "answer": "35648"}
{"prompt": "33283,33284,33285,33286,33287,33288", "answer": "33289"}
{"prompt": "29159,29160,29161,29162,29163", "answer": "29164"}
{"prompt": "11079,11080,11081", "answer": "11082"}
{"prompt": "23908,23909,23910", "answer": "23911"}
{"prompt": "11012,11013,11014,11015,11016", "answer": "11017"}
{"prompt": "11144,11145,11146,11147,11148,11149,11150", "answer": "11151"}
{"prompt": "137,138", "answer": "139"}
{"prompt": "5659,5660,5661,5662", "answer": "5663"}
{"prompt": "19656,19657,19658,19659,19660,19661,19662", "answer": "19663"}
{"prompt": "41845,41846,41847,41848,41849", "answer": "41850"}
{"prompt": "37181,37182,37183,37184,37185,37186,37187,37188", "answer": "37189"}
{"prompt": "20100,20101,20102,20103,20104,20105,20106,20107,20108,20109", "answer": "20110"}
{"prompt": "7738,7739,7740,7741,7742,7743,7744", "answer": "7745"}
{"prompt": "45071,45072,45073,45074,45075,45076,45077", "answer": "45078"}
{"prompt": "21301,21302,21303,21304,21305", "answer": "21306"}
{"prompt": "22422", "answer": "22423"}
{"prompt": "11251,11252", "answer": "11253"}
{"prompt": "31733,31734,31735,31736,31737,31738", "answer": "31739"}
{"prompt": "13613,13614", "answer": "13615"}
{"prompt": "24991,24992", "answer": "24993"}
{"prompt": "39473,39474,39475,39476,39477,39478,39479,39480", "answer": "39481"}
{"prompt": "31977,31978,31979,31980", "answer": "31981"}
{"prompt": "13382,13383,13384,13385,13386,13387,13388,13389", "answer": "13390"}
{"prompt": "11308", "answer": "11309"}
{"prompt": "3166,3167,3168,3169,3170,3171", "answer": "3172"}
{"prompt": "6302,6303,6304,6305,6306", "answer": "6307"}
{"prompt": "26883,26884,26885,26886,26887,26888,26889", "answer": "26890"}
{"prompt": "8782,8783,8784,8785,8786,8787,8788,8789,8790,8791", "answer": "8792"}
{"prompt": "24919,24920,24921,24922,24923", "answer": "24924"}
{"prompt": "5650,5651", "answer": "5652"}
{"prompt": "26681,26682,26683,26684", "answer": "26685"}
{"prompt": "20949,20950,20951,20952", "answer": "20953"}
{"prompt": "7572,7573,7574,7575,7576,7577", "answer": "7578"}
{"prompt": "16698,16699,16700,16701,16702,16703,16704", "answer": "16705"}
{"prompt": "8167,8168,8169,8170,8171,8172", "answer": "8173"}
{"prompt": "12683,12684,12685,12686,12687,12688,12689,12690,12691", "answer": "12692"}
{"prompt": "36631,36632", "answer": "36633"}
{"prompt": "8342,8343", "answer": "8344"}
{"prompt": "28752,28753,28754", "answer": "28755"}
{"prompt": "16796,16797,16798,16799,16800,16801", "answer": "16802"}
{"prompt": "43413,43414,43415,43416,43417", "answer": "43418"}
{"prompt": "43205,43206", "answer": "43207"}
{"prompt": "11059", "answer": "11060"}
{"prompt": "28805,28806,28807,28808,28809,28810,28811,28812,28813,28814", "answer": "28815"}
{"prompt": "31859,31860,31861", "answer": "31862"}
{"prompt": "16841,16842", "answer": "16843"}
{"prompt": "1690,1691,1692,1693", "answer": "1694"}
{"prompt": "16684,16685,16686,16687", "answer": "16688"}
{"prompt": "62,63,64,65,66,67,68,69,70", "answer": "71"}
{"prompt": "10623,10624,10625,10626", "answer": "10627"}
{"prompt": "31066,31067", "answer": "31068"}
{"prompt": "38071,38072,38073,38074,38075,38076", "answer": "38077"}
{"prompt": "7652", "answer": "7653"}
{"prompt": "22055,22056,22057,22058,22059,22060,22061,22062", "answer": "22063"}
{"prompt": "40548,40549,40550,40551,40552", "answer": "40553"}
{"prompt": "7672,7673", "answer": "7674"}
{"prompt": "3258,3259,3260,3261,3262,3263", "answer": "3264"}
{"prompt": "1512,1513,1514,1515,1516", "answer": "1517"}
{"prompt": "44900,44901,44902,44903,44904,44905,44906", "answer": "44907"}
{"prompt": "40471,40472,40473,40474,40475,40476,40477,40478", "answer": "40479"}
{"prompt": "19822,19823,19824,19825,19826,19827", "answer": "19828"}
{"prompt": "40468,40469,40470,40471", "answer": "40472"}
{"prompt": "4115,4116,4117", "answer": "4118"}
{"prompt": "18092,18093,18094", "answer": "18095"}
{"prompt": "11580,11581,11582,11583,11584,11585,11586,11587", "answer": "11588"}
{"prompt": "35680,35681,35682,35683,35684", "answer": "35685"}
{"prompt": "24785,24786,24787,24788,24789", "answer": "24790"}
{"prompt": "22907,22908,22909,22910,22911,22912,22913", "answer": "22914"}
{"prompt": "12222,12223", "answer": "12224"}
{"prompt": "45093,45094,45095,45096,45097,45098,45099,45100,45101", "answer": "45102"}
{"prompt": "35804,35805,35806,35807,35808,35809,35810", "answer": "35811"}
{"prompt": "10431,10432,10433,10434,10435", "answer": "10436"}
{"prompt": "15166,15167,15168,15169,15170,15171,15172", "answer": "15173"}
{"prompt": "6308,6309,6310,6311,6312", "answer": "6313"}
{"prompt": "25216,25217", "answer": "25218"}
{"prompt": "40397,40398,40399,40400,40401,40402", "answer": "40403"}
{"prompt": "42204,42205,42206,42207", "answer": "42208"}
{"prompt": "667", "answer": "668"}
{"prompt": "965,966", "answer": "967"}
{"prompt": "10681,10682,10683,10684,10685,10686", "answer": "10687"}
{"prompt": "19844,19845,19846,19847,19848,19849,19850,19851,19852,19853", "answer": "19854"}
{"prompt": "6194,6195,6196,6197,6198,6199,6200,6201,6202", "answer": "6203"}
{"prompt": "43944,43945,43946,43947,43948,43949,43950", "answer": "43951"}
{"prompt": "9894,9895,9896,9897,9898,9899,9900,9901,9902", "answer": "9903"}
{"prompt": "3189,3190,3191,3192,3193,3194,3195,3196", "answer": "3197"}
{"prompt": "966,967", "answer": "968"}
{"prompt": "44159,44160,44161,44162,44163,44164,44165,44166,44167", "answer": "44168"}
{"prompt": "1476,1477,1478,1479,1480", "answer": "1481"}
{"prompt": "28687,28688,28689,28690,28691,28692,28693,28694,28695", "answer": "28696"}
{"prompt": "28209,28210,28211,28212,28213,28214,28215,28216,28217,28218", "answer": "28219"}
{"prompt": "7416,7417,7418", "answer": "7419"}
{"prompt": "843", "answer": "844"}
{"prompt": "10311,10312,10313,10314", "answer": "10315"}
{"prompt": "39181,39182,39183,39184,39185,39186,39187", "answer": "39188"}
{"prompt": "7453,7454,7455,7456,7457,7458,7459,7460,7461,7462", "answer": "7463"}
{"prompt": "30084,30085,30086,30087,30088,30089,30090", "answer": "30091"}
{"prompt": "33927,33928,33929,33930", "answer": "33931"}
{"prompt": "18215,18216,18217,18218,18219,18220,18221,18222,18223", "answer": "18224"}
{"prompt": "31798,31799,31800,31801,31802,31803,31804,31805,31806,31807", "answer": "31808"}
{"prompt": "5348,5349,5350,5351,5352,5353", "answer": "5354"}
{"prompt": "10743,10744,10745,10746", "answer": "10747"}
{"prompt": "5167,5168,5169,5170,5171,5172,5173,5174,5175,5176", "answer": "5177"}
{"prompt": "14138", "answer": "14139"}
{"prompt": "29426,29427,29428,29429,29430,29431,29432,29433", "answer": "29434"}
{"prompt": "13351,13352,13353,13354,13355,13356,13357,13358", "answer": "13359"}
{"prompt": "12217,12218,12219,12220,12221", "answer": "12222"}
{"prompt": "23112,23113,23114,23115", "answer": "23116"}
{"prompt": "1505,1506,1507,1508,1509", "answer": "1510"}
{"prompt": "20966,20967", "answer": "20968"}
{"prompt": "13541,13542,13543,13544,13545,13546,13547", "answer": "13548"}
{"prompt": "36539,36540,36541,36542,36543", "answer": "36544"}
{"prompt": "14214,14215,14216,14217", "answer": "14218"}
{"prompt": "13223,13224,13225,13226,13227,13228,13229,13230,13231,13232", "answer": "13233"}
{"prompt": "13912,13913,13914,13915,13916,13917", "answer": "13918"}
{"prompt": "34237,34238,34239,34240,34241,34242,34243,34244,34245", "answer": "34246"}
{"prompt": "13623,13624", "answer": "13625"}
{"prompt": "36934,36935,36936", "answer": "36937"}
{"prompt": "6951,6952", "answer": "6953"}
{"prompt": "35688", "answer": "35689"}
{"prompt": "11126,11127,11128", "answer": "11129"}
{"prompt": "27490,27491,27492,27493,27494,27495", "answer": "27496"}
{"prompt": "32329,32330,32331,32332,32333,32334,32335,32336,32337,32338", "answer": "32339"}
{"prompt": "17179,17180,17181,17182,17183,17184,17185,17186", "answer": "17187"}
{"prompt": "33238,33239,33240,33241,33242,33243", "answer": "33244"}
{"prompt": "11671,11672,11673,11674,11675", "answer": "11676"}
{"prompt": "29541,29542,29543,29544", "answer": "29545"}
{"prompt": "15267,15268", "answer": "15269"}
{"prompt": "19922,19923,19924", "answer": "19925"}
{"prompt": "24224,24225,24226", "answer": "24227"}
{"prompt": "16413,16414,16415", "answer": "16416"}
{"prompt": "32968,32969", "answer": "32970"}
{"prompt": "15409", "answer": "15410"}
{"prompt": "41017", "answer": "41018"}
{"prompt": "19089,19090,19091,19092,19093", "answer": "19094"}
{"prompt": "28538,28539,28540,28541", "answer": "28542"}
{"prompt": "7905,7906", "answer": "7907"}
{"prompt": "40024,40025,40026", "answer": "40027"}
{"prompt": "1095,1096,1097,1098,1099,1100,1101,1102", "answer": "1103"}
{"prompt": "18983,18984,18985,18986,18987,18988,18989,18990", "answer": "18991"}
{"prompt": "13268,13269,13270,13271,13272,13273", "answer": "13274"}
{"prompt": "20774,20775,20776,20777", "answer": "20778"}
{"prompt": "16316,16317,16318,16319,16320,16321", "answer": "16322"}
{"prompt": "26534,26535,26536,26537,26538,26539,26540,26541,26542", "answer": "26543"}
{"prompt": "731,732,733", "answer": "734"}
{"prompt": "4224,4225,4226,4227,4228,4229", "answer": "4230"}
{"prompt": "24257,24258,24259,24260,24261,24262,24263", "answer": "24264"}
{"prompt": "21897,21898,21899,21900", "answer": "21901"}
{"prompt": "30573,30574,30575", "answer": "30576"}
{"prompt": "10007,10008,10009,10010,10011,10012,10013,10014,10015", "answer": "10016"}
{"prompt": "19555,19556,19557,19558,19559,19560,19561", "answer": "19562"}
{"prompt": "40903,40904,40905", "answer": "40906"}
{"prompt": "6162,6163,6164,6165,6166", "answer": "6167"}
{"prompt": "24248,24249,24250,24251,24252,24253,24254,24255,24256,24257", "answer": "24258"}
{"prompt": "27532,27533,27534,27535,27536,27537", "answer": "27538"}
{"prompt": "25894,25895,25896", "answer": "25897"}
{"prompt": "81,82,83,84,85,86,87", "answer": "88"}
{"prompt": "8623,8624,8625,8626,8627,8628,8629,8630,8631,8632", "answer": "8633"}
{"prompt": "39823,39824", "answer": "39825"}
{"prompt": "15677,15678,15679,15680,15681", "answer": "15682"}
{"prompt": "18497,18498,18499,18500,18501,18502,18503,18504,18505,18506", "answer": "18507"}
{"prompt": "3804,3805,3806,3807", "answer": "3808"}
{"prompt": "20040,20041,20042,20043,20044,20045,20046,20047,20048", "answer": "20049"}
{"prompt": "9953,9954,9955", "answer": "9956"}
{"prompt": "20623,20624,20625,20626,20627", "answer": "20628"}
{"prompt": "11111,11112,11113,11114,11115,11116,11117", "answer": "11118"}
{"prompt": "2847,2848,2849,2850,2851,2852,2853,2854,2855", "answer": "2856"}
{"prompt": "21651,21652,21653,21654,21655,21656,21657,21658,21659", "answer": "21660"}
{"prompt": "17703,17704,17705,17706,17707,17708,17709,17710,17711,17712", "answer": "17713"}
{"prompt": "42162,42163,42164,42165,42166,42167", "answer": "42168"}
{"prompt": "3348,3349", "answer": "3350"}
{"prompt": "16642,16643,16644,16645,16646,16647,16648", "answer": "16649"}
{"prompt": "12800,12801,12802", "answer": "12803"}
{"prompt": "8842,8843,8844,8845,8846,8847", "answer": "8848"}
{"prompt": "41098,41099,41100,41101,41102,41103,41104,41105,41106,41107", "answer": "41108"}
{"prompt": "19912,19913", "answer": "19914"}
{"prompt": "22022,22023,22024,22025,22026,22027,22028", "answer": "22029"}
{"prompt": "16390", "answer": "16391"}
{"prompt": "22579,22580,22581,22582,22583,22584,22585", "answer": "22586"}
{"prompt": "19183,19184", "answer": "19185"}
{"prompt": "39066,39067,39068,39069", "answer": "39070"}
{"prompt": "37507", "answer": "37508"}
{"prompt": "33943,33944,33945,33946,33947,33948,33949,33950,33951,33952", "answer": "33953"}
{"prompt": "38160", "answer": "38161"}
{"prompt": "42997,42998,42999,43000,43001,43002,43003,43004", "answer": "43005"}
{"prompt": "16203", "answer": "16204"}
{"prompt": "12004,12005,12006", "answer": "12007"}
{"prompt": "234,235,236,237,238", "answer": "239"}
{"prompt": "13835,13836,13837,13838,13839,13840,13841", "answer": "13842"}
{"prompt": "15465,15466,15467,15468,15469,15470,15471,15472,15473", "answer": "15474"}
{"prompt": "20152,20153,20154,20155", "answer": "20156"}
{"prompt": "29975,29976,29977,29978,29979,29980,29981", "answer": "29982"}
{"prompt": "29127,29128,29129,29130,29131,29132,29133,29134,29135", "answer": "29136"}
{"prompt": "43979,43980,43981,43982", "answer": "43983"}
{"prompt": "28699,28700,28701,28702,28703,28704,28705,28706,28707,28708", "answer": "28709"}
{"prompt": "37914,37915,37916,37917,37918", "answer": "37919"}
{"prompt": "32629", "answer": "32630"}
{"prompt": "12386,12387,12388,12389", "answer": "12390"}
{"prompt": "5570,5571,5572,5573,5574,5575", "answer": "5576"}
{"prompt": "38225,38226,38227,38228,38229,38230,38231", "answer": "38232"}
{"prompt": "39630,39631,39632,39633,39634,39635,39636,39637", "answer": "39638"}
{"prompt": "44554,44555,44556", "answer": "44557"}
{"prompt": "29713,29714,29715,29716,29717,29718,29719,29720,29721,29722", "answer": "29723"}
{"prompt": "14313,14314,14315,14316", "answer": "14317"}
{"prompt": "4497,4498,4499,4500,4501,4502", "answer": "4503"}
{"prompt": "3334,3335,3336,3337,3338,3339,3340,3341", "answer": "3342"}
{"prompt": "21490,21491,21492,21493,21494,21495,21496,21497,21498,21499", "answer": "21500"}
{"prompt": "9609,9610,9611,9612,9613,9614", "answer": "9615"}
{"prompt": "20365", "answer": "20366"}
{"prompt": "12504,12505,12506,12507,12508,12509,12510,12511", "answer": "12512"}
{"prompt": "1556,1557,1558,1559,1560", "answer": "1561"}
{"prompt": "37507,37508,37509,37510,37511", "answer": "37512"}
{"prompt": "38978,38979,38980", "answer": "38981"}
{"prompt": "31322,31323,31324,31325,31326,31327", "answer": "31328"}
{"prompt": "36009,36010,36011,36012,36013", "answer": "36014"}
{"prompt": "5033,5034,5035,5036,5037", "answer": "5038"}
{"prompt": "32512,32513,32514,32515,32516,32517,32518,32519", "answer": "32520"}
{"prompt": "8706,8707,8708,8709,8710,8711", "answer": "8712"}
{"prompt": "33427,33428", "answer": "33429"}
{"prompt": "27292,27293,27294", "answer": "27295"}
{"prompt": "25881,25882,25883,25884,25885,25886,25887,25888,25889", "answer": "25890"}
{"prompt": "41693,41694,41695,41696,41697,41698,41699,41700,41701,41702", "answer": "41703"}
{"prompt": "18758,18759,18760,18761,18762,18763", "answer": "18764"}
{"prompt": "40992,40993,40994,40995,40996,40997,40998,40999", "answer": "41000"}
{"prompt": "31253,31254,31255,31256,31257,31258,31259,31260", "answer": "31261"}
{"prompt": "14427,14428,14429,14430,14431,14432,14433,14434", "answer": "14435"}
{"prompt": "45016,45017,45018,45019,45020,45021,45022,45023,45024,45025", "answer": "45026"}
{"prompt": "3196,3197,3198,3199,3200,3201,3202,3203,3204,3205", "answer": "3206"}
{"prompt": "11513,11514,11515,11516,11517,11518,11519,11520", "answer": "11521"}
{"prompt": "39744,39745,39746", "answer": "39747"}
{"prompt": "15141,15142,15143,15144,15145,15146", "answer": "15147"}
{"prompt": "35326", "answer": "35327"}
{"prompt": "22421,22422", "answer": "22423"}
{"prompt": "25574,25575,25576,25577,25578,25579,25580", "answer": "25581"}
{"prompt": "40699,40700,40701,40702,40703", "answer": "40704"}
{"prompt": "5560,5561,5562,5563,5564,5565,5566,5567", "answer": "5568"}
{"prompt": "7347,7348,7349,7350,7351,7352", "answer": "7353"}
{"prompt": "33230,33231,33232", "answer": "33233"}
{"prompt": "14531", "answer": "14532"}
{"prompt": "14326,14327,14328,14329,14330,14331,14332", "answer": "14333"}
{"prompt": "2972,2973,2974,2975,2976,2977,2978", "answer": "2979"}
{"prompt": "8931,8932,8933,8934,8935,8936", "answer": "8937"}
{"prompt": "9736,9737,9738,9739,9740", "answer": "9741"}
{"prompt": "7898,7899,7900,7901,7902,7903,7904,7905", "answer": "7906"}
{"prompt": "6466,6467,6468,6469,6470,6471,6472,6473", "answer": "6474"}
{"prompt": "28695,28696,28697,28698,28699", "answer": "28700"}
{"prompt": "15681,15682", "answer": "15683"}
{"prompt": "20492", "answer": "20493"}
{"prompt": "17712,17713,17714,17715,17716,17717,17718", "answer": "17719"}
{"prompt": "27746,27747,27748", "answer": "27749"}
{"prompt": "39359,39360,39361,39362,39363,39364,39365,39366,39367", "answer": "39368"}
{"prompt": "26957,26958,26959,26960,26961,26962,26963,26964,26965", "answer": "26966"}
{"prompt": "26889,26890,26891,26892", "answer": "26893"}
{"prompt": "42791,42792,42793,42794,42795,42796,42797,42798,42799", "answer": "42800"}
{"prompt": "9719,9720,9721", "answer": "9722"}
{"prompt": "41081,41082,41083,41084", "answer": "41085"}
{"prompt": "42702,42703,42704,42705,42706,42707,42708,42709", "answer": "42710"}
{"prompt": "7210,7211,7212,7213,7214", "answer": "7215"}
{"prompt": "8275,8276,8277,8278,8279,8280,8281,8282", "answer": "8283"}
{"prompt": "22659,22660,22661,22662,22663", "answer": "22664"}
{"prompt": "24942,24943,24944,24945,24946,24947,24948,24949", "answer": "24950"}
{"prompt": "42386,42387", "answer": "42388"}
{"prompt": "36601,36602,36603", "answer": "36604"}
{"prompt": "18742,18743,18744,18745,18746,18747,18748,18749,18750", "answer": "18751"}
{"prompt": "13896,13897,13898,13899,13900,13901,13902,13903", "answer": "13904"}
{"prompt": "32120,32121,32122,32123", "answer": "32124"}
{"prompt": "7494,7495,7496", "answer": "7497"}
{"prompt": "20816,20817,20818,20819,20820,20821,20822,20823", "answer": "20824"}
{"prompt": "35143,35144,35145,35146,35147,35148,35149,35150,35151", "answer": "35152"}
{"prompt": "21171,21172,21173,21174,21175,21176,21177,21178", "answer": "21179"}
{"prompt": "15817,15818,15819,15820,15821,15822,15823,15824,15825,15826", "answer": "15827"}
{"prompt": "24009,24010,24011,24012,24013", "answer": "24014"}
{"prompt": "3833", "answer": "3834"}
{"prompt": "22,23", "answer": "24"}
{"prompt": "2959", "answer": "2960"}
{"prompt": "13639,13640,13641,13642,13643,13644", "answer": "13645"}
{"prompt": "3503,3504,3505,3506,3507,3508,3509,3510,3511", "answer": "3512"}
{"prompt": "23870,23871,23872,23873,23874,23875", "answer": "23876"}
{"prompt": "18343,18344,18345,18346,18347,18348,18349", "answer": "18350"}
{"prompt": "31245", "answer": "31246"}
{"prompt": "26180,26181,26182,26183,26184,26185,26186,26187,26188,26189", "answer": "26190"}
{"prompt": "20844,20845,20846,20847", "answer": "20848"}
{"prompt": "43964,43965,43966,43967", "answer": "43968"}
{"prompt": "19951,19952,19953,19954,19955,19956,19957", "answer": "19958"}
{"prompt": "8167", "answer": "8168"}
{"prompt": "22653,22654,22655,22656,22657,22658,22659", "answer": "22660"}
{"prompt": "3810,3811,3812,3813,3814", "answer": "3815"}
{"prompt": "44342,44343,44344,44345,44346", "answer": "44347"}
{"prompt": "37956", "answer": "37957"}
{"prompt": "4547,4548,4549", "answer": "4550"}
{"prompt": "35701,35702,35703,35704,35705,35706,35707", "answer": "35708"}
{"prompt": "31787,31788,31789,31790,31791,31792,31793,31794", "answer": "31795"}
{"prompt": "25065,25066", "answer": "25067"}
{"prompt": "16513", "answer": "16514"}
{"prompt": "17154,17155,17156,17157,17158,17159,17160,17161", "answer": "17162"}
{"prompt": "22829,22830,22831,22832,22833,22834,22835,22836,22837", "answer": "22838"}
{"prompt": "39060,39061,39062,39063,39064,39065,39066", "answer": "39067"}
{"prompt": "30502,30503,30504,30505,30506,30507,30508,30509", "answer": "30510"}
{"prompt": "28414,28415,28416", "answer": "28417"}
{"prompt": "43198,43199,43200,43201,43202,43203,43204,43205", "answer": "43206"}
{"prompt": "6734,6735,6736,6737,6738,6739", "answer": "6740"}
{"prompt": "14965,14966,14967,14968,14969,14970", "answer": "14971"}
{"prompt": "1244,1245", "answer": "1246"}
{"prompt": "31795,31796,31797", "answer": "31798"}
{"prompt": "10975,10976,10977,10978,10979,10980,10981", "answer": "10982"}
{"prompt": "14466,14467,14468,14469,14470,14471,14472,14473", "answer": "14474"}
{"prompt": "20356,20357", "answer": "20358"}
{"prompt": "2794,2795,2796,2797,2798,2799", "answer": "2800"}
{"prompt": "30006,30007,30008,30009,30010,30011,30012,30013,30014", "answer": "30015"}
{"prompt": "9911,9912,9913,9914,9915,9916,9917", "answer": "9918"}
{"prompt": "8939,8940,8941,8942,8943,8944", "answer": "8945"}
{"prompt": "17026,17027", "answer": "17028"}
{"prompt": "11150,11151,11152,11153,11154,11155,11156,11157,11158", "answer": "11159"}
{"prompt": "14200,14201,14202,14203,14204,14205,14206,14207,14208,14209", "answer": "14210"}
{"prompt": "13603,13604,13605,13606", "answer": "13607"}
{"prompt": "44579,44580,44581,44582", "answer": "44583"}
{"prompt": "7686,7687", "answer": "7688"}
{"prompt": "35294,35295,35296,35297,35298,35299,35300,35301", "answer": "35302"}
{"prompt": "14875", "answer": "14876"}
{"prompt": "32006,32007,32008", "answer": "32009"}
{"prompt": "18376,18377,18378,18379,18380,18381", "answer": "18382"}
{"prompt": "19503,19504,19505,19506,19507,19508", "answer": "19509"}
{"prompt": "8539,8540,8541", "answer": "8542"}
{"prompt": "20890,20891,20892,20893,20894,20895,20896,20897,20898", "answer": "20899"}
{"prompt": "18543,18544,18545,18546,18547,18548,18549,18550,18551,18552", "answer": "18553"}
{"prompt": "14062,14063,14064,14065,14066,14067,14068,14069,14070", "answer": "14071"}
{"prompt": "38054,38055,38056,38057,38058,38059,38060", "answer": "38061"}
{"prompt": "11421,11422,11423,11424,11425,11426,11427,11428,11429", "answer": "11430"}
{"prompt": "18416,18417,18418", "answer": "18419"}
{"prompt": "31988,31989,31990", "answer": "31991"}
{"prompt": "44192,44193,44194,44195,44196,44197", "answer": "44198"}
{"prompt": "45263,45264,45265", "answer": "45266"}
{"prompt": "20969,20970,20971,20972,20973,20974,20975,20976,20977", "answer": "20978"}
{"prompt": "21472,21473,21474,21475,21476,21477", "answer": "21478"}
{"prompt": "35787,35788", "answer": "35789"}
{"prompt": "32371,32372,32373,32374", "answer": "32375"}
{"prompt": "566,567,568,569,570", "answer": "571"}
{"prompt": "32030,32031,32032,32033,32034,32035", "answer": "32036"}
{"prompt": "25505,25506,25507,25508", "answer": "25509"}
{"prompt": "3830,3831", "answer": "3832"}
{"prompt": "17559,17560,17561,17562,17563,17564,17565", "answer": "17566"}
{"prompt": "967,968,969,970,971,972,973", "answer": "974"}
{"prompt": "37231,37232,37233,37234,37235", "answer": "37236"}
{"prompt": "25645,25646,25647,25648,25649,25650,25651,25652,25653,25654", "answer": "25655"}
{"prompt": "11663,11664,11665,11666", "answer": "11667"}
{"prompt": "9383,9384,9385,9386,9387,9388,9389,9390,9391", "answer": "9392"}
{"prompt": "1510,1511,1512", "answer": "1513"}
{"prompt": "8020,8021,8022,8023,8024,8025,8026,8027,8028", "answer": "8029"}
{"prompt": "8150,8151,8152,8153,8154,8155,8156,8157", "answer": "8158"}
{"prompt": "9831,9832,9833,9834,9835", "answer": "9836"}
{"prompt": "29029,29030,29031,29032,29033,29034,29035,29036,29037,29038", "answer": "29039"}
{"prompt": "37361", "answer": "37362"}
{"prompt": "29902,29903,29904,29905,29906,29907,29908,29909,29910", "answer": "29911"}
{"prompt": "24267,24268,24269,24270,24271,24272", "answer": "24273"}
{"prompt": "44766,44767,44768,44769,44770", "answer": "44771"}
{"prompt": "36906,36907,36908,36909", "answer": "36910"}
{"prompt": "40969,40970,40971,40972,40973,40974,40975,40976,40977,40978", "answer": "40979"}
{"prompt": "36442,36443,36444,36445,36446,36447,36448,36449", "answer": "36450"}
{"prompt": "31460,31461,31462,31463,31464,31465,31466,31467,31468", "answer": "31469"}
{"prompt": "44272,44273,44274,44275,44276,44277,44278,44279,44280", "answer": "44281"}
{"prompt": "19689,19690,19691,19692,19693,19694,19695,19696", "answer": "19697"}
{"prompt": "35707,35708,35709,35710", "answer": "35711"}
{"prompt": "14920,14921,14922,14923", "answer": "14924"}
{"prompt": "12012,12013,12014,12015", "answer": "12016"}
{"prompt": "2251,2252", "answer": "2253"}
{"prompt": "24739,24740,24741,24742,24743,24744,24745", "answer": "24746"}
{"prompt": "31459,31460", "answer": "31461"}
{"prompt": "29460,29461,29462,29463,29464,29465,29466,29467,29468,29469", "answer": "29470"}
{"prompt": "10015,10016,10017,10018,10019,10020", "answer": "10021"}
{"prompt": "2913,2914,2915,2916,2917", "answer": "2918"}
{"prompt": "21140,21141,21142,21143,21144,21145,21146,21147,21148", "answer": "21149"}
{"prompt": "14271,14272,14273,14274,14275", "answer": "14276"}
{"prompt": "8212,8213,8214,8215,8216", "answer": "8217"}
{"prompt": "14875,14876,14877,14878,14879", "answer": "14880"}
{"prompt": "26806,26807,26808,26809,26810,26811,26812", "answer": "26813"}
{"prompt": "388,389,390,391,392,393,394", "answer": "395"}
{"prompt": "32338,32339,32340,32341,32342,32343,32344,32345,32346", "answer": "32347"}
{"prompt": "26394,26395,26396,26397,26398,26399,26400,26401,26402", "answer": "26403"}
{"prompt": "43918,43919,43920,43921,43922,43923,43924", "answer": "43925"}
{"prompt": "12130,12131", "answer": "12132"}
{"prompt": "32748,32749,32750,32751,32752,32753", "answer": "32754"}
{"prompt": "32692,32693", "answer": "32694"}
{"prompt": "8085,8086", "answer": "8087"}
{"prompt": "19970,19971,19972,19973,19974,19975", "answer": "19976"}
{"prompt": "44067,44068,44069,44070,44071,44072", "answer": "44073"}
{"prompt": "13674,13675,13676,13677,13678,13679", "answer": "13680"}
{"prompt": "31946,31947,31948,31949,31950,31951", "answer": "31952"}
{"prompt": "27189,27190,27191,27192,27193", "answer": "27194"}
{"prompt": "22239", "answer": "22240"}
{"prompt": "27938,27939,27940,27941,27942,27943,27944,27945", "answer": "27946"}
{"prompt": "29526,29527,29528,29529,29530,29531,29532,29533,29534,29535", "answer": "29536"}
{"prompt": "35020,35021,35022,35023,35024,35025,35026,35027", "answer": "35028"}
{"prompt": "16809,16810,16811,16812,16813,16814", "answer": "16815"}
{"prompt": "18596,18597,18598", "answer": "18599"}
{"prompt": "11666,11667,11668,11669,11670,11671", "answer": "11672"}
{"prompt": "487,488", "answer": "489"}
{"prompt": "36321,36322,36323,36324,36325,36326,36327,36328,36329", "answer": "36330"}
{"prompt": "9214,9215,9216,9217,9218,9219", "answer": "9220"}
{"prompt": "30748,30749,30750,30751,30752", "answer": "30753"}
{"prompt": "11520", "answer": "11521"}
{"prompt": "38259,38260,38261,38262", "answer": "38263"}
{"prompt": "39384,39385,39386", "answer": "39387"}
{"prompt": "6293,6294,6295,6296,6297,6298,6299,6300,6301,6302", "answer": "6303"}
{"prompt": "14801,14802,14803,14804,14805,14806,14807", "answer": "14808"}
{"prompt": "36645,36646,36647", "answer": "36648"}
{"prompt": "32114,32115,32116,32117,32118,32119,32120", "answer": "32121"}
{"prompt": "7544,7545,7546,7547", "answer": "7548"}
{"prompt": "622,623,624,625,626,627,628,629,630", "answer": "631"}
{"prompt": "26448,26449,26450,26451,26452,26453,26454,26455,26456", "answer": "26457"}
{"prompt": "30051,30052,30053,30054,30055,30056,30057", "answer": "30058"}
{"prompt": "14006,14007,14008,14009,14010", "answer": "14011"}
{"prompt": "26082", "answer": "26083"}
{"prompt": "342,343,344,345", "answer": "346"}
{"prompt": "7963", "answer": "7964"}
{"prompt": "26406,26407,26408,26409,26410,26411,26412", "answer": "26413"}
{"prompt": "44110,44111,44112,44113,44114", "answer": "44115"}
{"prompt": "24521,24522,24523", "answer": "24524"}
{"prompt": "34317,34318,34319", "answer": "34320"}
{"prompt": "394,395,396,397,398,399,400,401", "answer": "402"}
{"prompt": "26562,26563,26564,26565", "answer": "26566"}
{"prompt": "4244", "answer": "4245"}
{"prompt": "36391", "answer": "36392"}
{"prompt": "34462,34463,34464", "answer": "34465"}
{"prompt": "2554,2555,2556,2557,2558,2559,2560,2561,2562", "answer": "2563"}
{"prompt": "38348,38349,38350,38351", "answer": "38352"}
{"prompt": "22692", "answer": "22693"}
{"prompt": "16168,16169,16170,16171", "answer": "16172"}
{"prompt": "29388,29389,29390,29391,29392,29393", "answer": "29394"}
{"prompt": "42292,42293,42294,42295,42296,42297,42298,42299,42300,42301", "answer": "42302"}
{"prompt": "138,139", "answer": "140"}
{"prompt": "15896,15897", "answer": "15898"}
{"prompt": "19606,19607", "answer": "19608"}
{"prompt": "21804,21805,21806,21807", "answer": "21808"}
{"prompt": "36032,36033,36034,36035", "answer": "36036"}
{"prompt": "22228,22229,22230,22231,22232,22233,22234,22235,22236,22237", "answer": "22238"}
{"prompt": "21535,21536,21537", "answer": "21538"}
{"prompt": "8738", "answer": "8739"}
{"prompt": "40160,40161,40162,40163", "answer": "40164"}
{"prompt": "18571,18572", "answer": "18573"}
{"prompt": "25184", "answer": "25185"}
{"prompt": "8413,8414,8415,8416,8417,8418,8419", "answer": "8420"}
{"prompt": "27869,27870,27871,27872,27873,27874,27875,27876,27877,27878", "answer": "27879"}
{"prompt": "12766,12767,12768", "answer": "12769"}
{"prompt": "28297,28298,28299,28300,28301,28302,28303,28304,28305", "answer": "28306"}
{"prompt": "36900,36901,36902,36903,36904,36905,36906", "answer": "36907"}
{"prompt": "31568,31569,31570,31571,31572,31573,31574,31575,31576,31577", "answer": "31578"}
{"prompt": "3746,3747,3748,3749,3750,3751,3752,3753", "answer": "3754"}
{"prompt": "26358,26359,26360,26361", "answer": "26362"}
{"prompt": "38238,38239,38240", "answer": "38241"}
{"prompt": "9987,9988,9989,9990,9991,9992,9993,9994", "answer": "9995"}
{"prompt": "27376,27377,27378", "answer": "27379"}
{"prompt": "5576,5577,5578,5579,5580,5581", "answer": "5582"}
{"prompt": "13107,13108,13109,13110,13111,13112,13113,13114", "answer": "13115"}
{"prompt": "44522,44523,44524,44525", "answer": "44526"}
{"prompt": "38965,38966", "answer": "38967"}
{"prompt": "12611,12612,12613,12614,12615,12616,12617,12618", "answer": "12619"}
{"prompt": "33435,33436,33437", "answer": "33438"}
{"prompt": "3068,3069,3070,3071,3072,3073,3074,3075", "answer": "3076"}
{"prompt": "39305,39306", "answer": "39307"}
{"prompt": "18123,18124,18125,18126,18127", "answer": "18128"}
{"prompt": "25708,25709,25710,25711,25712,25713,25714,25715,25716", "answer": "25717"}
{"prompt": "39808", "answer": "39809"}
{"prompt": "31718,31719", "answer": "31720"}
{"prompt": "499,500,501,502,503,504,505,506,507,508", "answer": "509"}
{"prompt": "14311,14312,14313", "answer": "14314"}
{"prompt": "990,991,992,993,994,995,996,997", "answer": "998"}
{"prompt": "30355", "answer": "30356"}
{"prompt": "9276,9277,9278,9279", "answer": "9280"}
{"prompt": "39628,39629,39630", "answer": "39631"}
{"prompt": "38306,38307", "answer": "38308"}
{"prompt": "37062,37063,37064,37065,37066,37067,37068,37069", "answer": "37070"}
{"prompt": "35739,35740,35741,35742,35743,35744", "answer": "35745"}
{"prompt": "10246,10247,10248,10249", "answer": "10250"}
{"prompt": "37863,37864,37865", "answer": "37866"}
{"prompt": "31648,31649,31650,31651", "answer": "31652"}
{"prompt": "752,753,754,755,756", "answer": "757"}
{"prompt": "36710,36711", "answer": "36712"}
{"prompt": "41269,41270,41271,41272,41273", "answer": "41274"}
{"prompt": "21212,21213,21214,21215,21216,21217,21218", "answer": "21219"}
{"prompt": "6276,6277,6278,6279,6280,6281,6282,6283,6284,6285", "answer": "6286"}
{"prompt": "4230,4231,4232,4233,4234,4235,4236", "answer": "4237"}
{"prompt": "42810,42811,42812,42813,42814,42815", "answer": "42816"}
{"prompt": "12362,12363,12364", "answer": "12365"}
{"prompt": "6944,6945,6946,6947,6948,6949,6950,6951", "answer": "6952"}
{"prompt": "17833,17834,17835,17836,17837,17838,17839,17840", "answer": "17841"}
{"prompt": "5682,5683,5684", "answer": "5685"}
{"prompt": "5867,5868,5869,5870,5871,5872,5873,5874", "answer": "5875"}
{"prompt": "6664,6665,6666,6667,6668,6669,6670,6671,6672,6673", "answer": "6674"}
{"prompt": "23307,23308,23309,23310,23311,23312,23313,23314,23315", "answer": "23316"}
{"prompt": "30441,30442,30443,30444,30445", "answer": "30446"}
{"prompt": "22751,22752,22753,22754,22755,22756,22757", "answer": "22758"}
{"prompt": "6433,6434,6435,6436,6437", "answer": "6438"}
{"prompt": "22717,22718", "answer": "22719"}
{"prompt": "16976,16977,16978,16979,16980,16981,16982,16983,16984,16985", "answer": "16986"}
{"prompt": "38758,38759,38760,38761,38762,38763", "answer": "38764"}
{"prompt": "31907,31908,31909,31910,31911,31912,31913", "answer": "31914"}
{"prompt": "20484,20485,20486,20487,20488,20489,20490,20491,20492", "answer": "20493"}
{"prompt": "21284,21285,21286,21287,21288,21289,21290,21291,21292", "answer": "21293"}
{"prompt": "37395,37396,37397,37398,37399,37400,37401,37402", "answer": "37403"}
{"prompt": "34866,34867,34868,34869,34870,34871", "answer": "34872"}
{"prompt": "26412,26413,26414,26415,26416", "answer": "26417"}
{"prompt": "32720", "answer": "32721"}
{"prompt": "13769,13770", "answer": "13771"}
{"prompt": "34122,34123,34124,34125,34126,34127,34128,34129,34130", "answer": "34131"}
{"prompt": "31260,31261,31262,31263,31264,31265,31266,31267", "answer": "31268"}
{"prompt": "18510,18511,18512,18513,18514,18515,18516,18517", "answer": "18518"}
{"prompt": "27634", "answer": "27635"}
{"prompt": "3885,3886,3887,3888", "answer": "3889"}
{"prompt": "19812,19813,19814,19815", "answer": "19816"}
{"prompt": "42199,42200,42201,42202,42203,42204", "answer": "42205"}
{"prompt": "28273,28274", "answer": "28275"}
{"prompt": "10686,10687,10688,10689", "answer": "10690"}
{"prompt": "9404,9405,9406,9407,9408,9409,9410,9411,9412,9413", "answer": "9414"}
{"prompt": "11656,11657,11658,11659,11660,11661,11662,11663", "answer": "11664"}
{"prompt": "38235,38236", "answer": "38237"}
{"prompt": "45308,45309,45310,45311,45312,45313,45314", "answer": "45315"}
{"prompt": "44823", "answer": "44824"}
{"prompt": "9492", "answer": "9493"}
{"prompt": "35499,35500,35501,35502,35503,35504,35505,35506", "answer": "35507"}
{"prompt": "30101,30102,30103,30104,30105,30106,30107,30108", "answer": "30109"}
{"prompt": "41065,41066,41067,41068,41069,41070,41071,41072", "answer": "41073"}
{"prompt": "39590,39591,39592,39593", "answer": "39594"}
{"prompt": "25722,25723,25724,25725,25726,25727", "answer": "25728"}
{"prompt": "44800,44801", "answer": "44802"}
{"prompt": "29085,29086,29087,29088,29089", "answer": "29090"}
{"prompt": "23727,23728,23729", "answer": "23730"}
{"prompt": "12778,12779,12780,12781,12782", "answer": "12783"}
{"prompt": "3532,3533,3534,3535", "answer": "3536"}
{"prompt": "7382", "answer": "7383"}
{"prompt": "20094,20095,20096,20097,20098,20099,20100", "answer": "20101"}
{"prompt": "41061", "answer": "41062"}
{"prompt": "20965,20966", "answer": "20967"}
{"prompt": "42579,42580,42581,42582,42583,42584", "answer": "42585"}
{"prompt": "26040", "answer": "26041"}
{"prompt": "39371,39372,39373,39374,39375,39376,39377,39378,39379", "answer": "39380"}
{"prompt": "7101,7102,7103,7104,7105,7106", "answer": "7107"}
{"prompt": "36477,36478,36479,36480", "answer": "36481"}
{"prompt": "22845,22846,22847,22848,22849,22850,22851,22852", "answer": "22853"}
{"prompt": "39158,39159,39160", "answer": "39161"}
{"prompt": "13188,13189,13190,13191,13192,13193,13194,13195,13196", "answer": "13197"}
{"prompt": "9185,9186,9187,9188", "answer": "9189"}
{"prompt": "7803,7804,7805,7806,7807,7808,7809,7810", "answer": "7811"}
{"prompt": "28260,28261,28262,28263,28264", "answer": "28265"}
{"prompt": "16529,16530,16531,16532,16533,16534,16535,16536,16537", "answer": "16538"}
{"prompt": "28150", "answer": "28151"}
{"prompt": "7290,7291", "answer": "7292"}
{"prompt": "698,699,700,701", "answer": "702"}
{"prompt": "20342,20343,20344,20345,20346,20347,20348", "answer": "20349"}
{"prompt": "16792,16793", "answer": "16794"}
{"prompt": "10988,10989,10990,10991,10992,10993,10994,10995,10996,10997", "answer": "10998"}
{"prompt": "20291,20292,20293,20294,20295,20296,20297,20298,20299", "answer": "20300"}
{"prompt": "24916", "answer": "24917"}
{"prompt": "27056,27057,27058,27059", "answer": "27060"}
{"prompt": "6583", "answer": "6584"}
{"prompt": "24613,24614,24615,24616", "answer": "24617"}
{"prompt": "4888,4889,4890,4891,4892,4893,4894", "answer": "4895"}
{"prompt": "30458,30459,30460,30461,30462,30463,30464,30465", "answer": "30466"}
{"prompt": "40844,40845,40846,40847,40848", "answer": "40849"}
{"prompt": "8164,8165,8166,8167", "answer": "8168"}
{"prompt": "39567,39568", "answer": "39569"}
{"prompt": "9269,9270,9271,9272,9273,9274,9275,9276", "answer": "9277"}
{"prompt": "20023,20024,20025", "answer": "20026"}
{"prompt": "5723,5724,5725,5726", "answer": "5727"}
{"prompt": "18392,18393,18394,18395,18396,18397,18398,18399", "answer": "18400"}
{"prompt": "1804,1805,1806,1807", "answer": "1808"}
{"prompt": "28278,28279,28280,28281,28282,28283", "answer": "28284"}
{"prompt": "32303,32304,32305,32306,32307", "answer": "32308"}
{"prompt": "23584", "answer": "23585"}
{"prompt": "11504,11505,11506,11507", "answer": "11508"}
{"prompt": "31373,31374,31375,31376", "answer": "31377"}
{"prompt": "12287,12288,12289,12290,12291,12292,12293,12294,12295", "answer": "12296"}
{"prompt": "38061,38062,38063,38064,38065,38066,38067", "answer": "38068"}
{"prompt": "41953,41954,41955,41956,41957,41958,41959,41960,41961,41962", "answer": "41963"}
{"prompt": "27791,27792,27793", "answer": "27794"}
{"prompt": "14510,14511,14512,14513,14514,14515,14516,14517,14518,14519", "answer": "14520"}
{"prompt": "19960,19961,19962,19963,19964,19965,19966,19967", "answer": "19968"}
{"prompt": "5241,5242,5243,5244,5245,5246", "answer": "5247"}
{"prompt": "15256,15257,15258,15259,15260,15261", "answer": "15262"}
{"prompt": "39912,39913,39914,39915,39916,39917,39918", "answer": "39919"}
{"prompt": "10721,10722", "answer": "10723"}
{"prompt": "31738,31739,31740,31741,31742,31743,31744,31745,31746", "answer": "31747"}
{"prompt": "18875,18876,18877,18878,18879,18880", "answer": "18881"}
{"prompt": "6166,6167,6168,6169,6170,6171,6172,6173,6174,6175", "answer": "6176"}
{"prompt": "34013,34014,34015,34016,34017,34018,34019,34020,34021,34022", "answer": "34023"}
{"prompt": "29910,29911,29912,29913,29914,29915,29916,29917,29918", "answer": "29919"}
{"prompt": "12235,12236,12237,12238,12239,12240,12241", "answer": "12242"}
{"prompt": "28527,28528,28529,28530,28531,28532,28533,28534,28535", "answer": "28536"}
{"prompt": "19281,19282,19283,19284,19285,19286,19287,19288", "answer": "19289"}
{"prompt": "18923,18924,18925,18926,18927,18928,18929,18930,18931", "answer": "18932"}
{"prompt": "40950", "answer": "40951"}
{"prompt": "5519,5520,5521,5522,5523,5524,5525,5526", "answer": "5527"}
{"prompt": "31522,31523,31524,31525,31526,31527,31528,31529", "answer": "31530"}
{"prompt": "9581,9582", "answer": "9583"}
{"prompt": "20594,20595,20596,20597,20598", "answer": "20599"}
{"prompt": "26795,26796,26797,26798,26799,26800,26801,26802,26803,26804", "answer": "26805"}
{"prompt": "16063", "answer": "16064"}
{"prompt": "41094,41095,41096,41097,41098", "answer": "41099"}
{"prompt": "10063,10064,10065,10066,10067,10068", "answer": "10069"}
{"prompt": "16019,16020", "answer": "16021"}
{"prompt": "22270,22271,22272,22273,22274,22275,22276,22277,22278,22279", "answer": "22280"}
{"prompt": "10611,10612,10613,10614,10615,10616,10617,10618", "answer": "10619"}
{"prompt": "14154,14155", "answer": "14156"}
{"prompt": "2670,2671,2672,2673,2674,2675,2676,2677", "answer": "2678"}
{"prompt": "17605,17606,17607,17608,17609,17610,17611,17612,17613,17614", "answer": "17615"}
{"prompt": "3276,3277,3278,3279,3280", "answer": "3281"}
{"prompt": "7377,7378,7379,7380,7381,7382", "answer": "7383"}
{"prompt": "15675", "answer": "15676"}
{"prompt": "38011,38012,38013,38014,38015", "answer": "38016"}
{"prompt": "40102,40103,40104,40105,40106,40107", "answer": "40108"}
{"prompt": "26268,26269,26270,26271,26272,26273", "answer": "26274"}
{"prompt": "38908,38909", "answer": "38910"}
{"prompt": "23335,23336,23337,23338,23339,23340,23341", "answer": "23342"}
{"prompt": "36537,36538,36539", "answer": "36540"}
{"prompt": "42954,42955,42956,42957,42958,42959,42960,42961", "answer": "42962"}
{"prompt": "10474,10475,10476,10477,10478,10479,10480,10481,10482", "answer": "10483"}
{"prompt": "33174,33175,33176,33177,33178,33179", "answer": "33180"}
{"prompt": "39790,39791", "answer": "39792"}
{"prompt": "21796,21797,21798,21799,21800,21801,21802,21803,21804", "answer": "21805"}
{"prompt": "38686,38687,38688,38689", "answer": "38690"}
{"prompt": "3390,3391,3392,3393,3394,3395,3396,3397,3398", "answer": "3399"}
{"prompt": "22348,22349,22350", "answer": "22351"}
{"prompt": "18454,18455,18456", "answer": "18457"}
{"prompt": "1", "answer": "2"}
{"prompt": "31584", "answer": "31585"}
{"prompt": "12835,12836,12837,12838,12839", "answer": "12840"}
{"prompt": "40539", "answer": "40540"}
{"prompt": "27110,27111,27112,27113,27114,27115,27116,27117,27118,27119", "answer": "27120"}
{"prompt": "22193", "answer": "22194"}
{"prompt": "37664,37665,37666,37667,37668,37669,37670", "answer": "37671"}
{"prompt": "9279,9280,9281", "answer": "9282"}
{"prompt": "6285,6286,6287,6288,6289,6290,6291,6292,6293", "answer": "6294"}
{"prompt": "2525,2526,2527,2528,2529,2530,2531", "answer": "2532"}
{"prompt": "19032,19033,19034,19035,19036,19037,19038,19039,19040", "answer": "19041"}
{"prompt": "41872", "answer": "41873"}
{"prompt": "6507,6508,6509,6510,6511", "answer": "6512"}
{"prompt": "12089", "answer": "12090"}
{"prompt": "15409,15410,15411,15412,15413,15414,15415,15416,15417", "answer": "15418"}
{"prompt": "42799,42800,42801,42802", "answer": "42803"}
{"prompt": "9596,9597,9598,9599,9600,9601", "answer": "9602"}
{"prompt": "2855", "answer": "2856"}
{"prompt": "9148,9149,9150,9151,9152,9153,9154,9155", "answer": "9156"}
{"prompt": "23445,23446,23447,23448,23449", "answer": "23450"}
{"prompt": "33329,33330", "answer": "33331"}
{"prompt": "41312", "answer": "41313"}
{"prompt": "350,351,352,353,354,355,356", "answer": "357"}
{"prompt": "13502,13503,13504,13505,13506,13507,13508,13509,13510", "answer": "13511"}
{"prompt": "13563", "answer": "13564"}
{"prompt": "44309,44310,44311,44312,44313,44314,44315", "answer": "44316"}
{"prompt": "15500,15501,15502,15503,15504", "answer": "15505"}
{"prompt": "9232,9233,9234,9235,9236,9237,9238,9239,9240", "answer": "9241"}
{"prompt": "40151,40152,40153,40154,40155,40156,40157,40158,40159", "answer": "40160"}
{"prompt": "43552,43553,43554,43555,43556,43557,43558", "answer": "43559"}
{"prompt": "38638,38639,38640,38641,38642,38643,38644,38645", "answer": "38646"}
{"prompt": "4753,4754,4755,4756,4757,4758,4759,4760,4761,4762", "answer": "4763"}
{"prompt": "36403,36404,36405,36406,36407", "answer": "36408"}
{"prompt": "39451,39452", "answer": "39453"}
{"prompt": "39938,39939", "answer": "39940"}
{"prompt": "41394,41395", "answer": "41396"}
{"prompt": "44440", "answer": "44441"}
{"prompt": "1405,1406,1407,1408,1409,1410,1411,1412,1413,1414", "answer": "1415"}
{"prompt": "30333,30334,30335,30336,30337,30338,30339,30340,30341,30342", "answer": "30343"}
{"prompt": "13903,13904,13905,13906,13907,13908,13909,13910,13911,13912", "answer": "13913"}
{"prompt": "40034,40035,40036,40037,40038,40039,40040,40041", "answer": "40042"}
{"prompt": "4726,4727,4728", "answer": "4729"}
{"prompt": "24293,24294,24295,24296,24297,24298,24299,24300,24301,24302", "answer": "24303"}
{"prompt": "7401,7402,7403,7404,7405,7406,7407,7408", "answer": "7409"}
{"prompt": "9310,9311,9312", "answer": "9313"}
{"prompt": "42524,42525,42526,42527", "answer": "42528"}
{"prompt": "22176,22177,22178,22179,22180,22181,22182,22183,22184,22185", "answer": "22186"}
{"prompt": "32307,32308,32309,32310,32311,32312,32313,32314,32315,32316", "answer": "32317"}
{"prompt": "36096,36097,36098,36099,36100", "answer": "36101"}
{"prompt": "28687", "answer": "28688"}
{"prompt": "13603", "answer": "13604"}
{"prompt": "44072,44073,44074,44075,44076,44077", "answer": "44078"}
{"prompt": "7015", "answer": "7016"}
{"prompt": "20348", "answer": "20349"}
{"prompt": "35729,35730", "answer": "35731"}
{"prompt": "42604,42605,42606,42607,42608,42609,42610,42611", "answer": "42612"}
{"prompt": "42636,42637,42638,42639,42640,42641,42642,42643", "answer": "42644"}
{"prompt": "43708,43709,43710,43711,43712", "answer": "43713"}
{"prompt": "1632,1633", "answer": "1634"}
{"prompt": "16725,16726,16727,16728,16729,16730,16731", "answer": "16732"}
{"prompt": "37943,37944,37945,37946,37947", "answer": "37948"}
{"prompt": "36455,36456,36457,36458,36459,36460,36461", "answer": "36462"}
{"prompt": "9065", "answer": "9066"}
{"prompt": "6114", "answer": "6115"}
{"prompt": "8650,8651,8652,8653,8654,8655,8656,8657", "answer": "8658"}
{"prompt": "8913,8914,8915,8916,8917,8918,8919,8920,8921", "answer": "8922"}
{"prompt": "834,835,836,837", "answer": "838"}
{"prompt": "27407,27408,27409", "answer": "27410"}
{"prompt": "33183,33184,33185", "answer": "33186"}
{"prompt": "20432,20433,20434,20435,20436,20437,20438,20439,20440", "answer": "20441"}
{"prompt": "28545,28546,28547,28548,28549", "answer": "28550"}
{"prompt": "34497,34498,34499,34500,34501,34502,34503,34504,34505", "answer": "34506"}
{"prompt": "6638,6639", "answer": "6640"}
{"prompt": "28018,28019,28020,28021", "answer": "28022"}
{"prompt": "12910,12911,12912,12913,12914,12915", "answer": "12916"}
{"prompt": "22513,22514,22515,22516,22517,22518,22519,22520,22521,22522", "answer": "22523"}
{"prompt": "36407,36408,36409,36410,36411,36412,36413,36414,36415", "answer": "36416"}
{"prompt": "29637,29638,29639,29640,29641,29642,29643,29644,29645,29646", "answer": "29647"}
{"prompt": "44973,44974,44975,44976,44977,44978,44979,44980", "answer": "44981"}
{"prompt": "8818,8819,8820,8821,8822,8823,8824", "answer": "8825"}
{"prompt": "2454,2455,2456,2457,2458", "answer": "2459"}
{"prompt": "18201,18202", "answer": "18203"}
{"prompt": "30227", "answer": "30228"}
{"prompt": "11136,11137,11138,11139,11140,11141,11142,11143,11144", "answer": "11145"}
{"prompt": "32318,32319,32320,32321,32322,32323,32324,32325,32326,32327", "answer": "32328"}
{"prompt": "44106,44107,44108,44109", "answer": "44110"}
{"prompt": "25217,25218,25219,25220", "answer": "25221"}
{"prompt": "38332,38333,38334,38335,38336,38337,38338,38339", "answer": "38340"}
{"prompt": "8704,8705,8706", "answer": "8707"}
{"prompt": "3862,3863,3864,3865,3866", "answer": "3867"}
{"prompt": "13486,13487", "answer": "13488"}
{"prompt": "35285,35286,35287,35288,35289,35290,35291,35292,35293,35294", "answer": "35295"}
{"prompt": "26542,26543,26544,26545,26546,26547,26548,26549,26550,26551", "answer": "26552"}
{"prompt": "7140,7141,7142,7143,7144,7145", "answer": "7146"}
{"prompt": "4152,4153,4154,4155,4156,4157,4158", "answer": "4159"}
{"prompt": "12600,12601,12602,12603,12604,12605", "answer": "12606"}
{"prompt": "31856,31857,31858,31859", "answer": "31860"}
{"prompt": "28115", "answer": "28116"}
{"prompt": "11067,11068,11069,11070,11071", "answer": "11072"}
{"prompt": "7600,7601,7602,7603,7604", "answer": "7605"}
{"prompt": "42839,42840,42841", "answer": "42842"}
{"prompt": "27015,27016,27017,27018,27019", "answer": "27020"}
{"prompt": "644,645,646,647,648,649", "answer": "650"}
{"prompt": "14678,14679,14680,14681", "answer": "14682"}
{"prompt": "16216,16217,16218,16219,16220,16221,16222", "answer": "16223"}
{"prompt": "15662,15663,15664,15665,15666,15667,15668", "answer": "15669"}
{"prompt": "10861,10862", "answer": "10863"}
{"prompt": "21615,21616", "answer": "21617"}
{"prompt": "35982,35983,35984,35985,35986,35987,35988", "answer": "35989"}
{"prompt": "32954,32955", "answer": "32956"}
{"prompt": "10318,10319,10320,10321,10322,10323,10324", "answer": "10325"}
{"prompt": "42968,42969,42970,42971,42972,42973", "answer": "42974"}
{"prompt": "12258,12259", "answer": "12260"}
{"prompt": "34108,34109,34110", "answer": "34111"}
{"prompt": "22631,22632", "answer": "22633"}
{"prompt": "3967,3968,3969,3970,3971,3972,3973,3974", "answer": "3975"}
{"prompt": "43232,43233,43234", "answer": "43235"}
{"prompt": "24142,24143,24144,24145,24146,24147,24148,24149,24150,24151", "answer": "24152"}
{"prompt": "9785,9786,9787,9788,9789,9790,9791,9792,9793,9794", "answer": "9795"}
{"prompt": "7245,7246", "answer": "7247"}
{"prompt": "29398,29399,29400,29401,29402,29403,29404,29405", "answer": "29406"}
{"prompt": "40806,40807,40808,40809,40810,40811,40812,40813,40814,40815", "answer": "40816"}
{"prompt": "45038,45039,45040,45041,45042,45043,45044", "answer": "45045"}
{"prompt": "20985,20986", "answer": "20987"}
{"prompt": "21019,21020,21021,21022,21023,21024,21025,21026", "answer": "21027"}
{"prompt": "39287,39288,39289,39290,39291,39292", "answer": "39293"}
{"prompt": "5328,5329,5330,5331,5332", "answer": "5333"}
{"prompt": "29196,29197,29198,29199,29200,29201,29202,29203,29204", "answer": "29205"}
{"prompt": "29213,29214,29215,29216,29217,29218,29219,29220", "answer": "29221"}
{"prompt": "25977,25978,25979,25980,25981,25982,25983,25984,25985,25986", "answer": "25987"}
{"prompt": "35239,35240,35241,35242,35243,35244,35245", "answer": "35246"}
{"prompt": "31552,31553,31554", "answer": "31555"}
{"prompt": "25148,25149,25150,25151,25152,25153,25154", "answer": "25155"}
{"prompt": "29285,29286,29287,29288,29289,29290", "answer": "29291"}
{"prompt": "40803,40804,40805,40806", "answer": "40807"}
{"prompt": "1532,1533,1534,1535,1536", "answer": "1537"}
{"prompt": "11960,11961,11962", "answer": "11963"}
{"prompt": "22228", "answer": "22229"}
{"prompt": "29234,29235,29236,29237,29238,29239,29240", "answer": "29241"}
{"prompt": "36334,36335", "answer": "36336"}
{"prompt": "13455,13456", "answer": "13457"}
{"prompt": "3866,3867,3868,3869", "answer": "3870"}
{"prompt": "16740", "answer": "16741"}
{"prompt": "15721,15722", "answer": "15723"}
{"prompt": "11436,11437,11438,11439,11440,11441", "answer": "11442"}
{"prompt": "24898,24899,24900,24901", "answer": "24902"}
{"prompt": "4340,4341,4342,4343,4344,4345,4346,4347,4348,4349", "answer": "4350"}
{"prompt": "28120", "answer": "28121"}
{"prompt": "21634,21635,21636,21637,21638,21639,21640,21641,21642", "answer": "21643"}
{"prompt": "36868,36869,36870,36871", "answer": "36872"}
{"prompt": "16047,16048,16049,16050,16051,16052,16053,16054", "answer": "16055"}
{"prompt": "35632,35633,35634", "answer": "35635"}
{"prompt": "42726,42727,42728,42729,42730,42731,42732,42733", "answer": "42734"}
{"prompt": "20324,20325,20326,20327,20328,20329,20330", "answer": "20331"}
{"prompt": "9178,9179,9180,9181,9182,9183,9184,9185", "answer": "9186"}
{"prompt": "37403,37404,37405", "answer": "37406"}
{"prompt": "23013,23014,23015,23016,23017,23018,23019,23020,23021", "answer": "23022"}
{"prompt": "23897,23898,23899", "answer": "23900"}
{"prompt": "44495", "answer": "44496"}
{"prompt": "2487,2488", "answer": "2489"}
{"prompt": "10943,10944,10945,10946,10947,10948,10949,10950,10951", "answer": "10952"}
{"prompt": "21033,21034,21035", "answer": "21036"}
{"prompt": "11059,11060", "answer": "11061"}
{"prompt": "33988,33989,33990,33991,33992", "answer": "33993"}
{"prompt": "37222", "answer": "37223"}
{"prompt": "16291,16292,16293,16294,16295,16296,16297,16298,16299", "answer": "16300"}
{"prompt": "22069,22070,22071,22072,22073,22074,22075,22076,22077,22078", "answer": "22079"}
{"prompt": "10851,10852", "answer": "10853"}
{"prompt": "23558,23559,23560,23561,23562,23563", "answer": "23564"}
{"prompt": "34343,34344,34345,34346,34347,34348", "answer": "34349"}
{"prompt": "40107,40108,40109,40110,40111,40112,40113,40114,40115", "answer": "40116"}
{"prompt": "649,650,651", "answer": "652"}
{"prompt": "29520,29521,29522,29523,29524,29525,29526", "answer": "29527"}
{"prompt": "7914,7915,7916,7917,7918,7919,7920,7921,7922,7923", "answer": "7924"}
{"prompt": "16529", "answer": "16530"}
{"prompt": "43953,43954,43955,43956", "answer": "43957"}
{"prompt": "38703,38704,38705", "answer": "38706"}
{"prompt": "9401,9402,9403,9404", "answer": "9405"}
{"prompt": "27228,27229,27230,27231,27232,27233,27234,27235,27236", "answer": "27237"}
{"prompt": "23855,23856,23857,23858,23859,23860,23861", "answer": "23862"}
{"prompt": "31619,31620,31621,31622,31623,31624,31625,31626", "answer": "31627"}
{"prompt": "28990,28991,28992,28993,28994", "answer": "28995"}
{"prompt": "14297,14298,14299", "answer": "14300"}
{"prompt": "39892,39893,39894,39895,39896,39897,39898,39899", "answer": "39900"}
{"prompt": "43909", "answer": "43910"}
{"prompt": "4597,4598,4599,4600,4601,4602,4603", "answer": "4604"}
{"prompt": "23157,23158,23159,23160,23161,23162,23163,23164,23165", "answer": "23166"}
{"prompt": "110", "answer": "111"}
{"prompt": "42937,42938,42939,42940,42941,42942,42943,42944,42945,42946", "answer": "42947"}
{"prompt": "28400,28401,28402,28403,28404,28405,28406,28407,28408,28409", "answer": "28410"}
{"prompt": "23379,23380,23381,23382,23383,23384,23385,23386,23387,23388", "answer": "23389"}
{"prompt": "9481,9482,9483,9484,9485,9486", "answer": "9487"}
{"prompt": "27436,27437,27438,27439", "answer": "27440"}
{"prompt": "42627,42628,42629,42630,42631,42632,42633,42634,42635,42636", "answer": "42637"}
{"prompt": "8620,8621,8622,8623", "answer": "8624"}
{"prompt": "14155,14156,14157,14158,14159,14160,14161,14162", "answer": "14163"}
{"prompt": "44024,44025,44026,44027", "answer": "44028"}
{"prompt": "25339,25340,25341,25342,25343", "answer": "25344"}
{"prompt": "6596,6597,6598", "answer": "6599"}
{"prompt": "8261,8262,8263,8264,8265,8266", "answer": "8267"}
{"prompt": "6500,6501,6502,6503,6504,6505,6506", "answer": "6507"}
{"prompt": "21600,21601,21602,21603,21604,21605,21606,21607", "answer": "21608"}
{"prompt": "44985", "answer": "44986"}
{"prompt": "19202,19203", "answer": "19204"}
{"prompt": "16623,16624", "answer": "16625"}
{"prompt": "17302,17303,17304,17305", "answer": "17306"}
{"prompt": "32562,32563,32564,32565,32566", "answer": "32567"}
{"prompt": "41826,41827,41828,41829,41830,41831,41832,41833,41834", "answer": "41835"}
{"prompt": "28517", "answer": "28518"}
{"prompt": "28140,28141,28142,28143,28144", "answer": "28145"}
{"prompt": "25595,25596", "answer": "25597"}
{"prompt": "4818,4819,4820,4821", "answer": "4822"}
{"prompt": "44620,44621", "answer": "44622"}
{"prompt": "42857,42858,42859,42860,42861", "answer": "42862"}
{"prompt": "16638,16639,16640", "answer": "16641"}
{"prompt": "24855,24856,24857,24858,24859,24860,24861,24862", "answer": "24863"}
{"prompt": "6700,6701,6702,6703,6704", "answer": "6705"}
{"prompt": "36637,36638,36639,36640,36641,36642,36643,36644,36645", "answer": "36646"}
{"prompt": "39818,39819,39820,39821,39822,39823", "answer": "39824"}
{"prompt": "10201,10202,10203,10204,10205,10206,10207", "answer": "10208"}
{"prompt": "9155,9156", "answer": "9157"}
{"prompt": "35473,35474", "answer": "35475"}
{"prompt": "19102,19103,19104,19105", "answer": "19106"}
{"prompt": "16390,16391,16392,16393", "answer": "16394"}
{"prompt": "20831,20832", "answer": "20833"}
{"prompt": "28645,28646,28647,28648,28649,28650,28651,28652", "answer": "28653"}
{"prompt": "24381,24382", "answer": "24383"}
{"prompt": "12012", "answer": "12013"}
{"prompt": "2058,2059,2060,2061,2062,2063,2064", "answer": "2065"}
{"prompt": "32413,32414,32415,32416,32417,32418", "answer": "32419"}
{"prompt": "7834,7835,7836", "answer": "7837"}
{"prompt": "6617,6618,6619,6620,6621,6622,6623,6624,6625", "answer": "6626"}
{"prompt": "12758,12759,12760,12761,12762,12763,12764,12765,12766", "answer": "12767"}
{"prompt": "15797,15798,15799,15800,15801,15802,15803,15804", "answer": "15805"}
{"prompt": "18065,18066,18067,18068,18069", "answer": "18070"}
{"prompt": "17901,17902,17903", "answer": "17904"}
{"prompt": "40299", "answer": "40300"}
{"prompt": "35964,35965,35966,35967,35968,35969,35970,35971", "answer": "35972"}
{"prompt": "8582,8583,8584,8585,8586,8587,8588,8589,8590", "answer": "8591"}
{"prompt": "33254,33255,33256,33257,33258,33259,33260,33261", "answer": "33262"}
{"prompt": "12587,12588,12589", "answer": "12590"}
{"prompt": "34735,34736,34737,34738,34739,34740,34741,34742,34743,34744", "answer": "34745"}
{"prompt": "40871,40872,40873,40874,40875,40876,40877,40878,40879,40880", "answer": "40881"}
{"prompt": "22413,22414,22415,22416,22417,22418,22419", "answer": "22420"}
{"prompt": "6444,6445,6446,6447,6448,6449,6450", "answer": "6451"}
{"prompt": "37074,37075,37076,37077,37078,37079,37080,37081,37082,37083", "answer": "37084"}
{"prompt": "9512,9513,9514,9515,9516,9517", "answer": "9518"}
{"prompt": "2265,2266,2267,2268,2269,2270,2271,2272,2273,2274", "answer": "2275"}
{"prompt": "37555,37556,37557,37558,37559,37560,37561,37562", "answer": "37563"}
{"prompt": "42552,42553,42554,42555,42556", "answer": "42557"}
{"prompt": "45268", "answer": "45269"}
{"prompt": "10717,10718,10719,10720,10721", "answer": "10722"}
{"prompt": "14649,14650,14651,14652,14653,14654,14655,14656", "answer": "14657"}
{"prompt": "21828,21829,21830,21831,21832,21833,21834,21835", "answer": "21836"}
{"prompt": "28758", "answer": "28759"}
{"prompt": "7473,7474,7475,7476,7477,7478,7479", "answer": "7480"}
{"prompt": "35459,35460,35461,35462,35463", "answer": "35464"}
{"prompt": "31913,31914,31915,31916,31917,31918,31919,31920,31921", "answer": "31922"}
{"prompt": "25986,25987,25988,25989,25990,25991,25992,25993,25994", "answer": "25995"}
{"prompt": "6034,6035,6036,6037,6038,6039,6040,6041", "answer": "6042"}
{"prompt": "29923,29924", "answer": "29925"}
{"prompt": "36118,36119,36120", "answer": "36121"}
{"prompt": "17313,17314,17315,17316,17317,17318,17319", "answer": "17320"}
{"prompt": "33125,33126,33127,33128,33129,33130,33131,33132", "answer": "33133"}
{"prompt": "24324,24325,24326,24327,24328,24329,24330,24331,24332,24333", "answer": "24334"}
{"prompt": "3353,3354,3355,3356", "answer": "3357"}
{"prompt": "26869,26870,26871,26872,26873", "answer": "26874"}
{"prompt": "1170,1171,1172,1173", "answer": "1174"}
{"prompt": "24043,24044,24045,24046", "answer": "24047"}
{"prompt": "204,205,206,207,208,209,210,211,212,213", "answer": "214"}
{"prompt": "14145,14146,14147,14148,14149", "answer": "14150"}
{"prompt": "30922,30923,30924,30925,30926,30927,30928,30929,30930", "answer": "30931"}
{"prompt": "38306", "answer": "38307"}
{"prompt": "35397,35398,35399,35400,35401,35402", "answer": "35403"}
{"prompt": "33693,33694,33695", "answer": "33696"}
{"prompt": "27467,27468,27469,27470,27471,27472,27473,27474", "answer": "27475"}
{"prompt": "18465,18466,18467,18468,18469,18470", "answer": "18471"}
{"prompt": "20759,20760,20761,20762,20763,20764,20765", "answer": "20766"}
{"prompt": "39485,39486,39487,39488", "answer": "39489"}
{"prompt": "9138,9139,9140,9141,9142,9143,9144", "answer": "9145"}
{"prompt": "44726,44727,44728", "answer": "44729"}
{"prompt": "1794,1795,1796,1797,1798", "answer": "1799"}
{"prompt": "10408,10409,10410,10411,10412,10413,10414", "answer": "10415"}
{"prompt": "30041,30042", "answer": "30043"}
{"prompt": "34064,34065,34066,34067,34068,34069", "answer": "34070"}
{"prompt": "200,201,202,203,204", "answer": "205"}
{"prompt": "7448,7449,7450,7451,7452,7453", "answer": "7454"}
{"prompt": "24664,24665,24666,24667,24668", "answer": "24669"}
{"prompt": "26581,26582,26583,26584,26585,26586,26587,26588,26589,26590", "answer": "26591"}
{"prompt": "4220,4221,4222,4223,4224", "answer": "4225"}
{"prompt": "28245,28246,28247,28248,28249,28250,28251", "answer": "28252"}
{"prompt": "29784,29785,29786,29787,29788", "answer": "29789"}
{"prompt": "26942,26943,26944,26945,26946,26947,26948,26949,26950", "answer": "26951"}
{"prompt": "17798,17799,17800,17801,17802,17803,17804", "answer": "17805"}
{"prompt": "23512,23513,23514", "answer": "23515"}
{"prompt": "25585,25586", "answer": "25587"}
{"prompt": "27680,27681,27682,27683,27684", "answer": "27685"}
{"prompt": "25099,25100,25101", "answer": "25102"}
{"prompt": "32017,32018,32019,32020", "answer": "32021"}
{"prompt": "44920,44921,44922,44923,44924,44925,44926", "answer": "44927"}
{"prompt": "25129,25130,25131,25132,25133", "answer": "25134"}
{"prompt": "35227,35228,35229,35230,35231,35232,35233", "answer": "35234"}
{"prompt": "36214,36215,36216,36217,36218", "answer": "36219"}
{"prompt": "19696,19697", "answer": "19698"}
{"prompt": "38726,38727", "answer": "38728"}
{"prompt": "44818,44819,44820", "answer": "44821"}
{"prompt": "28044,28045,28046,28047,28048,28049,28050", "answer": "28051"}
{"prompt": "45302,45303", "answer": "45304"}
{"prompt": "38874,38875,38876,38877,38878,38879,38880,38881", "answer": "38882"}
{"prompt": "15757,15758,15759,15760,15761,15762,15763", "answer": "15764"}
{"prompt": "7205,7206,7207,7208,7209,7210", "answer": "7211"}
{"prompt": "3029,3030,3031,3032,3033,3034,3035,3036,3037", "answer": "3038"}
{"prompt": "43361,43362", "answer": "43363"}
{"prompt": "493,494,495,496,497,498,499", "answer": "500"}
{"prompt": "19716,19717", "answer": "19718"}
{"prompt": "4514,4515,4516,4517,4518", "answer": "4519"}
{"prompt": "676,677,678,679,680,681", "answer": "682"}
{"prompt": "7496,7497,7498,7499,7500,7501,7502,7503", "answer": "7504"}
{"prompt": "36153,36154,36155,36156,36157,36158", "answer": "36159"}
{"prompt": "35596,35597,35598,35599,35600,35601,35602,35603", "answer": "35604"}
{"prompt": "17431,17432,17433", "answer": "17434"}
{"prompt": "43626,43627,43628,43629", "answer": "43630"}